SPEAKER_19: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_19: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_19: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_19: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_19: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_19: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_19: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_19: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_19: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_19: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_19: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_19: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_19: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_19: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_19: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_19: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_19: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_19: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_19: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_19: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_19: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_19: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_19: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_19: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_19: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_19: Enough?
SPEAKER_19: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_19: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_19: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_19: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_19: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_19: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_19: I wouldn't dare.