SPEAKER_18: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_18: I will remember.
SPEAKER_18: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_18: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_18: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_18: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_18: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_18: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_18: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_18: Really?
SPEAKER_18: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_18: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_18: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_18: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_18: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_18: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_18: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_18: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_18: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_18: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_18: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_18: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_18: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_18: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_18: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_18: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_18: Let me think.
SPEAKER_18: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_18: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_18: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_18: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_18: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_18: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_18: What's with him?
SPEAKER_18: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_18: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_18: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_18: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_18: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_18: Little Bun, behave yourself.