SPEAKER_17: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_17: Of course.
SPEAKER_17: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_17: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_17: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_17: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_17: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_17: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_17: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_17: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_17: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_17: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_17: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_17: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_17: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_17: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_17: They shot him.
SPEAKER_17: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_17: He is dead.
SPEAKER_17: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_17: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_17: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_17: Landlords?
SPEAKER_17: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_17: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_17: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_17: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_17: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_17: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_17: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_17: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_17: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_17: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_17: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_17: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_17: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_17: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_17: Cheers!
SPEAKER_17: Of course.
SPEAKER_17: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_17: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_17: What do you want?
SPEAKER_17: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_17: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_17: You came for this?
SPEAKER_17: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_17: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_17: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_17: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_17: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_17: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_17: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_17: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_17: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_17: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_17: He's all right.
SPEAKER_17: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_17: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_17: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_17: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_17: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_17: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_17: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_17: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_17: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_17: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_17: How about in here?