SPEAKER_06: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_06: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_06: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_06: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_06: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_06: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_06: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_06: Come inside.
SPEAKER_06: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_06: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_06: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_06: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_06: You cold?
SPEAKER_06: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_06: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_06: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_06: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_06: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_06: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_06: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_06: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_06: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_06: Yes.
SPEAKER_06: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_06: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_06: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_06: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_06: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_06: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_06: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_06: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_06: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_06: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.