SPEAKER_25: Mr. Xie...
SPEAKER_25: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_25: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_25: Sir!
SPEAKER_25: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_25: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_25: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_25: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_25: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_25: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_25: You're here.
SPEAKER_25: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_25: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_25: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_25: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_25: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_25: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_25: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_25: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_25: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_25: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_25: You won't go?
SPEAKER_25: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_25: Enough!
SPEAKER_25: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_25: What's up?
SPEAKER_25: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_25: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_25: What's happened?
SPEAKER_25: Answer me!
SPEAKER_25: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_25: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_25: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_25: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_25: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_25: No!
SPEAKER_25: The 1960s
SPEAKER_25: What do you think?
SPEAKER_25: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_25: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_25: Come on in!
SPEAKER_25: Oxygen.