SPEAKER_13: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_13: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_13: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_13: Please.
SPEAKER_13: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_13: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_13: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_13: Tell me.
SPEAKER_13: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_13: Come home.
SPEAKER_13: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_13: I've realized...
SPEAKER_13: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_13: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_13: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_13: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_13: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_13: What's his name?
SPEAKER_13: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_13: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_13: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_13: Me.
SPEAKER_13: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_13: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_13: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_13: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_13: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_13: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_13: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_13: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_13: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_13: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_13: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_13: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_13: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_13: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_13: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_13: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_13: You should have written.
SPEAKER_13: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_13: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_13: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_13: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_13: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_13: They never get...
SPEAKER_13: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_13: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_13: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_13: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_13: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_13: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_13: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_13: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_13: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_13: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_13: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_13: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_13: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_13: Of course.
SPEAKER_13: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_13: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_13: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_13: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_13: Good idea!
SPEAKER_13: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_13: Well?
SPEAKER_13: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_13: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_13: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_13: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_13: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_13: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_13: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_13: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_13: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_13: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_13: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_13: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_13: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_13: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_13: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_13: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_13: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_13: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_13: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_13: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_13: A good family.
SPEAKER_13: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_13: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_13: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_13: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_13: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_13: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_13: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_13: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_13: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_13: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_13: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_13: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_13: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_13: A cripple?
SPEAKER_13: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_13: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_13: We approve.
SPEAKER_13: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_13: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_13: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_13: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_13: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_13: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_13: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_13: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_13: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_13: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_13: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_13: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_13: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_13: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_13: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_13: Very!
SPEAKER_13: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_13: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_13: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_13: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_13: Okay.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_13: Come inside.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_13: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_13: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_13: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_13: When is it due?
SPEAKER_13: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_13: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_13: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_13: Go ask.
SPEAKER_13: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_13: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_13: Want one?
SPEAKER_13: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_13: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_13: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_13: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_13: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_13: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_13: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_13: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_13: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_13: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_13: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_13: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_13: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_13: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_13: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_13: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_13: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_13: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_13: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_13: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_13: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_13: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_13: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_13: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_13: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_13: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_13: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_13: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_13: to show her.
SPEAKER_13: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_13: Uncle.
SPEAKER_13: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_13: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_13: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_13: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_13: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_13: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_13: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_13: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_13: And then?
SPEAKER_13: And then...
SPEAKER_13: You will ride on an ox's back.
SPEAKER_13: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...