SPEAKER_11: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_11: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_11: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_11: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_11: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_11: Take that!
SPEAKER_11: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_11: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_11: Enough?
SPEAKER_11: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_11: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_11: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_11: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_11: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_11: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_11: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_11: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_11: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_11: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_11: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_11: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_11: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_11: Come over here.
SPEAKER_11: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_11: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_11: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_11: Quick!
SPEAKER_11: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_11: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_11: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_11: Some years later...