SPEAKER_03: Turtle spawn! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_03: I'll cut him into pieces! I'll clobber him!
SPEAKER_03: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_03: The 1950s
SPEAKER_03: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_03: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_03: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_03: Take a break.
SPEAKER_03: Tired?
SPEAKER_03: Fugui!
SPEAKER_03: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_03: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_03: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_03: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_03: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_03: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_03: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_03: He'll know.
SPEAKER_03: What's wrong with him? What happened?