SPEAKER_15: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_15: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_15: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_15: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_15: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_15: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_15: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_15: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_15: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_15: Just like me.
SPEAKER_15: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_15: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_15: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_15: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_15: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_15: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_15: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_15: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_15: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_15: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_15: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_15: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_15: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_15: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_15: Sit here.
SPEAKER_15: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_15: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_15: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_15: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.