SPEAKER_10: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_10: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_10: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_10: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_10: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_10: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_10: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_10: Besides...
SPEAKER_10: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_10: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_10: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_10: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_10: As for me...
SPEAKER_10: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_10: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_10: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_10: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_10: The wounded.
SPEAKER_10: No one's left.
SPEAKER_10: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_10: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_10: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_10: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_10: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_10: Daddy.
SPEAKER_10: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_10: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_10: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_10: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_10: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_10: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_10: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_10: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_10: Fugui!
SPEAKER_10: Who's there?
SPEAKER_10: Well?
SPEAKER_10: Fugui...
SPEAKER_10: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_10: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_10: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_10: Take this...
SPEAKER_10: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_10: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_10: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_10: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_10: and better get back.
SPEAKER_10: Chunsheng, remember...
SPEAKER_10: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_10: Let me wear it!