SPEAKER_12: It's settled.
SPEAKER_12: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_12: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_12: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_12: Okay?
SPEAKER_12: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_12: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_12: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_12: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_12: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_12: How could you?
SPEAKER_12: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_12: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_12: come see the show.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_12: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_12: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_12: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_12: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_12: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_12: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_12: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_12: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_12: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_12: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_12: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_12: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_12: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_12: Good idea.