SPEAKER_26: Get out!
SPEAKER_26: I've just...
SPEAKER_26: Let's play!
SPEAKER_26: Go!
SPEAKER_26: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_26: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_26: Sit down.
SPEAKER_26: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_26: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_26: Take this.
SPEAKER_26: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_26: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_26: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_26: How could you?
SPEAKER_26: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_26: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_26: What is this?
SPEAKER_26: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_26: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_26: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_26: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_26: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_26: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_26: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_26: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_26: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_26: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_26: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_26: Now!
SPEAKER_26: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_26: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_26: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_26: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_26: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_26: Go away!
SPEAKER_26: All right.
SPEAKER_26: I'm going.
SPEAKER_26: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_26: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_26: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_26: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_26: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_26: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_26: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_26: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_26: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_26: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_26: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_26: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_26: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_26: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_26: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_26: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_26: He was starving.
SPEAKER_26: But he was okay after the water.
SPEAKER_26: It was the water that did it.