SPEAKER_04: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_04: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_04: You're up.
SPEAKER_04: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_04: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui...
SPEAKER_04: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_04: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_04: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_04: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_04: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_04: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_04: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_04: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_04: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_04: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_04: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_04: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_04: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_04: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_04: When you get there...
SPEAKER_04: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_04: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_04: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_04: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_04: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_04: That's good.
SPEAKER_04: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_04: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_04: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_04: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_04: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_04: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_04: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_04: From where?
SPEAKER_04: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_04: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_04: On the mend.
SPEAKER_04: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_04: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_04: This is great.
SPEAKER_04: Who?
SPEAKER_04: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_04: Why?
SPEAKER_04: I don't know.
SPEAKER_04: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_04: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_04: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_04: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_04: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_04: You just have to!
SPEAKER_04: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_04: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_04: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_04: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_04: Is it?
SPEAKER_04: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_04: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_04: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_04: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_04: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_04: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_04: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_04: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_04: Let's see.
SPEAKER_04: And soon they'll grow up.