SPEAKER_26: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_26: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_26: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_26: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_26: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_26: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_26: Just like me.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_26: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_26: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_26: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_26: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_26: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_26: What's happened?
SPEAKER_26: Answer me!
SPEAKER_26: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_26: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_26: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_26: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_26: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_26: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_26: Move aside! Stand still!