SPEAKER_12: Take care.
SPEAKER_12: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_12: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_12: Dad!
SPEAKER_12: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_12: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_12: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_12: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_12: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_12: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_12: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_12: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_12: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_12: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_12: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_12: Cheers!
SPEAKER_12: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_12: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_12: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_12: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_12: Yes, 7.9 pounds!