SPEAKER_08: Get out!
SPEAKER_08: I've just...
SPEAKER_08: Let's play!
SPEAKER_08: Go!
SPEAKER_08: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_08: Sit down.
SPEAKER_08: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_08: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_08: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_08: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_08: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_08: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_08: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_08: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_08: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_08: Take this.
SPEAKER_08: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_08: How could you?
SPEAKER_08: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_08: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_08: What is this?
SPEAKER_08: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_08: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_08: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_08: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_08: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_08: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_08: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_08: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_08: Now!
SPEAKER_08: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_08: Go away!
SPEAKER_08: All right.
SPEAKER_08: I'm going.
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_08: How dare you!
SPEAKER_08: What's going on?
SPEAKER_08: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_08: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_08: Let her go!
SPEAKER_08: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_08: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_08: No!
SPEAKER_08: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_08: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_08: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_08: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_08: Come on in!
SPEAKER_08: Sit down.
SPEAKER_08: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_08: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_08: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_08: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_08: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_08: He was starving.
SPEAKER_08: But he was okay after the water.