SPEAKER_00: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_00: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_00: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_00: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_00: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_00: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_00: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_00: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_00: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_00: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_00: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_00: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_00: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_00: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_00: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_00: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_00: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_00: The only child I have left.