SPEAKER_20: Besides...
SPEAKER_20: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_20: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_20: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_20: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_20: As for me...
SPEAKER_20: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_20: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_20: The wounded.
SPEAKER_20: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_20: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_20: No one's left.
SPEAKER_20: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_20: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_20: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_20: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_20: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_20: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_20: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_20: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_20: Run now...
SPEAKER_20: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_20: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_20: That's right.
SPEAKER_20: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_20: How?
SPEAKER_20: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_20: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_20: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_20: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_20: The coat's from my brother's unit.