SPEAKER_13: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_13: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_13: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_13: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_13: wounded me
SPEAKER_13: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_13: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_13: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_13: You won't go?
SPEAKER_13: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_13: Enough!
SPEAKER_13: How could you?
SPEAKER_13: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_13: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_13: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_13: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_13: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_13: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_13: Please come again.
SPEAKER_13: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_13: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_13: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_13: Come over here.
SPEAKER_13: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_13: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_13: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_13: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_13: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_13: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_13: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_13: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_13: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_13: Oxygen.