SPEAKER_03: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_03: How much?
SPEAKER_03: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_03: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_03: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_03: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_03: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_03: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_03: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_03: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_03: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui...
SPEAKER_03: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_03: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_03: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_03: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_03: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_03: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_03: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_03: It's settled.
SPEAKER_03: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_03: Of course.
SPEAKER_03: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_03: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_03: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_03: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_03: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_03: Okay?
SPEAKER_03: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_03: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_03: What's his name?
SPEAKER_03: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_03: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_03: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_03: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_03: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_03: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_03: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_03: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_03: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_03: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_03: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_03: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_03: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_03: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_03: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_03: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_03: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_03: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_03: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_03: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_03: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_03: They shot him.
SPEAKER_03: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_03: He is dead.
SPEAKER_03: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_03: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_03: Landlords?
SPEAKER_03: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_03: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_03: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_03: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_03: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_03: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_03: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_03: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_03: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_03: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_03: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_03: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_03: How so?
SPEAKER_03: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_03: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_03: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_03: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_03: come see the show.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_03: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_03: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_03: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_03: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_03: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_03: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_03: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_03: When you get there...
SPEAKER_03: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_03: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_03: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_03: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_03: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_03: That's good.
SPEAKER_03: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_03: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_03: Our family...
SPEAKER_03: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_03: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_03: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_03: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_03: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_03: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_03: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_03: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_03: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_03: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_03: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_03: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_03: Sit here.
SPEAKER_03: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_03: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_03: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_03: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_03: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_03: No, really.
SPEAKER_03: From where?
SPEAKER_03: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_03: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_03: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_03: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_03: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_03: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_03: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_03: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_03: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_03: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_03: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_03: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_03: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_03: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_03: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_03: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_03: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_03: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_03: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_03: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_03: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_03: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_03: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_03: On the mend.
SPEAKER_03: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_03: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_03: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_03: Really?
SPEAKER_03: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_03: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_03: This is great.
SPEAKER_03: Of course.
SPEAKER_03: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_03: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_03: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_03: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_03: You came for this?
SPEAKER_03: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_03: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_03: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_03: Why?
SPEAKER_03: I don't know.
SPEAKER_03: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_03: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_03: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_03: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_03: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_03: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_03: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_03: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_03: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_03: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_03: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_03: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_03: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_03: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_03: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_03: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_03: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_03: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_03: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_03: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_03: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_03: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_03: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_03: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_03: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_03: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_03: He's all right.
SPEAKER_03: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_03: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_03: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_03: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_03: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_03: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_03: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_03: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_03: Help us!
SPEAKER_03: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_03: Quick!
SPEAKER_03: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_03: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_03: Is it?
SPEAKER_03: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_03: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_03: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_03: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_03: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_03: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_03: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_03: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_03: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_03: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_03: How about in here?
SPEAKER_03: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_03: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_03: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_03: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_03: And then...
SPEAKER_03: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_03: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_03: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_03: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...