SPEAKER_06: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_06: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_06: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_06: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_06: wounded me
SPEAKER_06: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_06: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_06: You won't go?
SPEAKER_06: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_06: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_06: Enough!
SPEAKER_06: How could you?
SPEAKER_06: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_06: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_06: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_06: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_06: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_06: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_06: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_06: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_06: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_06: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_06: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_06: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_06: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_06: Go away!
SPEAKER_06: All right.
SPEAKER_06: I'm going.
SPEAKER_06: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_06: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_06: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_06: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_06: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_06: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_06: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_06: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_06: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_06: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_06: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_06: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_06: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_06: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_06: Oxygen.