SPEAKER_19: Besides...
SPEAKER_19: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_19: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_19: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_19: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_19: As for me...
SPEAKER_19: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_19: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_19: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_19: The wounded.
SPEAKER_19: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_19: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_19: No one's left.
SPEAKER_19: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_19: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_19: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_19: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_19: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_19: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_19: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_19: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_19: Run now...
SPEAKER_19: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_19: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_19: That's right.
SPEAKER_19: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_19: How?
SPEAKER_19: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_19: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_19: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_19: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_19: The coat's from my brother's unit.