SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_18: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_18: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_18: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_18: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_18: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_18: How could that be?
SPEAKER_18: So, no running?
SPEAKER_18: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_18: Let her go!
SPEAKER_18: We must be going.
SPEAKER_18: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_18: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_18: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_18: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_18: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_18: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_18: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_18: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_18: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_18: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_18: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_18: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_18: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_18: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_18: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_18: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_18: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_18: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_18: It's okay.
SPEAKER_18: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_18: anything made from wheat.