SPEAKER_07: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_07: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_07: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_07: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_07: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_07: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_07: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_07: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_07: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_07: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_07: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_07: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_07: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_07: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_07: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_07: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_07: The 1940s
SPEAKER_07: Is gambling all you know?
SPEAKER_07: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_07: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_07: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_07: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_07: Take that!
SPEAKER_07: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_07: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_07: Enough?
SPEAKER_07: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_07: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_07: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_07: Come over here.
SPEAKER_07: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_07: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_07: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_07: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_07: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_07: You'll pull through!
SPEAKER_07: It's all right.
SPEAKER_07: Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_07: Some years later...