SPEAKER_27: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_27: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_27: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_27: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_27: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_27: from making you go.
SPEAKER_27: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_27: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_27: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_27: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_27: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_27: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_27: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_27: Go away!
SPEAKER_27: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_27: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_27: You killed him.
SPEAKER_27: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_27: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_27: Fengxia! You'll pull through.
Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_27: Please, Doctor, she's my only daughter.