SPEAKER_11: Get out!
SPEAKER_11: I've just...
SPEAKER_11: Let's play!
SPEAKER_11: Go!
SPEAKER_11: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_11: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_11: Sit down.
SPEAKER_11: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_11: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_11: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_11: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_11: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_11: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_11: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_11: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_11: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_11: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_11: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_11: Take this.
SPEAKER_11: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_11: How could you?
SPEAKER_11: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_11: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_11: What is this?
SPEAKER_11: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_11: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_11: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_11: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_11: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_11: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_11: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_11: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_11: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_11: Now!
SPEAKER_11: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_11: Daddy.
SPEAKER_11: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_11: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_11: How dare you!
SPEAKER_11: What's going on?
SPEAKER_11: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_11: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_11: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_11: No!
SPEAKER_11: The 1960s
SPEAKER_11: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_11: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_11: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_11: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_11: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_11: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_11: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_11: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_11: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_11: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_11: Come on in!
SPEAKER_11: Sit down.
SPEAKER_11: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_11: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_11: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_11: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_11: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_11: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_11: He was starving.
SPEAKER_11: But he was okay after the water.