SPEAKER_03: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_03: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_03: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_03: I see your point.
SPEAKER_03: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_03: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_03: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_03: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_03: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_03: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_03: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_03: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_03: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_03: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_03: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_03: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_03: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_03: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_03: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_03: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_03: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_03: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_03: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_03: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_03: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's about to give birth?