SPEAKER_22: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_22: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_22: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_22: Take a break.
SPEAKER_22: Tired?
SPEAKER_22: Fugui!
SPEAKER_22: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_22: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_22: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_22: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_22: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_22: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_22: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_22: What do you think?
SPEAKER_22: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_22: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_22: Yes.
SPEAKER_22: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_22: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_22: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_22: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_22: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_22: He'd know for sure.