SPEAKER_16: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_16: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_16: Sit down.
SPEAKER_16: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_16: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_16: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_16: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_16: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_16: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_16: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_16: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_16: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_16: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_16: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_16: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_16: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_16: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_16: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_16: How could that be?
SPEAKER_16: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_16: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_16: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_16: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_16: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_16: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_16: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_16: Just like me.
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_16: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_16: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_16: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_16: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_16: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_16: You won't go?
SPEAKER_16: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_16: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_16: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_16: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_16: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_16: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_16: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_16: Daddy.
SPEAKER_16: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_16: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_16: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_16: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_16: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_16: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_16: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_16: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_16: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_16: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_16: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_16: Go away!
SPEAKER_16: All right.
SPEAKER_16: I'm going.
SPEAKER_16: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_16: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_16: How dare you!
SPEAKER_16: What's going on?
SPEAKER_16: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_16: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_16: Let her go!
SPEAKER_16: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_16: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_16: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_16: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_16: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_16: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_16: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_16: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_16: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_16: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_16: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.