SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_12: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_12: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_12: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_12: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_12: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_12: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_12: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_12: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_12: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_12: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_12: Both sides must sign.
SPEAKER_12: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_12: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_12: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_12: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_12: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_12: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_12: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_12: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_12: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_12: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_12: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_12: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_12: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_12: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_12: Take this.
SPEAKER_12: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_12: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_12: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_12: Enough?
SPEAKER_12: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_12: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_12: Now!
SPEAKER_12: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_12: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_12: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_12: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_12: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_12: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_12: Who?
SPEAKER_12: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_12: What do you want?
SPEAKER_12: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_12: But he was okay after the water.