SPEAKER_06: A dog's gotta eat shit! Little bastard!
SPEAKER_06: If you don't stop...
SPEAKER_06: we'll lose the little we have.
SPEAKER_06: Aren't you capable of anything else?
SPEAKER_06: Is gambling all you know?
SPEAKER_06: Of all you could have learned, bastard!
SPEAKER_06: Will you cut it out?
SPEAKER_06: - What'd he just say?
- Nothing. Eat.
SPEAKER_06: Good.
SPEAKER_06: A gambling debt's a debt,
and debts must be paid.
SPEAKER_06: Everyone's here today.
SPEAKER_06: So let's do what must be done.
SPEAKER_06: I thought I'd live my final days here.
SPEAKER_06: Fugui.
SPEAKER_06: Turtle spawn! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_06: I'll cut him into pieces! I'll clobber him!
SPEAKER_06: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_06: It's ready.