SPEAKER_03: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_03: want more time
SPEAKER_03: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_03: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_03: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_03: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_03: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_03: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_03: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_03: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_03: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_03: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_03: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_03: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_03: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_03: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_03: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_03: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_03: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_03: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_03: What is this?
SPEAKER_03: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_03: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_03: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_03: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_03: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_03: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_03: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_03: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_03: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_03: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_03: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_03: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_03: What's happened?
SPEAKER_03: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_03: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_03: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_03: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_03: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_03: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_03: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_03: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_03: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_03: What's wrong with him? What happened?