SPEAKER_17: Well?
SPEAKER_17: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_17: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_17: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_17: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_17: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_17: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_17: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_17: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_17: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_17: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_17: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_17: come see the show.
SPEAKER_17: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_17: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_17: It's money.
SPEAKER_17: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_17: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_17: I will remember.
SPEAKER_17: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_17: Let's go.
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_17: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_17: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_17: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_17: Never mind.
SPEAKER_17: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_17: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui!
SPEAKER_17: Who's there?
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_17: Take this...
SPEAKER_17: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_17: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_17: No.
SPEAKER_17: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_17: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_17: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_17: and better get back.
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng, remember...