SPEAKER_13: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_13: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_13: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_13: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_13: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_13: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_13: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_13: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_13: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_13: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_13: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_13: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_13: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_13: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_13: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_13: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_13: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_13: Really?
SPEAKER_13: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_13: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_13: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_13: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_13: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_13: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_13: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_13: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_13: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_13: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_13: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_13: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_13: No.
SPEAKER_13: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_13: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_13: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_13: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_13: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_13: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_13: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_13: Let me think.
SPEAKER_13: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_13: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_13: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_13: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_13: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_13: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_13: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_13: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_13: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_13: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_13: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_13: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_13: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_13: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_13: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_13: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_13: Little Bun, behave yourself.