SPEAKER_20: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_20: Take care.
SPEAKER_20: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_20: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_20: Dad!
SPEAKER_20: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_20: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_20: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_20: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_20: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_20: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_20: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_20: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_20: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_20: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_20: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_20: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_20: We must be going.
SPEAKER_20: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_20: Please come again.
SPEAKER_20: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_20: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_20: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_20: Come on in!
SPEAKER_20: Sit down.
SPEAKER_20: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_20: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_20: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_20: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_20: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_20: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_20: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_20: Good idea.
SPEAKER_20: What's with him?
SPEAKER_20: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_20: Don't panic. Think of something.