SPEAKER_18: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_18: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_18: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_18: Besides...
SPEAKER_18: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_18: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_18: As for me...
SPEAKER_18: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_18: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_18: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_18: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_18: The wounded.
SPEAKER_18: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_18: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_18: No one's left.
SPEAKER_18: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_18: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_18: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_18: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_18: Home!
SPEAKER_18: Home?
SPEAKER_18: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_18: Run now...
SPEAKER_18: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_18: That's right.
SPEAKER_18: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_18: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_18: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_18: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_18: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_18: It's all in this account. Take it.