SPEAKER_05: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_05: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_05: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_05: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_05: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_05: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_05: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_05: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_05: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_05: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_05: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_05: I'm home.
SPEAKER_05: Home.
SPEAKER_05: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_05: He is dead.
SPEAKER_05: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_05: I approve.
SPEAKER_05: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_05: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_05: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_05: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_05: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_05: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_05: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_05: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_05: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_05: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_05: He's all right.
SPEAKER_05: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_05: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_05: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_05: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_05: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_05: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_05: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_05: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_05: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_05: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_05: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_05: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_05: Let's see.
SPEAKER_05: How about in here?
SPEAKER_05: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_05: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_05: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_05: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_05: And then...
SPEAKER_05: and the sheep will turn into oxen.