SPEAKER_16: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_16: want more time
SPEAKER_16: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_16: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_16: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_16: Come out!
SPEAKER_16: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_16: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_16: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_16: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_16: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_16: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_16: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_16: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_16: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_16: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_16: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_16: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.