SPEAKER_06: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_06: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_06: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_06: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_06: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_06: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_06: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_06: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_06: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_06: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_06: Of course.
SPEAKER_06: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_06: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_06: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_06: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_06: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_06: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_06: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_06: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_06: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_06: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_06: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_06: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_06: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_06: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_06: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_06: Landlords?
SPEAKER_06: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_06: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_06: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_06: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_06: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_06: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_06: How could you?
SPEAKER_06: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_06: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_06: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_06: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_06: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_06: How so?
SPEAKER_06: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_06: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_06: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_06: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_06: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_06: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_06: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_06: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_06: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_06: Daddy.
SPEAKER_06: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_06: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_06: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_06: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_06: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_06: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_06: No, really.
SPEAKER_06: From where?
SPEAKER_06: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_06: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_06: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_06: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_06: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_06: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_06: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_06: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_06: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_06: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_06: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_06: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_06: This is great.
SPEAKER_06: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_06: You just have to!
SPEAKER_06: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_06: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_06: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_06: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_06: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_06: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_06: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_06: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_06: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_06: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_06: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_06: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_06: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_06: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_06: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_06: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_06: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_06: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_06: Is it?
SPEAKER_06: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_06: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_06: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_06: Are you happy?