SPEAKER_15: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_15: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_15: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_15: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_15: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_15: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_15: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_15: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_15: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_15: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_15: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_15: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_15: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_15: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_15: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_15: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_15: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_15: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_15: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_15: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_15: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_15: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_15: Come over here.
SPEAKER_15: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_15: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_15: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_15: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_15: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_15: Some years later...