SPEAKER_23: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_23: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_23: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_23: Please.
SPEAKER_23: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_23: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_23: Tell me.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_23: Come home.
SPEAKER_23: I've realized...
SPEAKER_23: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_23: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_23: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_23: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_23: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_23: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_23: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_23: What's his name?
SPEAKER_23: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_23: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_23: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_23: Me.
SPEAKER_23: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_23: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_23: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_23: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_23: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_23: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_23: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_23: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_23: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_23: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_23: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_23: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_23: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_23: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_23: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_23: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_23: You should have written.
SPEAKER_23: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_23: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_23: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_23: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_23: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_23: They never get...
SPEAKER_23: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_23: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_23: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_23: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_23: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_23: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_23: You're here.
SPEAKER_23: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_23: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_23: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_23: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_23: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_23: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_23: Of course.
SPEAKER_23: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_23: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_23: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_23: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_23: Good idea!
SPEAKER_23: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_23: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_23: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_23: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_23: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_23: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_23: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_23: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_23: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_23: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_23: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_23: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_23: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_23: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_23: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_23: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_23: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_23: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_23: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_23: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_23: Come inside.
SPEAKER_23: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_23: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_23: A good family.
SPEAKER_23: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_23: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_23: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_23: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_23: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_23: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_23: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_23: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_23: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_23: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_23: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_23: A cripple?
SPEAKER_23: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_23: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_23: We approve.
SPEAKER_23: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_23: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_23: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_23: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_23: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_23: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_23: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_23: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_23: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_23: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_23: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_23: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_23: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_23: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_23: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_23: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_23: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_23: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_23: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_23: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_23: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_23: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_23: Come inside.
SPEAKER_23: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_23: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_23: What's happened?
SPEAKER_23: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_23: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_23: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_23: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_23: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_23: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_23: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_23: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_23: Go ask.
SPEAKER_23: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_23: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_23: Want one?
SPEAKER_23: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_23: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_23: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_23: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_23: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_23: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_23: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_23: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_23: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_23: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_23: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_23: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_23: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_23: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_23: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_23: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_23: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_23: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_23: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_23: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_23: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_23: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_23: Have some water.
SPEAKER_23: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_23: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_23: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_23: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_23: to show her.
SPEAKER_23: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_23: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_23: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_23: Uncle.
SPEAKER_23: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_23: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_23: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_23: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_23: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_23: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_23: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_23: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_23: After oxen...
SPEAKER_23: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_23: You will ride on an ox's back.