SPEAKER_12: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_12: Get out!
SPEAKER_12: I've just...
SPEAKER_12: Let's play!
SPEAKER_12: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_12: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_12: Sir!
SPEAKER_12: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_12: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_12: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_12: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_12: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_12: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_12: Just like me.
SPEAKER_12: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_12: wounded me
SPEAKER_12: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_12: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_12: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_12: You won't go?
SPEAKER_12: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_12: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_12: What's up?
SPEAKER_12: What's happened?
SPEAKER_12: Answer me!
SPEAKER_12: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_12: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_12: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_12: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_12: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_12: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_12: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_12: Go away!
SPEAKER_12: All right.
SPEAKER_12: I'm going.
SPEAKER_12: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_12: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_12: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_12: He was starving.
SPEAKER_12: But he was okay after the water.