SPEAKER_02: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_02: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_02: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui...
SPEAKER_02: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_02: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_02: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_02: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_02: Granny!
SPEAKER_02: What do you know?
SPEAKER_02: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_02: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_02: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_02: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_02: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_02: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_02: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_02: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_02: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_02: from making you go.
SPEAKER_02: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_02: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_02: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_02: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_02: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_02: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_02: Go away!
SPEAKER_02: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him.
SPEAKER_02: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_02: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_02: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_02: Very!
SPEAKER_02: What a clever boy!