SPEAKER_19: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_19: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_19: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_19: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_19: Okay?
SPEAKER_19: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_19: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_19: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_19: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_19: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_19: Enough?
SPEAKER_19: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_19: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_19: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_19: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_19: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_19: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_19: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_19: No idea! The leader is a cripple.