SPEAKER_07: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_07: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_07: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_07: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_07: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_07: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_07: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_07: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_07: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_07: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_07: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_07: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_07: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_07: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_07: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_07: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_07: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_07: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_07: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_07: Fugui...
SPEAKER_07: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_07: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_07: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_07: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_07: They shot him.
SPEAKER_07: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_07: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_07: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_07: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_07: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_07: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_07: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_07: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_07: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_07: When you get there...
SPEAKER_07: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_07: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_07: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_07: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_07: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_07: That's good.
SPEAKER_07: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_07: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_07: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_07: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_07: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_07: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_07: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_07: Fugui...
SPEAKER_07: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_07: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_07: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_07: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_07: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_07: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_07: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_07: I will remember.
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_07: How dare you!
SPEAKER_07: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_07: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_07: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_07: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_07: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_07: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_07: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_07: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_07: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_07: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_07: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_07: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_07: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_07: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_07: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_07: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_07: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_07: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_07: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_07: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_07: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_07: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_07: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_07: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_07: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_07: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_07: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_07: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_07: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_07: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_07: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_07: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_07: and better get back.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng, remember...
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_07: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_07: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_07: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_07: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_07: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_07: Some water should help.