SPEAKER_10: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_10: Well?
SPEAKER_10: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_10: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_10: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_10: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_10: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_10: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_10: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_10: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_10: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_10: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_10: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_10: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_10: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_10: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_10: Don't move.
SPEAKER_10: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_10: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_10: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_10: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_10: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_10: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_10: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_10: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_10: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_10: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_10: Back already?
SPEAKER_10: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_10: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa, where will the chicks live?
SPEAKER_10: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_10: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_10: Very soon.
SPEAKER_10: And then?
SPEAKER_10: I want to ride on an ox's back!