SPEAKER_20: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_20: How much?
SPEAKER_20: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_20: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_20: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_20: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_20: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_20: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_20: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_20: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_20: It's settled.
SPEAKER_20: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_20: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_20: As for me...
SPEAKER_20: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_20: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_20: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_20: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_20: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_20: The day...
SPEAKER_20: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_20: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_20: Written?
SPEAKER_20: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_20: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_20: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_20: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_20: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_20: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_20: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_20: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_20: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_20: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_20: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_20: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_20: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_20: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_20: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_20: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_20: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_20: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_20: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_20: Wake up.
SPEAKER_20: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_20: Our family...
SPEAKER_20: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_20: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_20: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_20: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_20: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_20: that we could...
SPEAKER_20: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_20: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_20: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_20: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_20: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_20: He can run?
SPEAKER_20: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_20: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_20: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_20: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_20: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_20: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_20: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_20: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_20: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_20: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_20: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_20: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_20: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_20: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_20: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_20: Of course.
SPEAKER_20: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_20: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_20: You came for this?
SPEAKER_20: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_20: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_20: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_20: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_20: They did.
SPEAKER_20: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_20: No.
SPEAKER_20: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_20: No doctors?
SPEAKER_20: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_20: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_20: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_20: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_20: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_20: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_20: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_20: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_20: Help us!
SPEAKER_20: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_20: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_20: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_20: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_20: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_20: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_20: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_20: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_20: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_20: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_20: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_20: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_20: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_20: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_20: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_20: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_20: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_20: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_20: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_20: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_20: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_20: and life will get better and better.