SPEAKER_09: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_09: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_09: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_09: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_09: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_09: wounded me
SPEAKER_09: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_09: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_09: You won't go?
SPEAKER_09: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_09: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_09: Enough!
SPEAKER_09: How could you?
SPEAKER_09: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_09: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_09: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_09: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_09: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_09: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_09: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_09: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_09: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_09: Please come again.
SPEAKER_09: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_09: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_09: Come over here.
SPEAKER_09: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_09: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_09: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_09: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_09: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_09: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_09: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_09: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_09: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_09: Oxygen.