SPEAKER_04: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_04: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_04: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_04: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_04: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_04: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_04: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_04: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_04: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_04: Enough?
SPEAKER_04: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_04: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_04: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_04: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_04: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_04: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_04: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_04: Are you happy?