SPEAKER_06: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_06: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_06: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_06: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_06: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_06: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_06: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_06: So, no running?
SPEAKER_06: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_06: come see the show.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_06: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_06: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_06: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_06: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_06: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_06: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_06: We must be going.
SPEAKER_06: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_06: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_06: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_06: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_06: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_06: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_06: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_06: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_06: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_06: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_06: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_06: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_06: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_06: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_06: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_06: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_06: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_06: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_06: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_06: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_06: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_06: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_06: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_06: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_06: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_06: What's with him?
SPEAKER_06: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_06: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_06: Have some water.
SPEAKER_06: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_06: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_06: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_06: It's okay.
SPEAKER_06: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_06: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_06: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.