SPEAKER_12: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_12: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_12: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_12: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_12: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_12: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_12: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_12: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_12: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_12: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_12: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_12: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_12: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_12: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_12: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_12: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_12: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_12: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_12: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_12: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_12: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_12: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_12: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_12: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_12: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_12: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_12: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_12: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_12: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_12: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_12: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_12: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_12: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_12: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_12: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_12: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_12: Quick, get some water.