SPEAKER_19: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_19: How much?
SPEAKER_19: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_19: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_19: Dad!
SPEAKER_19: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_19: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_19: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_19: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_19: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_19: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_19: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_19: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_19: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_19: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_19: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_19: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_19: Sit down.
SPEAKER_19: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_19: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_19: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_19: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.