SPEAKER_21: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_21: Take care.
SPEAKER_21: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_21: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_21: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_21: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_21: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_21: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_21: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_21: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_21: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_21: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_21: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_21: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_21: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_21: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_21: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_21: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_21: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_21: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_21: What do you want?
SPEAKER_21: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_21: Let me think.
SPEAKER_21: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_21: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_21: Please, I'm the father!