SPEAKER_14: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_14: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_14: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_14: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_14: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_14: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_14: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_14: Well?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_14: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: Well?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_14: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_14: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_14: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_14: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_14: What is it?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_14: Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_14: What?
SPEAKER_14: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_14: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_14: Good.
SPEAKER_14: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_14: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_14: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_14: Chunsheng.