SPEAKER_05: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_05: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_05: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_05: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_05: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_05: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_05: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_05: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_05: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_05: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_05: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_05: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_05: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_05: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_05: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_05: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_05: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_05: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_05: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_05: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_05: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_05: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_05: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_05: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_05: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_05: How so?
SPEAKER_05: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_05: What do you know?
SPEAKER_05: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_05: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_05: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_05: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_05: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_05: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_05: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_05: Fugui...
SPEAKER_05: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_05: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_05: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_05: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_05: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_05: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_05: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_05: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_05: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_05: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_05: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_05: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_05: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_05: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_05: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_05: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_05: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_05: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_05: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_05: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_05: No, really.
SPEAKER_05: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_05: I approve.
SPEAKER_05: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_05: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_05: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_05: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_05: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_05: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_05: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_05: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_05: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_05: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_05: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_05: Have some water.
SPEAKER_05: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_05: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_05: They'll have more room to run around.