SPEAKER_24: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_24: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_24: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_24: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_24: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_24: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_24: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_24: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_24: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_24: So, no running?
SPEAKER_24: This is too much.
SPEAKER_24: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_24: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_24: We must be going.
SPEAKER_24: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_24: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_24: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_24: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_24: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_24: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_24: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_24: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_24: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_24: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_24: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_24: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_24: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_24: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_24: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_24: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_24: It's okay.