SPEAKER_27: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_27: Take care.
SPEAKER_27: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_27: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_27: Dad!
SPEAKER_27: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_27: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_27: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_27: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_27: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_27: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_27: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_27: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_27: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_27: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_27: Please come again.
SPEAKER_27: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_27: Sit down.
SPEAKER_27: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_27: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_27: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_27: Please, I'm the father!