SPEAKER_16: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_16: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_16: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_16: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_16: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_16: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_16: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_16: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_16: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_16: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_16: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_16: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_16: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_16: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_16: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_16: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_16: The 1940s
SPEAKER_16: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_16: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_16: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_16: How much?
SPEAKER_16: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_16: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_16: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_16: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_16: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_16: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_16: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_16: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_16: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_16: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_16: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_16: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_16: As for me...
SPEAKER_16: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_16: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_16: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_16: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_16: The day...
SPEAKER_16: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_16: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_16: Written?
SPEAKER_16: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_16: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_16: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_16: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_16: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_16: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_16: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_16: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_16: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_16: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_16: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_16: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_16: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_16: Wake up.
SPEAKER_16: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_16: Our family...
SPEAKER_16: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_16: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_16: that we could...
SPEAKER_16: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_16: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_16: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_16: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_16: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_16: He can run?
SPEAKER_16: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_16: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_16: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_16: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_16: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_16: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_16: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_16: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_16: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_16: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_16: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_16: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_16: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_16: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_16: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_16: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_16: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_16: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_16: They did.
SPEAKER_16: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_16: No doctors?
SPEAKER_16: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_16: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_16: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_16: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_16: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_16: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_16: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_16: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_16: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_16: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_16: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_16: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_16: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_16: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_16: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_16: Help us!
SPEAKER_16: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_16: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_16: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_16: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_16: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_16: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_16: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_16: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_16: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_16: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_16: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_16: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_16: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_16: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_16: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_16: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_16: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_16: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_16: and life will get better and better.