SPEAKER_07: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_07: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_07: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_07: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_07: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_07: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_07: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_07: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_07: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_07: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_07: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_07: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_07: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_07: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_07: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_07: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_07: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_07: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_07: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_07: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_07: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_07: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_07: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_07: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_07: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_07: and after that...
SPEAKER_07: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_07: I see your point.
SPEAKER_07: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_07: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_07: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_07: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_07: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_07: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_07: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_07: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_07: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_07: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_07: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_07: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_07: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_07: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_07: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_07: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_07: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_07: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_07: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_07: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_07: Let's go.
SPEAKER_07: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_07: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_07: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_07: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_07: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_07: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_07: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_07: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_07: What's happened?
SPEAKER_07: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_07: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_07: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_07: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_07: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_07: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_07: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_07: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!