SPEAKER_02: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_02: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui...
SPEAKER_02: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_02: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_02: Granny!
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_02: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_02: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_02: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_02: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_02: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_02: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_02: from making you go.
SPEAKER_02: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_02: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_02: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_02: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_02: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_02: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_02: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_02: Go away!
SPEAKER_02: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_02: You killed him.
SPEAKER_02: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_02: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_02: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?