SPEAKER_23: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_23: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_23: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_23: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_23: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_23: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_23: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_23: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_23: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_23: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_23: How could that be?
SPEAKER_23: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_23: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_23: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_23: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_23: It's ready.
SPEAKER_23: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_23: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_23: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_23: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_23: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_23: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_23: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_23: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_23: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_23: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_23: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_23: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_23: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_23: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_23: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_23: How dare you!
SPEAKER_23: What's going on?
SPEAKER_23: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_23: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_23: Let her go!
SPEAKER_23: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_23: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_23: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_23: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_23: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_23: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.