SPEAKER_29: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_29: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_29: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_29: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_29: Look at this.
SPEAKER_29: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_29: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_29: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_29: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_29: It's all here?
SPEAKER_29: Keep these.
SPEAKER_29: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_29: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_29: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_29: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_29: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_29: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_29: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_29: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_29: Fugui...
SPEAKER_29: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_29: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_29: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_29: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_29: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_29: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.