SPEAKER_20: I'm home.
SPEAKER_20: Home.
SPEAKER_20: It's money.
SPEAKER_20: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_20: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_20: Never mind.
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_20: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_20: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_20: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_20: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_20: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_20: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_20: No.
SPEAKER_20: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_20: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_20: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_20: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_20: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_20: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_20: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_20: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_20: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.