SPEAKER_03: Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_03: No, no. I think it's better alone.
SPEAKER_03: Or I introduce him.
Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_03: Gustavo Rojas, he is chief
of the Kawiyarí tribe...
SPEAKER_03: Well, there's many different ones.
Like Tucanos, and some others...
SPEAKER_03: Let's stop for a minute. One question.
She will ask so you can answer that...
SPEAKER_03: It’s August 9, 1996.
SPEAKER_03: Tomorrow is the parade of Silleteros.
Don Carlos Zapata is here with us
SPEAKER_03: who’s going to parade with a
monumental style silleta.
SPEAKER_03: Don Carlos, for how long have you been
participating in the parade?
SPEAKER_03: And how many times have you won?
SPEAKER_03: I've only lost twice in ten years.
SPEAKER_03: Because I stopped competing. I've been
the winner for eight years now.
SPEAKER_03: - You stopped competing?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_03: - We wish you good luck for tomorrow.
- Thank you.
SPEAKER_03: Federico.
SPEAKER_03: Federico...
SPEAKER_03: MUTE FIRE