SPEAKER_06: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_06: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_06: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_06: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_06: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_06: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_06: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_06: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_06: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_06: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_06: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_06: from making you go.
SPEAKER_06: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_06: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_06: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_06: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him.
SPEAKER_06: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_06: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_06: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_06: Very!
SPEAKER_06: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_06: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_06: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_06: After oxen...
SPEAKER_06: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.