SPEAKER_01: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_01: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_01: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_01: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_01: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_01: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_01: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_01: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_01: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_01: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_01: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_01: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_01: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_01: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_01: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_01: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_01: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_01: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_01: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_01: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_01: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_01: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_01: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_01: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_01: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_01: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_01: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_01: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_01: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_01: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_01: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_01: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_01: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_01: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_01: Good idea.