SPEAKER_29: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_29: Tired?
SPEAKER_29: Fugui!
SPEAKER_29: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_29: It's ready.
SPEAKER_29: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_29: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_29: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_29: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_29: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_29: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_29: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_29: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_29: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_29: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_29: You cold?
SPEAKER_29: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_29: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_29: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_29: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_29: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_29: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_29: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_29: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_29: Yes.
SPEAKER_29: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_29: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_29: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_29: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_29: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_29: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_29: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_29: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_29: Yes, he's a professor.