SPEAKER_25: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_25: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_25: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_25: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_25: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_25: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_25: Home!
SPEAKER_25: This is too much.
SPEAKER_25: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_25: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_25: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_25: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_25: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_25: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_25: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_25: You just have to!
SPEAKER_25: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_25: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_25: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_25: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_25: Yes, just gobbled them up.