SPEAKER_15: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_15: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_15: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_15: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_15: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_15: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_15: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_15: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_15: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_15: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_15: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_15: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_15: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_15: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_15: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_15: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_15: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_15: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_15: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_15: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_15: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_15: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_15: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_15: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_15: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_15: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_15: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_15: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_15: Let me think.
SPEAKER_15: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_15: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_15: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_15: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_15: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_15: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_15: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_15: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_15: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_15: Have some water.
SPEAKER_15: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_15: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_15: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_15: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_15: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_15: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_15: Little Bun, behave yourself.