SPEAKER_28: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_28: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_28: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_28: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_28: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_28: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_28: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_28: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_28: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_28: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_28: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_28: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_28: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_28: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_28: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_28: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_28: The 1940s
SPEAKER_28: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_28: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_28: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_28: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_28: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_28: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_28: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_28: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_28: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_28: Well?
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_28: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_28: Well?
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_28: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_28: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_28: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_28: What is it?
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_28: Good.
SPEAKER_28: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_28: Okay.