SPEAKER_13: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_13: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_13: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_13: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_13: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_13: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_13: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_13: Enough?
SPEAKER_13: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_13: This is too much.
SPEAKER_13: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_13: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_13: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_13: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_13: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_13: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_13: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_13: You just have to!
SPEAKER_13: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_13: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_13: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_13: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_13: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_13: Yes, just gobbled them up.