SPEAKER_05: The strange thing was that I didn’t
notice her as worried as I was.
SPEAKER_05: If I wake up mute I would
probably go crazy.
SPEAKER_05: I noticed it was an attitude
that she was assuming.
SPEAKER_05: I could never knew if was just
in front of me or everyone
SPEAKER_05: or facing life.
SPEAKER_05: Maybe she was punishing us all.
SPEAKER_05: But then she stopped speaking.
SPEAKER_05: I don’t think she can’t speak,
I think that she has decided not to speak.
SPEAKER_05: And I think it’s a voluntary decision.
SPEAKER_05: I thought, however, that it
could be a medical issue.
SPEAKER_05: I talked to Héctor, to César
and to other people.
SPEAKER_05: They all came to the
same conclusion:
SPEAKER_05: Aracelly's problem
is inexplicable.
SPEAKER_05: It’s not physiological, and it
doesn’t seem psychological either.
SPEAKER_05: Always, always, always, I think
that she always understands us.
SPEAKER_05: She hasn't lost the
capacity of understanding
SPEAKER_05: nor has she lost any
other kind of routines.
SPEAKER_05: She reads, she walks, she thinks,
SPEAKER_05: she insinuates, she takes initiatives.
SPEAKER_05: And I think that, somehow, what she’s pretending
is to make life unbearable to everyone.
SPEAKER_05: I think that families begin
SPEAKER_05: but to live academically,
and that we have lacked.