undefined: I had been in the army for three years,
until I got kicked out...
undefined: They wanted me to sell them.
undefined: MUTE FIRE
undefined: On February 10th 1906, four men
tried to murder the president of Colombia.
undefined: The staging of that event, was the
beginning of cinema in the country.
undefined: - Ok. What's your name?
- Gustavo Rojas.
undefined: No, no. I think it's better alone.
undefined: Let's stop for a minute. One question.
She will ask so you can answer that...
undefined: Since in June 1964 we had already...
undefined: Banana field blueprint
undefined: ♪ I remember when I saw
you for the first time
undefined: ♪ I can't deny it, I was
scared to confess to you
undefined: ♪ You looked at me, and I stared at you.
undefined: ♪ Until one day, we finally
understood each other.
undefined: ♪ Who could imagine that then
our children would come
undefined: ♪ To bring joy to this
place for all eternity.
undefined: We took her to the doctor
undefined: To everyone I thought could know.
undefined: I think that she is taking somehow revenge.
undefined: If that’s the case, she
should have said it,
undefined: and it would have been better
undefined: that we would just
have ended everything.
undefined: and families dissolve, families
should not self-destruct.
undefined: I think we never talked enough about love.
undefined: Because if we had talked
enough about love
undefined: we would have understood
it from the beginning.
undefined: Love is born, it grows and it
dies like everything in nature.
undefined: I believe that the academic attitude is not
only repeating texts in the universities
undefined: - Was my exit okay?
- It was fine.
undefined: Cut.
undefined: Roll camera, roll sound.
undefined: - Do I have to clap again?
- Yes, please.
undefined: …or something like that.
undefined: ♪ With justice and truth
next to the people it is
undefined: ♪ the little song that was
born in our guerrilla voice
undefined: ♪ of struggle and future.
undefined: ♪ With Bolivar, Galán already rode again.
undefined: ♪ No more weeping and pain of the homeland.
undefined: ♪ We are people who go after freedom
undefined: ♪ building the path of peace.
undefined: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
undefined: ♪ for the fatherland,
the people and the bread.
undefined: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
undefined: ♪ to achieve freedom.
undefined: ♪ Guerrilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
undefined: ♪ for the fatherland,
the people and the bread.
undefined: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
undefined: ♪ to achieve freedom.
undefined: I've only lost twice in ten years.
undefined: Because I stopped competing. I've been
the winner for eight years now.
undefined: - You stopped competing?
- Yes.
undefined: - We wish you good luck for tomorrow.
- Thank you.
undefined: Federico.
undefined: Federico...
undefined: MUTE FIRE