SPEAKER_04: Please.
SPEAKER_04: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_04: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_04: Tell me.
SPEAKER_04: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_04: Come home.
SPEAKER_04: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_04: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_04: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_04: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_04: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_04: Me.
SPEAKER_04: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_04: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_04: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_04: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_04: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_04: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_04: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_04: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_04: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_04: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_04: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_04: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_04: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_04: You should have written.
SPEAKER_04: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_04: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_04: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_04: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_04: They never get...
SPEAKER_04: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_04: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_04: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_04: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_04: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_04: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_04: Look at this.
SPEAKER_04: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_04: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_04: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_04: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_04: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_04: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_04: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_04: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_04: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_04: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_04: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_04: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_04: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_04: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_04: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_04: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_04: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_04: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_04: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_04: Of course.
SPEAKER_04: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_04: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_04: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_04: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_04: Good idea!
SPEAKER_04: It's ready.
SPEAKER_04: It's all here?
SPEAKER_04: Keep these.
SPEAKER_04: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_04: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_04: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_04: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_04: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_04: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_04: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_04: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_04: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_04: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_04: I see your point.
SPEAKER_04: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_04: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_04: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_04: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_04: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_04: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_04: How so?
SPEAKER_04: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_04: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_04: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_04: Well?
SPEAKER_04: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_04: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_04: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_04: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_04: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_04: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_04: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_04: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_04: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_04: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_04: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_04: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_04: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_04: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_04: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_04: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_04: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_04: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_04: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_04: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_04: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_04: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_04: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_04: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_04: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_04: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_04: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_04: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_04: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_04: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_04: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_04: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_04: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_04: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_04: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_04: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui...
SPEAKER_04: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_04: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_04: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_04: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_04: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_04: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_04: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_04: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_04: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_04: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_04: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_04: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_04: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_04: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_04: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_04: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_04: No, really.
SPEAKER_04: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_04: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_04: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: A cripple?
SPEAKER_04: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_04: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_04: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_04: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_04: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_04: We approve.
SPEAKER_04: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_04: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_04: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_04: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_04: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_04: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_04: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_04: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_04: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_04: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_04: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_04: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_04: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_04: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_04: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_04: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_04: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_04: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_04: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_04: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_04: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_04: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_04: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_04: Who?
SPEAKER_04: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_04: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_04: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_04: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_04: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_04: What's happened?
SPEAKER_04: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_04: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_04: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_04: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_04: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_04: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_04: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_04: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_04: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_04: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_04: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_04: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_04: I wouldn't dare.
SPEAKER_04: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_04: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_04: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_04: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_04: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_04: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_04: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_04: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_04: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_04: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_04: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_04: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_04: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_04: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_04: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_04: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_04: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_04: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_04: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_04: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_04: to show her.
SPEAKER_04: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_04: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_04: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_04: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_04: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_04: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_04: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_04: Let's see.
SPEAKER_04: You will ride on an ox's back.
SPEAKER_04: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...