SPEAKER_12: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_12: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_12: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_12: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_12: You're up.
SPEAKER_12: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_12: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_12: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_12: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_12: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_12: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_12: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_12: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_12: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_12: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_12: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_12: It's settled.
SPEAKER_12: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_12: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_12: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_12: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_12: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_12: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_12: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_12: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_12: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_12: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_12: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_12: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_12: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_12: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_12: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_12: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_12: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_12: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_12: As for me...
SPEAKER_12: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_12: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_12: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_12: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_12: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_12: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_12: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_12: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_12: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_12: The day...
SPEAKER_12: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_12: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_12: Written?
SPEAKER_12: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_12: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_12: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_12: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_12: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_12: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_12: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_12: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_12: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_12: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_12: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_12: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_12: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_12: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_12: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_12: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_12: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_12: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_12: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_12: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_12: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_12: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_12: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_12: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_12: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_12: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_12: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_12: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_12: Wake up.
SPEAKER_12: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_12: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_12: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_12: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_12: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_12: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_12: that we could...
SPEAKER_12: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_12: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_12: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_12: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_12: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_12: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_12: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_12: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_12: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_12: He can run?
SPEAKER_12: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_12: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_12: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_12: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_12: I approve.
SPEAKER_12: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_12: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_12: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_12: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_12: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_12: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_12: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_12: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_12: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_12: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_12: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_12: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_12: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_12: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_12: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_12: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_12: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_12: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_12: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_12: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_12: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_12: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_12: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_12: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_12: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_12: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_12: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_12: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_12: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_12: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_12: They did.
SPEAKER_12: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_12: No.
SPEAKER_12: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_12: No doctors?
SPEAKER_12: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_12: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_12: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_12: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_12: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_12: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_12: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_12: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_12: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_12: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_12: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_12: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_12: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_12: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_12: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_12: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_12: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_12: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_12: Help us!
SPEAKER_12: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_12: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_12: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_12: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_12: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_12: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_12: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_12: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_12: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_12: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_12: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_12: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_12: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_12: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_12: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_12: How about in here?
SPEAKER_12: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_12: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_12: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_12: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_12: And then...
SPEAKER_12: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_12: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_12: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_12: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_12: and life will get better and better.