SPEAKER_03: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_03: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_03: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_03: Tired?
SPEAKER_03: Fugui!
SPEAKER_03: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_03: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_03: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_03: and after that...
SPEAKER_03: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_03: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_03: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_03: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_03: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_03: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_03: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_03: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_03: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_03: Come inside.
SPEAKER_03: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_03: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_03: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_03: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_03: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_03: You cold?
SPEAKER_03: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_03: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_03: On the mend.
SPEAKER_03: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_03: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_03: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_03: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_03: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_03: Yes.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_03: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_03: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_03: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_03: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_03: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_03: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_03: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_03: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_03: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_03: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_03: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_03: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_03: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_03: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_03: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_03: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_03: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_03: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_03: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_03: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_03: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_03: Uncle.
SPEAKER_03: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.