SPEAKER_05: Get out!
SPEAKER_05: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_05: Sit down.
SPEAKER_05: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_05: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_05: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_05: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_05: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_05: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_05: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_05: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_05: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_05: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_05: Take this.
SPEAKER_05: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_05: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_05: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_05: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_05: How could you?
SPEAKER_05: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_05: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_05: What is this?
SPEAKER_05: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_05: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_05: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_05: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_05: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_05: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_05: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_05: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_05: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_05: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_05: Now!
SPEAKER_05: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_05: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_05: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_05: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_05: Daddy.
SPEAKER_05: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_05: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_05: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_05: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_05: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_05: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_05: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_05: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_05: How dare you!
SPEAKER_05: What's going on?
SPEAKER_05: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_05: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_05: Let her go!
SPEAKER_05: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_05: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_05: No!
SPEAKER_05: The 1960s
SPEAKER_05: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_05: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_05: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_05: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_05: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_05: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_05: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_05: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_05: Sit down.
SPEAKER_05: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_05: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_05: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_05: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_05: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_05: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_05: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_05: He was starving.
SPEAKER_05: But he was okay after the water.