SPEAKER_25: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_25: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_25: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_25: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_25: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_25: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_25: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_25: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_25: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_25: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_25: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_25: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_25: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_25: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_25: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_25: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_25: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_25: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_25: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_25: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_25: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_25: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_25: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_25: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_25: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_25: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_25: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_25: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_25: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_25: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_25: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_25: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_25: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_25: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_25: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_25: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_25: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_25: Good idea.