SPEAKER_17: I'm home.
SPEAKER_17: Home.
SPEAKER_17: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_17: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_17: come see the show.
SPEAKER_17: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_17: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_17: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_17: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_17: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_17: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_17: It's money.
SPEAKER_17: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_17: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_17: Let's go.
SPEAKER_17: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_17: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_17: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_17: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_17: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_17: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_17: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_17: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_17: Never mind.
SPEAKER_17: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_17: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_17: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_17: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_17: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_17: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_17: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_17: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_17: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_17: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_17: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_17: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_17: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_17: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_17: He's all right.
SPEAKER_17: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_17: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_17: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_17: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_17: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_17: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_17: Little Bun, behave yourself.