SPEAKER_06: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_06: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_06: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_06: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_06: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_06: Fugui...
SPEAKER_06: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_06: I've realized...
SPEAKER_06: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_06: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_06: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_06: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_06: Granny!
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_06: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_06: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_06: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_06: What's his name?
SPEAKER_06: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_06: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_06: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_06: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_06: You're here.
SPEAKER_06: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_06: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_06: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_06: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_06: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_06: What do you know?
SPEAKER_06: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_06: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_06: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_06: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_06: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_06: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_06: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_06: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_06: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_06: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_06: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_06: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_06: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_06: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_06: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_06: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_06: from making you go.
SPEAKER_06: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_06: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_06: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_06: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_06: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_06: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_06: Go away!
SPEAKER_06: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him.
SPEAKER_06: A good family.
SPEAKER_06: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_06: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_06: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_06: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_06: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_06: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_06: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_06: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_06: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_06: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_06: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_06: Very!
SPEAKER_06: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_06: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_06: Come inside.
SPEAKER_06: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_06: When is it due?
SPEAKER_06: Go ask.
SPEAKER_06: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_06: Want one?
SPEAKER_06: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_06: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_06: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_06: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_06: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_06: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_06: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_06: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_06: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_06: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_06: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_06: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_06: After oxen...
SPEAKER_06: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.