SPEAKER_10: Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_10: No, no. I think it's better alone.
SPEAKER_10: Or I introduce him.
Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_10: Gustavo Rojas, he is chief
of the Kawiyarí tribe...
SPEAKER_10: Well, there's many different ones.
Like Tucanos, and some others...
SPEAKER_10: Let's stop for a minute. One question.
She will ask so you can answer that...
SPEAKER_10: ♪ how I would adore you.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ You looked at me, and I stared at you.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Until one day, we finally
understood each other.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Who could imagine that then
our children would come
SPEAKER_10: ♪ To bring joy to this
place for all eternity.
SPEAKER_10: The strange thing was that I didn’t
notice her as worried as I was.