SPEAKER_05: For example, he describes one by one the kind
of hat that each condemned was wearing.
SPEAKER_05: It’s worth quoting the whole fragment:
SPEAKER_05: "They were all wearing black:
Salgar wore a straight wing cinnamon hat.
SPEAKER_05: Aguilar wore a Panama hat.
SPEAKER_05: Gonzales, a black Tyrolean hat.
SPEAKER_05: And Ortiz wore a black hard hat."
SPEAKER_05: The reporter also collects
a series of interviews.
SPEAKER_05: the first round of shooting
resounds from the rifles.
SPEAKER_05: Afterwards, a group of doctors approaches
SPEAKER_05: and certify that the condemned
are still breathing,
SPEAKER_05: and give the order for
a second shooting,
SPEAKER_05: Reyes thought that, just like the people
who witnessed the shooting in person did,
SPEAKER_05: everyone who saw those photos
would immediately support his idea.
SPEAKER_05: Here lays the body of Rafael Reyes today.
SPEAKER_05: This was going to be a movie about the
beginnings of Cinema in Colombia,
SPEAKER_05: about its first images.
SPEAKER_05: But as it's being said:
SPEAKER_05: To talk about Colombia
we have to talk about war.
SPEAKER_05: And to talk about war we need to talk about
armies, about deaths, about cemeteries.
SPEAKER_05: That’s me.