SPEAKER_13: There’s a line dividing the brain
into a left and a right hemisphere.
SPEAKER_13: Usually, in most people,
the left hemisphere
SPEAKER_13: dominates language.
SPEAKER_13: Language works in two important parts.
One part is in the temporal lobe.
SPEAKER_13: The one responsible for perception
and comprehension of any language.
SPEAKER_13: And the other one in the frontal lobe
SPEAKER_13: that’s directly responsible
for performing words.
SPEAKER_13: So that words can coordinate a coherent
answer according to the understood question.
SPEAKER_13: A coherent and adequate answer.
SPEAKER_13: In your case, we’re hoping that you
understand the things we’re asking you.
SPEAKER_13: And in case you would
have any difficulties,
SPEAKER_13: we would find some structural injury
in this part that could be either a tumor
SPEAKER_13: or a scar of some cerebral stroke
that you might have had.
SPEAKER_13: No injury, no tumor.
Analyzing the neurological exam
SPEAKER_13: and this last generation
exam, we can conclude
SPEAKER_13: that Aracellys brain is completely normal.
SPEAKER_13: - Ok. What's your name?
- Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_13: Roll camera, roll sound.
SPEAKER_13: - Do I have to clap again?
- Yes, please.
SPEAKER_13: - Ready?
- Yes.