SPEAKER_03: This is the first recorded
game of the Atlético Nacional,
SPEAKER_03: in this filmic document
of the Pelbet company.
SPEAKER_03: We will present indistinctly,
according to journalistic consideration
SPEAKER_03: the main games, the ones
we consider essential
SPEAKER_03: for the conquer of the title of 1981.
SPEAKER_03: The team wins 3-0 in his opening game.
SPEAKER_03: The second game in
Armenia was tied 0-0.
SPEAKER_03: The final game of the championship tied
1-1 against Medellín in the first round
SPEAKER_03: and in the second round
they lost against Quindío 0-2.
SPEAKER_03: The first goal was scored by
Victor Luna and Guillermo La Rosa
SPEAKER_03: from the midfield, inside the area
SPEAKER_03: so that he can be, as
usually, close to the goal.
SPEAKER_03: Apparently, the foul can't
be seen clear enough.
SPEAKER_03: But let’s have a look
from the reverse angle.
SPEAKER_03: The one from the cameras at the other side
of the goal, placed by Pelbet’s company.
SPEAKER_03: 41 minutes of the
additional stage.
SPEAKER_03: Four minutes left for
Nacional to be the champion.
SPEAKER_03: Look at that karate blow from Gonzalez
Aquino to the peruvian Cesar Cueto.
SPEAKER_03: About ten years now, that I participate
in the parade of Silleteros.