SPEAKER_30: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_30: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_30: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_30: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_30: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_30: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_30: from making you go.
SPEAKER_30: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_30: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_30: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_30: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_30: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_30: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_30: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_30: Go away!
SPEAKER_30: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_30: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_30: You killed him.
SPEAKER_30: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_30: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_30: Very!