SPEAKER_28: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_28: It's ready.
SPEAKER_28: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_28: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_28: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_28: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_28: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_28: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_28: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_28: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_28: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_28: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_28: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_28: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_28: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_28: You cold?
SPEAKER_28: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_28: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_28: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_28: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_28: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_28: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_28: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_28: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_28: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_28: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_28: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_28: Yes.
SPEAKER_28: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_28: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_28: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_28: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_28: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_28: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_28: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_28: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_28: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_28: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.