SPEAKER_27: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_27: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_27: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_27: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_27: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_27: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_27: You're up.
SPEAKER_27: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_27: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_27: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_27: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_27: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_27: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_27: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_27: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_27: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_27: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_27: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_27: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_27: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_27: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_27: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_27: Landlords?
SPEAKER_27: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_27: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_27: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_27: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_27: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_27: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_27: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_27: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_27: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_27: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_27: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_27: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_27: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_27: How so?
SPEAKER_27: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_27: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_27: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_27: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_27: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_27: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_27: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_27: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_27: Daddy.
SPEAKER_27: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_27: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_27: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_27: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_27: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_27: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_27: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_27: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_27: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_27: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_27: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_27: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_27: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_27: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_27: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_27: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_27: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_27: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_27: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_27: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_27: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_27: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_27: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_27: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_27: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_27: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_27: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_27: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_27: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_27: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_27: Is it?
SPEAKER_27: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_27: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_27: Have you had your medicine?