SPEAKER_13: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_13: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_13: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_13: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_13: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_13: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_13: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_13: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_13: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_13: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_13: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_13: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_13: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_13: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_13: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_13: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_13: The 1940s
SPEAKER_13: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_13: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_13: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_13: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_13: Tired?
SPEAKER_13: Fugui!
SPEAKER_13: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_13: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_13: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_13: Enough?
SPEAKER_13: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_13: Sit here.
SPEAKER_13: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_13: Come over here.
SPEAKER_13: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_13: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_13: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_13: Some years later...