SPEAKER_08: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_08: How much?
SPEAKER_08: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_08: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_08: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_08: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_08: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: Fugui...
SPEAKER_08: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_08: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_08: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_08: It's settled.
SPEAKER_08: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_08: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_08: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_08: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_08: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_08: Okay?
SPEAKER_08: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_08: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_08: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_08: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_08: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_08: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_08: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_08: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_08: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_08: As for me...
SPEAKER_08: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_08: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_08: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_08: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_08: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_08: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_08: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_08: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_08: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_08: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_08: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_08: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_08: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_08: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_08: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_08: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_08: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_08: They shot him.
SPEAKER_08: He is dead.
SPEAKER_08: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_08: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_08: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_08: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_08: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_08: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_08: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_08: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_08: come see the show.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_08: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_08: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_08: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_08: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_08: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_08: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_08: When you get there...
SPEAKER_08: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_08: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_08: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_08: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_08: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_08: That's good.
SPEAKER_08: Our family...
SPEAKER_08: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_08: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_08: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_08: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_08: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_08: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_08: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_08: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_08: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_08: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_08: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_08: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_08: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_08: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_08: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_08: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_08: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_08: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_08: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_08: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_08: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_08: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_08: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_08: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_08: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_08: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_08: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_08: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_08: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_08: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_08: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_08: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_08: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_08: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_08: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_08: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_08: On the mend.
SPEAKER_08: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_08: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_08: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_08: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_08: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_08: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_08: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_08: Of course.
SPEAKER_08: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_08: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_08: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_08: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_08: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_08: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_08: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_08: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_08: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_08: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_08: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_08: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_08: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_08: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_08: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_08: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_08: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_08: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_08: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_08: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_08: He's all right.
SPEAKER_08: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_08: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_08: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_08: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_08: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_08: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_08: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_08: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_08: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_08: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_08: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_08: How about in here?
SPEAKER_08: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_08: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_08: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_08: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_08: And then...
SPEAKER_08: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_08: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_08: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_08: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...