SPEAKER_24: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_24: What's his name?
SPEAKER_24: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_24: Fugui...
SPEAKER_24: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_24: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_24: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_24: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_24: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_24: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_24: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_24: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_24: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_24: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_24: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_24: No, really.
SPEAKER_24: From where?
SPEAKER_24: Come on in!
SPEAKER_24: This is great.
SPEAKER_24: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_24: You came for this?
SPEAKER_24: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_24: Why?
SPEAKER_24: I don't know.
SPEAKER_24: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_24: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_24: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_24: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_24: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_24: The only child I have left.