SPEAKER_04: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_04: Tired?
SPEAKER_04: Fugui!
SPEAKER_04: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_04: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_04: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_04: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_04: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_04: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_04: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_04: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_04: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_04: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_04: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_04: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_04: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_04: You cold?
SPEAKER_04: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_04: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_04: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_04: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_04: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_04: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_04: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_04: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_04: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_04: Yes.
SPEAKER_04: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_04: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_04: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_04: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_04: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_04: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_04: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_04: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_04: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_04: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.