SPEAKER_27: Of course.
SPEAKER_27: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_27: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_27: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_27: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_27: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_27: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_27: Enough?
SPEAKER_27: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_27: This is too much.
SPEAKER_27: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_27: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_27: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_27: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_27: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_27: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_27: You just have to!
SPEAKER_27: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_27: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_27: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_27: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_27: Are they in there?