SPEAKER_03: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_03: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_03: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_03: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_03: from making you go.
SPEAKER_03: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_03: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_03: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_03: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_03: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_03: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_03: Go away!
SPEAKER_03: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_03: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_03: You killed him.
SPEAKER_03: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_03: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_03: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_03: Very!
SPEAKER_03: After oxen...
SPEAKER_03: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.