SPEAKER_16: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_16: Sir!
SPEAKER_16: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_16: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_16: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_16: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_16: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_16: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_16: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_16: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_16: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_16: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_16: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_16: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_16: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_16: You won't go?
SPEAKER_16: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_16: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_16: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_16: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_16: Get Dr. Wang over here.