SPEAKER_07: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_07: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_07: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_07: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_07: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_07: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_07: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_07: How could that be?
SPEAKER_07: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_07: Run now...
SPEAKER_07: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_07: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_07: That's right.
SPEAKER_07: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_07: How?
SPEAKER_07: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_07: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_07: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_07: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_07: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_07: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_07: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_07: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_07: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_07: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_07: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_07: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_07: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_07: What's up?
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_07: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.