SPEAKER_10: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_10: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_10: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_10: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_10: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_10: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_10: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_10: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_10: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_10: Well?
SPEAKER_10: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_10: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_10: Well?
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_10: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_10: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_10: What is it?
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_10: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_10: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_10: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_10: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_10: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_10: Good.
SPEAKER_10: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_10: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_10: Okay.
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_10: What do you want?
SPEAKER_10: Come out for a second.