SPEAKER_20: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_20: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_20: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_20: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_20: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_20: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_20: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_20: So, no running?
SPEAKER_20: This is too much.
SPEAKER_20: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_20: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_20: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_20: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_20: We must be going.
SPEAKER_20: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_20: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_20: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_20: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_20: Come on in!
SPEAKER_20: Really?
SPEAKER_20: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_20: Cheers!
SPEAKER_20: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_20: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_20: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_20: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_20: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_20: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_20: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_20: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_20: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_20: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_20: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_20: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_20: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_20: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_20: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_20: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_20: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_20: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_20: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_20: It's okay.
SPEAKER_20: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_20: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_20: anything made from wheat.