SPEAKER_02: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_02: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_02: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_02: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_02: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_02: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_02: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_02: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_02: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_02: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_02: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_02: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_02: Sit here.
SPEAKER_02: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_02: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_02: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_02: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_02: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_02: You just have to!
SPEAKER_02: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_02: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_02: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_02: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_02: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_02: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_02: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_02: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_02: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_02: Take the medicine to Granny.