SPEAKER_13: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_13: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_13: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_13: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_13: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_13: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_13: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_13: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_13: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_13: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_13: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_13: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_13: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_13: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_13: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_13: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_13: The 1940s
SPEAKER_13: Go!
SPEAKER_13: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_13: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_13: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_13: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_13: Take that!
SPEAKER_13: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_13: Enough?
SPEAKER_13: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_13: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_13: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_13: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_13: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_13: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_13: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_13: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_13: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_13: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_13: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_13: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_13: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_13: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_13: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_13: Come over here.
SPEAKER_13: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_13: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_13: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_13: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_13: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_13: Oxygen.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_13: Some years later...