SPEAKER_09: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_09: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_09: Both sides must sign.
SPEAKER_09: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_09: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_09: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_09: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_09: Besides...
SPEAKER_09: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_09: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_09: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_09: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_09: As for me...
SPEAKER_09: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_09: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_09: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_09: The wounded.
SPEAKER_09: No one's left.
SPEAKER_09: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_09: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_09: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_09: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_09: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_09: Home!
SPEAKER_09: Home?
SPEAKER_09: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_09: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_09: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_09: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_09: Fugui...
SPEAKER_09: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_09: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_09: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_09: I will remember.
SPEAKER_09: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_09: Fugui!
SPEAKER_09: Who's there?
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_09: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_09: Well?
SPEAKER_09: Fugui...
SPEAKER_09: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_09: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_09: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_09: Take this...
SPEAKER_09: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_09: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_09: No.
SPEAKER_09: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_09: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_09: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_09: and better get back.
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng, remember...
SPEAKER_09: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_09: Let me wear it!