SPEAKER_01: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_01: I want him dead!
SPEAKER_01: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_01: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_01: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_01: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_01: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_01: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_01: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_01: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_01: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_01: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_01: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_01: Don't move.
SPEAKER_01: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_01: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_01: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_01: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_01: He'll know.
SPEAKER_01: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_01: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_01: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_01: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_01: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_01: Back already?
SPEAKER_01: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_01: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_01: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_01: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_01: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_01: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_01: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_01: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_01: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_01: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_01: Very soon.
SPEAKER_01: And then?
SPEAKER_01: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_01: I want to ride on an ox's back!