SPEAKER_00: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_00: How much?
SPEAKER_00: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_00: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_00: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_00: Fugui...
SPEAKER_00: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_00: What?
SPEAKER_00: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_00: Fugui...
SPEAKER_00: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_00: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_00: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_00: They shot him.
SPEAKER_00: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_00: He is dead.
SPEAKER_00: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_00: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_00: Landlords?
SPEAKER_00: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_00: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_00: When you get there...
SPEAKER_00: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_00: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_00: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_00: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_00: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_00: That's good.
SPEAKER_00: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_00: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_00: Our family...
SPEAKER_00: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_00: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_00: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_00: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_00: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_00: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_00: From where?
SPEAKER_00: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_00: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_00: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_00: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_00: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_00: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_00: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_00: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_00: Of course.
SPEAKER_00: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_00: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_00: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_00: You came for this?
SPEAKER_00: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_00: Why?
SPEAKER_00: I don't know.
SPEAKER_00: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_00: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_00: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_00: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_00: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_00: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_00: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_00: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_00: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_00: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_00: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_00: Have some water.
SPEAKER_00: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_00: Is it?
SPEAKER_00: I'll fix it.