SPEAKER_22: Take care.
SPEAKER_22: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_22: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_22: Dad!
SPEAKER_22: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_22: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_22: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_22: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_22: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_22: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_22: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_22: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_22: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_22: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_22: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_22: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_22: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_22: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_22: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_22: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_22: Please come again.
SPEAKER_22: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_22: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_22: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_22: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_22: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_22: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_22: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_22: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_22: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_22: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_22: Let me think.
SPEAKER_22: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_22: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_22: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_22: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_22: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_22: What's with him?
SPEAKER_22: He ate too quickly.