SPEAKER_23: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_23: I've just...
SPEAKER_23: Let's play!
SPEAKER_23: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_23: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_23: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_23: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_23: Just like me.
SPEAKER_23: wounded me
SPEAKER_23: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_23: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_23: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_23: Enough!
SPEAKER_23: How could you?
SPEAKER_23: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_23: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_23: What's happened?
SPEAKER_23: Answer me!
SPEAKER_23: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_23: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_23: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_23: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_23: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_23: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_23: Time to wrap up.