SPEAKER_00: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_00: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_00: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_00: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_00: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_00: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_00: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_00: They shot him.
SPEAKER_00: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_00: He is dead.
SPEAKER_00: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_00: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_00: Landlords?
SPEAKER_00: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_00: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_00: When you get there...
SPEAKER_00: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_00: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_00: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_00: That's good.
SPEAKER_00: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_00: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_00: Our family...
SPEAKER_00: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_00: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_00: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_00: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_00: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_00: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_00: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_00: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_00: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_00: From where?
SPEAKER_00: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_00: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_00: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_00: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_00: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_00: On the mend.
SPEAKER_00: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_00: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_00: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_00: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_00: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_00: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_00: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_00: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_00: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_00: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_00: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_00: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_00: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_00: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_00: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_00: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_00: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_00: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_00: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_00: Have some water.
SPEAKER_00: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_00: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_00: I'll make lunch.