SPEAKER_04: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_04: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_04: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_04: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_04: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_04: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_04: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_04: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_04: Good.
SPEAKER_04: A gambling debt's a debt,
and debts must be paid.
SPEAKER_04: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_04: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_04: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_04: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_04: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_04: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_04: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_04: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_04: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_04: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_04: Really?
SPEAKER_04: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_04: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_04: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_04: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_04: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_04: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_04: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_04: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_04: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_04: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_04: What's with him?
SPEAKER_04: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_04: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_04: anything made from wheat.