SPEAKER_09: Both sides must sign.
SPEAKER_09: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_09: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_09: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_09: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_09: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_09: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_09: Home!
SPEAKER_09: Home?
SPEAKER_09: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_09: Run now...
SPEAKER_09: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_09: That's right.
SPEAKER_09: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_09: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_09: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_09: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_09: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_09: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_09: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_09: Look at this.
SPEAKER_09: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_09: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_09: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_09: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_09: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_09: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_09: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_09: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_09: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_09: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_09: It's all here?
SPEAKER_09: Keep these.
SPEAKER_09: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_09: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_09: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_09: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_09: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_09: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_09: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_09: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_09: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_09: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_09: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_09: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_09: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_09: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_09: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_09: I see your point.
SPEAKER_09: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_09: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_09: Daddy.
SPEAKER_09: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_09: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_09: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_09: Sit here.
SPEAKER_09: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_09: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_09: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_09: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_09: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_09: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_09: Fugui...
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_09: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_09: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_09: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_09: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_09: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_09: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_09: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_09: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_09: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_09: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_09: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_09: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_09: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_09: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_09: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_09: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_09: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_09: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_09: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_09: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!