SPEAKER_15: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_15: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_15: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_15: want more time
SPEAKER_15: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_15: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_15: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_15: Turtle spawn! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_15: I'll cut him into pieces! I'll clobber him!
SPEAKER_15: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_15: I want him dead!
SPEAKER_15: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_15: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_15: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_15: Tired?
SPEAKER_15: Fugui!
SPEAKER_15: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_15: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_15: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_15: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_15: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_15: Take that!
SPEAKER_15: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_15: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_15: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_15: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_15: What's up?
SPEAKER_15: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_15: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_15: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_15: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_15: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_15: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_15: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_15: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_15: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_15: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_15: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_15: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_15: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_15: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_15: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_15: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_15: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_15: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_15: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_15: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_15: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_15: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_15: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_15: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_15: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_15: He'll know.
SPEAKER_15: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_15: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_15: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.