SPEAKER_08: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: Well?
SPEAKER_08: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_08: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_08: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_08: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_08: I thought I'd live my final days here.
SPEAKER_08: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_08: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_08: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_08: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_08: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_08: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_08: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_08: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_08: I'm home.
SPEAKER_08: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_08: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_08: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_08: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_08: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_08: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_08: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_08: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_08: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_08: I approve.
SPEAKER_08: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_08: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_08: Well?
SPEAKER_08: Why?
SPEAKER_08: I don't know.
SPEAKER_08: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_08: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_08: He's all right.
SPEAKER_08: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_08: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_08: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_08: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_08: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_08: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_08: It's okay.
SPEAKER_08: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_08: How about in here?
SPEAKER_08: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_08: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_08: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_08: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_08: And then...
SPEAKER_08: and the sheep will turn into oxen.