SPEAKER_07: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_07: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_07: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_07: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_07: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_07: Get out!
SPEAKER_07: I've just...
SPEAKER_07: Let's play!
SPEAKER_07: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_07: Sit down.
SPEAKER_07: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_07: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_07: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_07: Sir!
SPEAKER_07: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_07: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_07: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_07: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_07: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_07: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_07: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_07: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_07: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_07: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_07: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_07: Just like me.
SPEAKER_07: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_07: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_07: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_07: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_07: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_07: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_07: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_07: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_07: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_07: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_07: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_07: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_07: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_07: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_07: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_07: Now!
SPEAKER_07: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_07: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_07: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_07: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_07: You won't go?
SPEAKER_07: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_07: Enough!
SPEAKER_07: How could you?
SPEAKER_07: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_07: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_07: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_07: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_07: How so?
SPEAKER_07: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_07: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_07: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_07: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_07: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_07: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_07: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_07: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_07: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_07: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_07: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_07: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_07: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_07: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_07: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_07: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_07: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_07: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_07: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_07: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_07: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_07: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_07: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_07: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_07: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_07: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_07: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_07: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_07: What's happened?
SPEAKER_07: Answer me!
SPEAKER_07: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_07: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_07: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_07: How dare you!
SPEAKER_07: What's going on?
SPEAKER_07: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_07: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_07: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_07: No!
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_07: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_07: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_07: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_07: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_07: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_07: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_07: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_07: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_07: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_07: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_07: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_07: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_07: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_07: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_07: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_07: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_07: Sit down.
SPEAKER_07: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_07: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_07: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_07: He was starving.
SPEAKER_07: But he was okay after the water.