SPEAKER_04: Or I introduce him.
Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_04: Gustavo Rojas, he is chief
of the Kawiyarí tribe...
SPEAKER_04: Are you having fun?
SPEAKER_04: - Are you all right?
- Yes!
SPEAKER_04: Come then, so you can
get some water on you.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ and my eyes teared up when I looked at you.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ I can't deny it, I was
scared to confess to you
SPEAKER_04: ♪ how I would adore you.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ You looked at me, and I stared at you.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ Until one day, we finally
understood each other.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ Who could imagine that then
our children would come
SPEAKER_04: ♪ To bring joy to this
place for all eternity.
SPEAKER_04: Tomorrow is the parade of Silleteros.
Don Carlos Zapata is here with us
SPEAKER_04: who’s going to parade with a
monumental style silleta.
SPEAKER_04: Don Carlos, for how long have you been
participating in the parade?