SPEAKER_09: We thank the Lord because...
SPEAKER_09: He has given us...
SPEAKER_09: an exact and clear message...
SPEAKER_09: and we have understood that message.
SPEAKER_09: It's not that we have a screw loose.
SPEAKER_09: It’s not that we’re crazy,
or that we’re less than you.
SPEAKER_09: It's not that.
SPEAKER_09: It’s just that we accepted
to walk with Jesus Christ.
SPEAKER_09: That’s the difference between you and us.
SPEAKER_09: That’s why, even with fear
SPEAKER_09: we’re here in front of the presence of God
SPEAKER_09: and maybe you, my friend, will say:
SPEAKER_09: The evangelics again...
SPEAKER_09: Making noise again...
SPEAKER_09: Those people who come here just to sing...
SPEAKER_09: who just…
SPEAKER_09: Because I stopped competing. I've been
the winner for eight years now.
SPEAKER_09: - You stopped competing?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_09: - We wish you good luck for tomorrow.
- Thank you.
SPEAKER_09: Federico.
SPEAKER_09: Federico...