SPEAKER_07: I had been in the army for three years,
until I got kicked out...
SPEAKER_07: because there were some corpses
that had to be buried.
SPEAKER_07: My lieutenant gave me
the order to bury them.
SPEAKER_07: But I didn’t. Instead I sold them
to some people who approached me.
SPEAKER_07: They wanted me to sell them.
SPEAKER_07: That they would use them for a play...
SPEAKER_07: or something like that.
SPEAKER_07: They told me not to worry,
that nobody would find out.
SPEAKER_07: So I believed them and
I sold them the corpses.
SPEAKER_07: I found out later what they
were really going to do with them.
SPEAKER_07: They would disguise them
SPEAKER_07: and leave them in the mountains as
if they would have died in combat.
SPEAKER_07: I kept silence until they were
declared as "false positives".
SPEAKER_07: MUTE FIRE
SPEAKER_07: On February 10th 1906, four men
tried to murder the president of Colombia.
SPEAKER_07: The staging of that event, was the
beginning of cinema in the country.
SPEAKER_07: They told me not to worry,
that nobody would find out.
SPEAKER_07: So I believed them and
sold them the corpses.
SPEAKER_07: I found out later what they
were going to do with them.
SPEAKER_07: That they would disguise them...
SPEAKER_07: …and leave them on the mountains
as if they would have died in combat.
SPEAKER_07: I kept silence until they were
declared as "false positives".