SPEAKER_04: The newspaper "Correo Nacional",
SPEAKER_04: published in Bogotá on March 6th, 1906,
SPEAKER_04: the exact and vivid account
of the execution of four men
SPEAKER_04: for the attempt of murder of
the General Rafael Reyes,
SPEAKER_04: by that time president
of Colombia.
SPEAKER_04: Marco Arturo Salgar, Carlos Roberto Gonzalez,
Juan Ortiz and Fernando Aguilar.
SPEAKER_04: were the four men sentenced
to death, and in consequence
SPEAKER_04: shot in the same place where
they committed the crime.
SPEAKER_04: The account, whose author's
name remains unknown,
SPEAKER_04: is extremely detailed.
SPEAKER_04: For example, he describes one by one the kind
of hat that each condemned was wearing.
SPEAKER_04: It’s worth quoting the whole fragment:
SPEAKER_04: "They were all wearing black:
Salgar wore a straight wing cinnamon hat.
SPEAKER_04: Aguilar wore a Panama hat.
SPEAKER_04: Gonzales, a black Tyrolean hat.
SPEAKER_04: And Ortiz wore a black hard hat."
SPEAKER_04: The reporter also collects
a series of interviews.
SPEAKER_04: The most striking is perhaps, the one from
the Captain of Executions, who just says,
SPEAKER_04: in a serious tone I'd guess:
"Nothing is sacred".
SPEAKER_04: The reporter states: "The shooting
proceeds as normal.
SPEAKER_04: Given the signal with his sword
by the Captain of Executions,
SPEAKER_04: the first round of shooting
resounds from the rifles.
SPEAKER_04: Afterwards, a group of doctors approaches
SPEAKER_04: and certify that the condemned
are still breathing,
SPEAKER_04: and give the order for
a second shooting,
SPEAKER_04: which ends with the immediate
entrance of the four coffins
SPEAKER_04: to transport the corpses
to the cemetery."
SPEAKER_04: This time, the event is more relevant than
usually, since president Rafael Reyes
SPEAKER_04: guided by this moment of political
instability, makes an exception
SPEAKER_04: and the shooting doesn't take place in
the courtyard of the School of Infantry,
SPEAKER_04: where it would normally happened.
SPEAKER_04: Instead, it's held in a public area,
in front of over 10,000 people.
SPEAKER_04: Rafael Reyes saw here the
remains of the last civil war
SPEAKER_04: that had ended only four years ago,
and still had the country in agony.
SPEAKER_04: Shooting people of his same
political party in public areas,
SPEAKER_04: was for him a sign of authority,
SPEAKER_04: but also an invitation to end
the traditional divide
SPEAKER_04: between the liberal
and the conservative party.
SPEAKER_04: With the purpose of making this shooting
visible to as many people as possible
SPEAKER_04: Reyes publishes the book "February 10th",
telling the events through photos.
SPEAKER_04: Reyes thought that, just like the people
who witnessed the shooting in person did,
SPEAKER_04: everyone who saw those photos
would immediately support his idea.
SPEAKER_04: Nevertheless, the most interesting
part of this series of photos
SPEAKER_04: happens after the moment
of the cemetery picture.
SPEAKER_04: It’s unknown whose idea it was, but due to the
impact caused by the pictures of the execution
SPEAKER_04: president Rafael Reyes, Chief of police
Pedro Pedraza, and photographer Lino Lara
SPEAKER_04: decided together to recreate
the moments before the shooting.
SPEAKER_04: They decided to recreate
the attack on the president
SPEAKER_04: and the capture of the condemned,
to create a story.
SPEAKER_04: The outcome was what the historians
called a "false document".
SPEAKER_04: From the 22 pictures that make up
the story, 18 are theatrical reenactments.
SPEAKER_04: This is the first time of a tale made
through photographs in Colombia.
SPEAKER_04: This little narrative gesture,
is acknowledged by tradition
SPEAKER_04: as the beginning of
filmmaking in the country.
SPEAKER_04: Here lays the body of Rafael Reyes today.
SPEAKER_04: This was going to be a movie about the
beginnings of Cinema in Colombia,
SPEAKER_04: about its first images.
SPEAKER_04: But as it's being said:
SPEAKER_04: To talk about Colombia
we have to talk about war.
SPEAKER_04: And to talk about war we need to talk about
armies, about deaths, about cemeteries.
SPEAKER_04: At the same time, my house and my
parents house looked like a cemetery.
SPEAKER_04: It felt like haunted by an inert current,
like flooded by murky water
SPEAKER_04: or better, by dead water.
SPEAKER_04: A few months ago my mother
had an episode of mutism,
SPEAKER_04: and without any explanation,
she just stopped talking.
SPEAKER_04: I remember with some nostalgia
SPEAKER_04: how she repeated the words of that
Mexican musician while cooking:
SPEAKER_04: that said something like:
"I wish you to be happy, very happy...
SPEAKER_04: I wish you to find love,
because you deserve it"
SPEAKER_04: I read somewhere that the first thing you
forget about a person is the voice.
SPEAKER_04: Affected by this
familiar incident,
SPEAKER_04: and because of what connects
all things together
SPEAKER_04: maybe the first moments
of national cinema
SPEAKER_04: and the muteness of my mother can
be part of the same scenario.
SPEAKER_04: Like when you look at a surface
where shadows are being projected
SPEAKER_04: and you can't tell each
object from the other apart.
SPEAKER_04: One night my father woke up and saw
the light of the bathroom on.
SPEAKER_04: When he came closer, he saw my mother in
front of the mirror, shaking.
SPEAKER_04: My father hugged her and
asked her what was going on,
SPEAKER_04: he asked her if she
had a bad dream
SPEAKER_04: but she couldn’t answer.
SPEAKER_04: Since that moment,
she has never spoken again.
SPEAKER_04: My mother spent most of the time locked in a
room looking at people through the window.
SPEAKER_04: Her presence had become more and
more unbearable for my father
SPEAKER_04: who couldn’t avoid feeling sometimes
guilty, and sometimes cheated.
SPEAKER_04: The ambiguity of the doctors answers
left a bad feeling behind
SPEAKER_04: which made him think
that she was just pretending.
SPEAKER_04: One day, a worker of the family suggested
to try with another type of specialist
SPEAKER_04: from his point of view, my mother's
muteness was due to a powerful spell.
SPEAKER_04: My father agreed, even if it
would make him feel humiliated
SPEAKER_04: because for him, superstitions
were for fools.
SPEAKER_04: After two weeks some kind of chaman
or warlock came to my mother.
SPEAKER_04: After wandering around the house, where some
kind of weird mantle could certainly be felt
SPEAKER_04: like a thick, rancid
smell, he told my father:
SPEAKER_04: "Your problems have a
solution, don’t worry.
SPEAKER_04: You just have to
sell this house,
SPEAKER_04: and leave somewhere visible a valuable
object and a picture of her."
SPEAKER_04: My father did so.
SPEAKER_04: The house was put on sale, and on a
shelf he left a picture of her
SPEAKER_04: and a black stone that she
held like a luck charm.
SPEAKER_04: Please, put your legs up.
SPEAKER_04: There’s an announcement on
the internet that says:
SPEAKER_04: "Recover all important moments of
your life that are kept in old tapes.
SPEAKER_04: Live those unique moments with
your family and friends again.
SPEAKER_04: All formats, Betacam SP,
VHS, DV, mini DV, 8mm…"
SPEAKER_04: I contacted the advertiser.
SPEAKER_04: That same afternoon, in a country
house on the outskirts of the city,
SPEAKER_04: I got to meet Carlos Pelbet,
SPEAKER_04: founder of an old audiovisual company
that he and his brother had
SPEAKER_04: since the beginning of the 80s.
SPEAKER_04: Carlos told me rapidly about
his interest in films
SPEAKER_04: or rather, he told me that at some
point of his life it was of his interest.
SPEAKER_04: Also that Pelbet, his company,
SPEAKER_04: inaugurated the recording and broadcasting
business of soccer matches in Colombia
SPEAKER_04: and that it was right then, when competing with
the big TV channels, that the company broke.
SPEAKER_04: He told me that a few years ago he started
collecting anonymous family home movies
SPEAKER_04: from the cassettes that he digitizes.
Hours and hours of family events
SPEAKER_04: weddings, first communions, birthdays,
baptisms, Christmas and holidays.
SPEAKER_04: In a sense, my film is
a relative of all these images,
SPEAKER_04: of the personal images of everyday rites.
SPEAKER_04: Carlos tells me that each week, a
different youngster arrives at his door
SPEAKER_04: wanting to digitize
images of his family
SPEAKER_04: with an idea similar to mine:
SPEAKER_04: To make a film about their mothers,
fathers or grandparents.
SPEAKER_04: Apparently more people are doing the
same film as me at this moment.
SPEAKER_04: We are all thinking about the same images.
SPEAKER_04: These are some images taken by my mother.
SPEAKER_04: A movie about a play in
a rural school she worked at.
SPEAKER_04: Back then, she sympathized with the
insurgent groups of the country.
SPEAKER_04: That’s me.
SPEAKER_04: In one of the movie cans,
it was written on a white tape:
SPEAKER_04: "Marquetalia, 1964".
SPEAKER_04: Those are the place and the date
where the famous FARC was founded.
SPEAKER_04: Apparently, the play is about a popular
narration about the first combats
SPEAKER_04: between the FARC guerilla
and the National Army.
SPEAKER_04: The story is the following:
SPEAKER_04: Having the intention of avoiding the
expansion of the communist guerrilla,
SPEAKER_04: on May 18th, 1964 president
Guillermo León Valencia
SPEAKER_04: sends over a thousand soldiers
to the Tolima plateau
SPEAKER_04: in search for a suspected FARC camp with
48 members of the insurgent movement in it.
SPEAKER_04: After nine days of intense
wandering, the group of soldiers,
SPEAKER_04: lead by Lieutenant Colonel
José Joaquín Matallana,
SPEAKER_04: starts suspecting that they’re wrong,
that there’s no such camp.
SPEAKER_04: They quickly realize that the insurgents
are not full time soldiers,
SPEAKER_04: and that most of them actually
SPEAKER_04: have a disguised life as farmers
among the civilians.
SPEAKER_04: A question immediately arose:
SPEAKER_04: How to tell the population, most of them
farmers, from the guerrillas apart?
SPEAKER_04: Facing this, Colonel
José Joaquín Matallana,
SPEAKER_04: who considered himself as an
analytic and methodic person
SPEAKER_04: and an innovating strategist,
thought to have the answer.
SPEAKER_04: He explains to his soldiers: "This problem
is essentially about appearances".
SPEAKER_04: Matallana ordered his soldiers to go
after every man and woman of the area
SPEAKER_04: and force them to wear the
guerrilla uniform in front of them.
SPEAKER_04: Matallana assured his soldiers,
SPEAKER_04: that the uniform had the
strength and essential capacity
SPEAKER_04: to reveal someone's identity.
SPEAKER_04: According to his logic,
wearing the uniform
SPEAKER_04: would immediately reveal if the person
was a real guerilla soldier or not.
SPEAKER_04: After two weeks they had captured 52 people,
including five children and eight elderly.
SPEAKER_04: This idea would be known later
as the Matallana logic.
SPEAKER_04: And what could have been a
brilliant military operation,
SPEAKER_04: ended up being one of the biggest
political failures in history
SPEAKER_04: because, in less than two years, those 48
soldiers would later turn into five thousand.
SPEAKER_04: From then on, the idea of the disguised
guerrilla would become an obsession
SPEAKER_04: in the development of
public opinion in the country.
SPEAKER_04: Throughout the years, the question
would be incessantly repeated:
SPEAKER_04: Who’s really from the guerilla,
and who’s not?
SPEAKER_04: More than 20 years ago
my mother filmed me.
SPEAKER_04: Today, I’m filming her.
SPEAKER_04: Seeing myself in that play,
playing role of a farmer
SPEAKER_04: captured by the army and forced
to dress like a guerilla man
SPEAKER_04: I couldn’t avoid thinking of the
recent events of the war in Colombia.
SPEAKER_04: Thousands of innocent young people were
captured by the National Army of Colombia
SPEAKER_04: and taken to different parts
of the country to be murdered later.
SPEAKER_04: Then, their bodies were
dressed up like guerilla-soldier
SPEAKER_04: and presented in front of the
media like military successes.
SPEAKER_04: It was a systematic
falsification of war events.
SPEAKER_04: Stagings, using real victims
to create a story.
SPEAKER_04: By the year 2008, this practice
was so common in the National Army
SPEAKER_04: that the victims of this type of
crime counted to the present day
SPEAKER_04: are more than the missing people
during the dictatorship in Chile.
SPEAKER_04: During the 1960s,
SPEAKER_04: in search of images of
true revolutionaries,
SPEAKER_04: two French filmmakers
travelled to Riochiquito,
SPEAKER_04: located in the north of
the province of Cauca.
SPEAKER_04: They recorded there the activities
of the recently founded FARC.
SPEAKER_04: According to a French article called
"Cinema declares war on us"
SPEAKER_04: the screening of this movie
SPEAKER_04: generated an unexpected anguish
among young people in Paris.
SPEAKER_04: Apparently, proving the
existence of revolutionary life
SPEAKER_04: radically buried any other
alternative of life.
SPEAKER_04: For the young Parisians of that time
SPEAKER_04: nothing could be compared to the idea
of leading a life in the armed struggle
SPEAKER_04: for political transformation.
SPEAKER_04: Hence,
the movie made them feel
SPEAKER_04: that their lives and
experiences were insignificant
SPEAKER_04: compared to those of Colombian guerilla.
SPEAKER_04: Louise Canet, a western
movies director,
SPEAKER_04: then recently joined to
the French Socialist Party
SPEAKER_04: declared after watching the movie:
SPEAKER_04: "It’s common to hear people saying that
South American people are violent by nature
SPEAKER_04: that they have a violent heritage from
the Spanish and the Indigenous people.
SPEAKER_04: I don’t know what to think.
But I’m sure of something:
SPEAKER_04: It’s a fertile land for rebels".
SPEAKER_04: This is the place where the attempt against
president Rafael Reyes happened
SPEAKER_04: and where the four men who
did it were shot later on.
SPEAKER_04: In the same place, just a few
weeks later, photographer Lino Lara
SPEAKER_04: and Commandant Pedro Pedraza
recreated the attempt of murder.
SPEAKER_04: According to the records
of the Correo Nacional,
SPEAKER_04: the pictures were
taken in two days
SPEAKER_04: and only during morning hours.
SPEAKER_04: From those two days, a brief
correspondence between Lino Lara
SPEAKER_04: and General Pedro Pedraza
hast been preserved.
SPEAKER_04: Here, after making it clear
that he’s also a photographer
SPEAKER_04: and not a superstitious person,
officer Pedraza asks himself:
SPEAKER_04: is there any risk in imitating the dead?
SPEAKER_04: There is no known answer from
Lino Lara to this question.
SPEAKER_04: In fact, very little
is known about him.
SPEAKER_04: In contrast, a lot has been
written about these photographs
SPEAKER_04: and the importance of violent
events reenactments in the country.
SPEAKER_04: It's easy to think that the idea of
this first tale has been influenced
SPEAKER_04: by some of the first films
of Thomas Alva Edison
SPEAKER_04: in which episodes of famous
executions are recreated.
SPEAKER_04: For example: Here they recreate
the death of Leon Czolgosz
SPEAKER_04: a Polish anarchist sentenced to death for the
murder of the president of the United States,
SPEAKER_04: William McKinley, on
September the 6th, 1901.
SPEAKER_04: Edison's goal was to
publicize the electric chair
SPEAKER_04: to make it the new method of execution in
the country and replace the gallows.
SPEAKER_04: He knew that neither technology, nor
his inventions were neutral
SPEAKER_04: and since electricity could be
turned into a killing device
SPEAKER_04: the cinematograph and the pictures
SPEAKER_04: could also unleash very useful energies
for the project of a country.
SPEAKER_04: These landscapes of the Magdalena river
SPEAKER_04: were recorded in photographs
by Rafael Reyes in 1909.
SPEAKER_04: Back then, the former president dedicated himself
to travel around the unknown national territory
SPEAKER_04: thinking about how Colombian cinema could be
used according to the project of a country.
SPEAKER_04: The result of this 22-day-long
adventure was a book called:
SPEAKER_04: "Presidential excursions,
notes from a travel journal."
SPEAKER_04: The book contains a detailed inventory of
the main natural resources of the country
SPEAKER_04: in relation to the industrial means
necessary for its exploitation.
SPEAKER_04: For instance:
SPEAKER_04: there's a list of the total length of
the railway tracks of each province
SPEAKER_04: in relation to the increase of hectares
cultivated year by year since 1895.
SPEAKER_04: Reyes intended to boost
several trades,
SPEAKER_04: especially in the areas
of banana plantations.
SPEAKER_04: Therefore, articles from
French and English magazines
SPEAKER_04: recommending the consumption
of bananas were included
SPEAKER_04: arguing that bananas were the most
hygienic and nutritious fruit of them all.
SPEAKER_04: At the same time, this documentation is
accompanied by a series of photographs
SPEAKER_04: that privilege images of landscapes,
agricultural colonies, train tracks
SPEAKER_04: prominent personalities of the
industrial world and workers.
SPEAKER_04: This book was the first visual
record of the national territory.
SPEAKER_04: Rafael Reyes described it as
an "explained cinematograph".
SPEAKER_04: Banana field blueprint
SPEAKER_04: The truth was, Rafael Reyes did not only
intend to create a catalog of wealths
SPEAKER_04: to allure foreign multinationals.
SPEAKER_04: His true purpose was to create a
unified image of the country,
SPEAKER_04: which due to the characteristics
of its geography
SPEAKER_04: suffered from a great lack of
communication among its regions
SPEAKER_04: which by the time was already producing great
losses in large portions of the territory.
SPEAKER_04: Rafael Reyes was looking for something a
little more elusive and much more dangerous.
SPEAKER_04: He was sure that all people of the
country should be united by something,
SPEAKER_04: a supposed "national essence" that
would prevent their dismemberment.
SPEAKER_04: He asked himself: What are we?
SPEAKER_04: The result of a discrete genocide?
SPEAKER_04: Or are we the occasional guardians
of infinite clusters of gold
SPEAKER_04: and immense expanses of water
that turn into fruits?
SPEAKER_04: Driven by the scientific spirit of the time
SPEAKER_04: Reyes saw in the photographic device
the best tool to look for that essence.
SPEAKER_04: He thought: If photographs can capture,
better than anything else in the world
SPEAKER_04: the outstanding feature of the identity of
a subject that is, of course, his face
SPEAKER_04: why wouldn’t it be able,
with enough effort,
SPEAKER_04: to reveal the image of the true face
of these lands and thus, its identity?
SPEAKER_04: A group of the right images
can unify the country.
SPEAKER_04: Thus, Rafael Reyes begins like this
with his obsession with portraits
SPEAKER_04: which would result in the most significant
image of the book and possibly of the time:
SPEAKER_04: The portrait of cacique
José Dolores and his wife
SPEAKER_04: holding a portrait of former
President Rafael Reyes.
SPEAKER_04: It has been thought, quite often,
SPEAKER_04: that Reyes was saying only one
thing with this photograph:
SPEAKER_04: I am Colombia.
SPEAKER_04: The photographs of Rafael Reyes
and Lino Lara
SPEAKER_04: represented a technological
innovation for the country.
SPEAKER_04: From this moment on,
SPEAKER_04: the way in which the different events were
narrated would be radically transformed.
SPEAKER_04: They marked the beginning of an informative
treatment based on the display of images.
SPEAKER_04: For those who, like myself, have experienced the
war in Colombia exclusively through images
SPEAKER_04: those of television,
magazines and newspapers;
SPEAKER_04: the figure of Rafael Rayes
asks us a question:
SPEAKER_04: Is there any link between the production of
images and the war events in the country?
SPEAKER_04: Over the years, the question about who’s
a guerilla combatant and who’s not,
SPEAKER_04: suffers a transformation.
SPEAKER_04: It mutates, becoming the obsession
for one specific image:
SPEAKER_04: The image of the dead guerilla.
SPEAKER_04: The image of the insurgent murdered
at hands of agents of the State
SPEAKER_04: is spread through all
screens of the country.
SPEAKER_04: In a short time, it manages to dominate
the imagination of public opinion
SPEAKER_04: and its production is furiously
demanded from everywhere.
SPEAKER_04: "¡More images!", says the
redactor to the journalist,
SPEAKER_04: the editor to the photographer,
and the General to the soldier.
SPEAKER_04: "I want to see a dead guerrilla
every day", says the president.
SPEAKER_04: But it’s also to be
heard in schools
SPEAKER_04: bars, stores, churches, houses;
among friends and family.
SPEAKER_04: Then, the horror came.
SPEAKER_04: It was discovered that many of those bodies,
and in consequence many of those images
SPEAKER_04: didn’t belong to authentic guerilla-soldier.
SPEAKER_04: That the bodies were
of young innocents disguised,
SPEAKER_04: that everything was a staging
SPEAKER_04: and that the testimonies of the soldiers
were also reproductions of other combats.
SPEAKER_04: The response of the audience
to that truth was apathy.
SPEAKER_04: We all said: Those are the mothers of
the youngsters called "false positives".
SPEAKER_04: Nobody said: "I’m the one who was found dead
in a distant area disguised as a guerilla".
SPEAKER_04: Nobody said: I’m the one
that’s missing.
SPEAKER_04: We just said:
SPEAKER_04: Those have to be the family members of
the murdered people that are protesting
SPEAKER_04: just asking to recover the good
name of their beloved ones.
SPEAKER_04: Nobody said:
SPEAKER_04: I’m one of the "false positives", one of
the State murders that were celebrated.
SPEAKER_04: Real deaths put in combat scenarios
SPEAKER_04: as if the war events in the country would
have been replaced by some kind of parody
SPEAKER_04: by an evil imitation created by war itself.
SPEAKER_04: As if after all these years, the war would
be trying to create its own representations
SPEAKER_04: its own copies.
SPEAKER_04: In 1906, Rafael Reyes
created a "false document"
SPEAKER_04: to produce a story
about an execution.
SPEAKER_04: A century later,
SPEAKER_04: the Colombian Army created the "false positives"
to simulate the victory of the war.
SPEAKER_04: Thus, the "false positives" seem to be
part of a national fiction tradition
SPEAKER_04: that begins with the photographs
of Lino Lara,
SPEAKER_04: with the first staging of violent events
SPEAKER_04: and the birth of Colombian Cinema.
SPEAKER_04: My mother had a recurrent dream that,
according to her, chased her.
SPEAKER_04: In the dream, a coffin was driven
around the streets of the city.
SPEAKER_04: Every time she told it, she said:
SPEAKER_04: "I think of that image as if I was
the dead person inside of the coffin."
SPEAKER_04: "I imagine the people on the streets watching
and thinking in silence: someone died."
SPEAKER_04: I asked her if she ever had
that dream again. She told me yes.
SPEAKER_04: But that it didn’t
matter to her anymore.
SPEAKER_04: Over time, that image had become
boring to her, kind of obvious, pathetic.
SPEAKER_04: Nevertheless,
SPEAKER_04: she had lately started to feel curious about
the identity of the man who drove the car.
SPEAKER_04: She told me: "I’ve been wondering
lately how his hands would be, his lips,
SPEAKER_04: the shape of his teeth.
I want to know his name".
SPEAKER_04: My mother has spent the last few months
between hospitals and this house.
SPEAKER_04: The house of Maria, her best friend.
SPEAKER_04: After several months,
SPEAKER_04: the doctors stated that if she didn’t
talk was because she didn’t want to.
SPEAKER_04: Because they couldn’t find
any reason for it.
SPEAKER_04: Other doctors, the most pessimistic
and less reserved ones,
SPEAKER_04: made us understand that she just
didn’t want to live anymore.
SPEAKER_04: The truth is,
the more time passes,
SPEAKER_04: the feeling that my mother
is disappearing grows.
SPEAKER_04: Somehow, every day her presence
resembles more of a ghost.
SPEAKER_04: It’s as if she would have escaped time,
and would be merely a thought of mine.
SPEAKER_04: Today is her birthday.
SPEAKER_04: During the last week, an evangelist called
Ricardo Javier has been harassing my mother.
SPEAKER_04: He stands in front of the house to talk to
her about the power of the word of Jesus.
SPEAKER_04: He was saying yesterday:
SPEAKER_04: "Gods kingdom is like a thief.
SPEAKER_04: If we would know when a thief is coming,
nobody would ever be robbed.
SPEAKER_04: Gods kingdom comes when we’re not
expecting it, so keep your eyes open."
SPEAKER_04: ♪ I remember when I saw
you for the first time
SPEAKER_04: ♪ and my eyes teared up when I looked at you.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ I can't deny it, I was
scared to confess to you
SPEAKER_04: These images belong to the thirty-fourth
Colombian professional football tournament
SPEAKER_04: having the Atlético
Nacional team as champion,
SPEAKER_04: after a victory against
América de Cali
SPEAKER_04: with a difference of one goal to zero.
SPEAKER_04: During the tournament, Atlético Nacional
would play a total of 61 matches.
SPEAKER_04: They would win 28, draw 17 and lose 16.
SPEAKER_04: The particularity of this
tournament is due to Carlos Pelbet
SPEAKER_04: and his small family
company, Pelbet S.A.
SPEAKER_04: Along with his brother, four
cameramen and a commentator
SPEAKER_04: Carlos Pelbet recorded all the matches
of Atlético Nacional during the tournament.
SPEAKER_04: This was the first time
SPEAKER_04: that professional cameras were taken
to the football stadiums in the country
SPEAKER_04: and those were also the first efforts to
broadcast the football events in Colombia.
SPEAKER_04: The transmissions made by Carlos
Pelbet were very limited,
SPEAKER_04: since they were designed to
reach a few radio studios only
SPEAKER_04: where the announcers told the listeners
what were seeing on the screens.
SPEAKER_04: Carlos Pelbet says to himself:
I transformed the history of this country
SPEAKER_04: through football and cameras.
SPEAKER_04: I brought the replay and the slow motion.
I educated the eye of many young people.
SPEAKER_04: Carlos stops in this image.
SPEAKER_04: Just a few minutes left
of the championship final.
SPEAKER_04: After this fall
SPEAKER_04: the referee interprets a
penalty kick and sanctions it.
SPEAKER_04: Immediately, the coach of the
America enters the field
SPEAKER_04: and tells all his players
to leave the game,
SPEAKER_04: arguing lack of guarantees
from the referee.
SPEAKER_04: The game was never finished.
SPEAKER_04: After this event, Carlos Pelbet was harassed
for several days by hundreds of fanatics
SPEAKER_04: who wanted to obtain the
recordings of the game,
SPEAKER_04: with the intention of studying the
images very carefully themselves
SPEAKER_04: together with friends and family.
SPEAKER_04: Repeat them again and
again, frame per frame,
SPEAKER_04: and dissecting that instant
as many times as necessary
SPEAKER_04: until it spoke for itself and said
if the fault was simulated or real.
SPEAKER_04: It's impossible for Carlos Pelbet
to determine that kind of issue.
SPEAKER_04: For him, there is simply no
difference between someone who falls
SPEAKER_04: and someone who
pretends to fall.
SPEAKER_04: More than 30 years after
those first recordings
SPEAKER_04: Carlos keeps working with images
coming from football events.
SPEAKER_04: - Was my exit okay?
- It was fine.
SPEAKER_04: Cut.
SPEAKER_04: Roll camera, roll sound.
SPEAKER_04: - Do I have to clap again?
- Yes, please.
SPEAKER_04: - Ready?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_04: When I started this movie, I was trying to
find out if my mother was pretending or not.
SPEAKER_04: If she had really turned mute,
if she was really dying.
SPEAKER_04: Neither my father nor other relatives
or close friends believed her
SPEAKER_04: nor the doctors nor even
the religious people.
SPEAKER_04: But, in a similar way to
what many experienced
SPEAKER_04: when analyzing the images of the national
Football championship final game
SPEAKER_04: there may be no difference
between someone who suffers
SPEAKER_04: and someone who
pretends to suffer.
SPEAKER_04: So, Carlos points out that
it's useless to judge an image
SPEAKER_04: wanting to discern what's
real in it and what’s not.
SPEAKER_04: For him, images are jus not a good
place to look for the truth.
SPEAKER_04: Then, from the projects of
Thomas Alva Edison, Rafael Reyes
SPEAKER_04: and the recent images that
dramatize deaths and violent events
SPEAKER_04: perhaps it would be
better to ask ourselves:
SPEAKER_04: What effects do these
images have on the living?
SPEAKER_04: Do they have any participation
in the events they represent?
SPEAKER_04: For example these women.
SPEAKER_04: All three are actresses
SPEAKER_04: who pose as if they had lost
a family member in the war
SPEAKER_04: and were claiming for them.
SPEAKER_04: …or something like that.
SPEAKER_04: In a similar way to what happened with
the photographs of February 10th
SPEAKER_04: what would be properly considered as
the first film made in Colombia
SPEAKER_04: was also born from the intention to represent
the attempt and death of a political leader.
SPEAKER_04: On October 15th, 1914, a few
blocks from the Capitol
SPEAKER_04: the popular military
hero Rafael Uribe Uribe
SPEAKER_04: received a mortal blow with an ax
on the right side of his head.
SPEAKER_04: The politician was immediately transferred
to a house in the center of the city
SPEAKER_04: where he agonized for
14 hours and finally died.
SPEAKER_04: It’s told that hundreds of his followers
walked all the way back to the Capitol
SPEAKER_04: and with a white handkerchief
in their hands
SPEAKER_04: tried to pick up of the ground
the blood of the politician.
SPEAKER_04: That same afternoon, while
Rafael Uribe Uribe still lived
SPEAKER_04: a few meters from the house where he was,
the Italian brothers Di Doménico
SPEAKER_04: who later would be recognized as
"the fathers of Colombian Cinema"
SPEAKER_04: began with urgency the filming of the
first film of the country, entitled:
SPEAKER_04: "The drama of October 15th",
in which this murder was recreated.
SPEAKER_04: Only one shot from the
film is preserved.
SPEAKER_04: These images are from the same
date but made with other cameras.
SPEAKER_04: However, due to the great
controversy caused by the film
SPEAKER_04: extensive descriptions of their images
can be found in newspapers of the time.
SPEAKER_04: For example, we know that the
film started with a fade
SPEAKER_04: that slowly showed a
portrait of the soldier.
SPEAKER_04: After almost a minute in which the
image was still on the screen
SPEAKER_04: followed a scene that recreated the last
moments of agony and death of the politician.
SPEAKER_04: We also know that the film
could never be fully projected.
SPEAKER_04: Despite the good intentions
of the Di Doménico brothers,
SPEAKER_04: the audience couldn't bear to see
the images of the hero dying
SPEAKER_04: nor could they bare seeing his assassins.
SPEAKER_04: The public opinion
reacted radically
SPEAKER_04: and pursued with the censorship
and destruction of the film.
SPEAKER_04: In their defense, the Italians,
SPEAKER_04: who due to the public harassment
could never make a film again
SPEAKER_04: argued in their favor referring to the
images of Christ dying on the cross.
SPEAKER_04: If the highest institutions such as museums
and churches in all regions of the planet
SPEAKER_04: allocate entire pavilions with the sole function
of protecting the image of Christ dying
SPEAKER_04: it is because Christ reincarnates
in each one of those images.
SPEAKER_04: To adore those images
is to adore the Christ,
SPEAKER_04: those images create the
world of Christianity.
SPEAKER_04: Thus, the Italians thought
SPEAKER_04: that a State is also the
sum of all its images.
SPEAKER_04: For the Di Doménico brothers, destroying
the images of Rafael Uribe Uribe dying
SPEAKER_04: was opting for a country incapable of
imagining and thinking about their dead.
SPEAKER_04: The first film of the Colombian Cinema,
is born, and dies from this event.
SPEAKER_04: This is its only remaining image
SPEAKER_04: the famous image of the woman
holding the patriotic symbols.
SPEAKER_04: I imagine the death
of Rafael Uribe Uribe
SPEAKER_04: with a coffin that crosses the streets,
marking the path of a crowd.
SPEAKER_04: The image of the people that
accompanies their leader.
SPEAKER_04: Perhaps this film by the
Di Doménico brothers
SPEAKER_04: and the events that surrounded it,
allow us to see from a new perspective,
SPEAKER_04: the images made by Rafael Reyes
and Thomas Alva Edison.
SPEAKER_04: A perspective that does not focus
on the truth of the images,
SPEAKER_04: but on the reaction that
the public has before them.
SPEAKER_04: These events highlight that the staging
of death has a relative value.
SPEAKER_04: Rafael Reyes and Thomas Edison
staged the death of rebels.
SPEAKER_04: These images are celebrated
and widely broadcasted.
SPEAKER_04: On the contrary,
SPEAKER_04: the Di Doménico brothers recreated
the death of a beloved political leader
SPEAKER_04: and hurt the sensitivity of the national
public, the images were destroyed.
SPEAKER_04: This shows that the images
collect a sensitivity.
SPEAKER_04: A sensitivity that
only becomes tolerable
SPEAKER_04: when it reflects the image that a
country likes to receive from itself.
SPEAKER_04: These events also reveal
something even simpler:
SPEAKER_04: the survival of certain
images leads to sympathy
SPEAKER_04: and intensifies the idea that there
are deaths worthy of mourning
SPEAKER_04: and others that are not.
SPEAKER_04: When I look at my
mother from a distance,
SPEAKER_04: I feel that at any moment she will say
something and her expression will change.
SPEAKER_04: Maybe all I have to do is wait.
SPEAKER_04: I have decided that I must
believe in her muteness.
SPEAKER_04: I can’t not do it,
when I see her images.
SPEAKER_04: I think that I've been looking
in the wrong places
SPEAKER_04: and the reasons for her muteness
are somewhere else.
SPEAKER_04: Together with Carlos Pelbet, we recreated the
work of a group of forensic anthropologists.
SPEAKER_04: Some years ago in Colombia,
they had started
SPEAKER_04: the search and identification of the bodies
of people missing during the war.
SPEAKER_04: Exhumation units
throughout the national territory
SPEAKER_04: were in search of the deaths who were hidden
underground by the different armies.
SPEAKER_04: Together with some neighbors and friends who
disguised themselves as forensic and military
SPEAKER_04: we walked around some
fields around the village
SPEAKER_04: dug graves and did a
small performance
SPEAKER_04: of the search for the bodies
of those missing persons.
SPEAKER_04: No matter how hard I try
SPEAKER_04: I can't make myself
more than a small idea
SPEAKER_04: of the dimension and cruelty that
the "false positives" meant.
SPEAKER_04: I wonder if, with the purpose
of telling about these crimes
SPEAKER_04: the best way wouldn’t have been through
images invoking the real victims
SPEAKER_04: the bodies of the executed youths, the
testimonies of the relatives, the witnesses
SPEAKER_04: and the people who actually
suffered it in life.
SPEAKER_04: However, I suspect that the same
thing would happened
SPEAKER_04: as it did, when they were first broadcasted
in television across the country.
SPEAKER_04: We would simply close our eyes
to avoid feeling those deaths.
SPEAKER_04: When the "false positives" were presented
as victories of the National Army
SPEAKER_04: they were celebrated and widespread deaths.
SPEAKER_04: But when those same dead people were
stripped of their insurgent disguise
SPEAKER_04: and turned into state crimes
SPEAKER_04: they didn't become a scandalous image.
SPEAKER_04: There was something about the theater they
represented, that the audience clung to.
SPEAKER_04: Perhaps, this is what the
"false positives" warn us from.
SPEAKER_04: That much of the way we feel about
the deaths of the war in the country
SPEAKER_04: is build upon the field of
appearances and images.
SPEAKER_04: The representations that have
been made of the violent events
SPEAKER_04: have directed our sensitivity, making the
war of the country seem tolerable for us
SPEAKER_04: as long as the dead ones remain the same.
SPEAKER_04: The images have become
an instrument of war.
SPEAKER_04: A war is also the history
of its images.
SPEAKER_04: ♪ With justice and truth
next to the people it is
SPEAKER_04: I found a recording made by my mother.
SPEAKER_04: It’s special because she doesn’t appear,
instead her voice is heard.
SPEAKER_04: Near the end she says my name.