SPEAKER_10: ♪ with the first fire of the dawn
SPEAKER_10: ♪ the little song that was
born in our guerrilla voice
SPEAKER_10: ♪ of struggle and future.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ With Bolivar, Galán already rode again.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ No more weeping and pain of the homeland.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ We are people who go after freedom
SPEAKER_10: ♪ building the path of peace.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
SPEAKER_10: ♪ for the fatherland,
the people and the bread.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
SPEAKER_10: ♪ to achieve freedom.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Guerrilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
SPEAKER_10: ♪ for the fatherland,
the people and the bread.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
SPEAKER_10: ♪ to achieve freedom.