SPEAKER_16: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_16: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_16: Dad!
SPEAKER_16: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_16: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_16: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_16: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_16: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_16: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_16: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_16: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_16: Please.
SPEAKER_16: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_16: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_16: Tell me.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_16: Come home.
SPEAKER_16: Go!
SPEAKER_16: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_16: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui...
SPEAKER_16: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_16: I've realized...
SPEAKER_16: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_16: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_16: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_16: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_16: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_16: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_16: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_16: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_16: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_16: Granny!
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_16: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_16: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_16: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_16: What's his name?
SPEAKER_16: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_16: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_16: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_16: Me.
SPEAKER_16: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_16: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_16: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_16: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_16: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_16: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_16: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_16: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_16: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_16: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_16: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_16: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_16: Come out!
SPEAKER_16: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_16: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_16: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_16: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_16: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_16: wounded me
SPEAKER_16: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_16: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_16: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_16: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_16: You should have written.
SPEAKER_16: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_16: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_16: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_16: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_16: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_16: They never get...
SPEAKER_16: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_16: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_16: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_16: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_16: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_16: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_16: You're here.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_16: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_16: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_16: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_16: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_16: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_16: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_16: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_16: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_16: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_16: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_16: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_16: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_16: Of course.
SPEAKER_16: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_16: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_16: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_16: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_16: Good idea!
SPEAKER_16: The 1950s
SPEAKER_16: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_16: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_16: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_16: Take a break.
SPEAKER_16: It's ready.
SPEAKER_16: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_16: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_16: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_16: and after that...
SPEAKER_16: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_16: Enough?
SPEAKER_16: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_16: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_16: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_16: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_16: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_16: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_16: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_16: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_16: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_16: What do you know?
SPEAKER_16: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_16: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_16: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_16: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_16: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_16: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_16: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_16: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_16: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_16: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_16: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_16: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_16: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_16: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_16: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_16: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_16: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_16: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_16: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_16: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_16: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_16: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_16: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_16: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_16: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_16: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_16: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_16: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_16: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_16: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_16: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_16: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_16: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_16: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_16: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_16: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_16: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_16: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_16: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_16: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_16: from making you go.
SPEAKER_16: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_16: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_16: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_16: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_16: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_16: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_16: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_16: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_16: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_16: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_16: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_16: Go away!
SPEAKER_16: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_16: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_16: You killed him.
SPEAKER_16: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_16: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_16: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_16: Go away!
SPEAKER_16: All right.
SPEAKER_16: I'm going.
SPEAKER_16: The 1960s
SPEAKER_16: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_16: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_16: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_16: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_16: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_16: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_16: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_16: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_16: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_16: He can run?
SPEAKER_16: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_16: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_16: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_16: Come inside.
SPEAKER_16: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_16: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_16: A good family.
SPEAKER_16: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_16: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_16: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_16: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_16: What do you think?
SPEAKER_16: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_16: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_16: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_16: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_16: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_16: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_16: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_16: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_16: A cripple?
SPEAKER_16: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_16: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_16: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_16: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_16: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_16: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_16: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_16: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_16: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_16: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_16: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_16: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_16: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_16: Come over here.
SPEAKER_16: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_16: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_16: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_16: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_16: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_16: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_16: You cold?
SPEAKER_16: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_16: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_16: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_16: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_16: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_16: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_16: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_16: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_16: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_16: Very!
SPEAKER_16: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_16: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_16: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_16: Okay.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_16: Come inside.
SPEAKER_16: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_16: Yes.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_16: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_16: What's happened?
SPEAKER_16: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_16: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_16: When is it due?
SPEAKER_16: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_16: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_16: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_16: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_16: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_16: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_16: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_16: Don't move.
SPEAKER_16: Go ask.
SPEAKER_16: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_16: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_16: Want one?
SPEAKER_16: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_16: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_16: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_16: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_16: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_16: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_16: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_16: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_16: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_16: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_16: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_16: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_16: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_16: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_16: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_16: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_16: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_16: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_16: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_16: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_16: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_16: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_16: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_16: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_16: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_16: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_16: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_16: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_16: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_16: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_16: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_16: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_16: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_16: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_16: You'll pull through!
SPEAKER_16: It's all right.
SPEAKER_16: Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_16: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_16: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia! You'll pull through.
Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_16: Please, Doctor, she's my only daughter.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_16: Some years later...
SPEAKER_16: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_16: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_16: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_16: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_16: to show her.
SPEAKER_16: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_16: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_16: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_16: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_16: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_16: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_16: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_16: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_16: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_16: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_16: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_16: You will ride on an ox's back.
SPEAKER_16: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...