SPEAKER_01: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_01: How much?
SPEAKER_01: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_01: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_01: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_01: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_01: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_01: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_01: What is it?
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_01: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_01: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_01: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_01: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_01: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_01: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_01: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_01: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_01: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_01: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_01: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_01: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_01: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_01: Fugui...
SPEAKER_01: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_01: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_01: The day...
SPEAKER_01: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_01: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_01: Written?
SPEAKER_01: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_01: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_01: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_01: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_01: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_01: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_01: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_01: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_01: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_01: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_01: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_01: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_01: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_01: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_01: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_01: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_01: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_01: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_01: that we could...
SPEAKER_01: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_01: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_01: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_01: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_01: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_01: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_01: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_01: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_01: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_01: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_01: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_01: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_01: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_01: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_01: No, really.
SPEAKER_01: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_01: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_01: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_01: We approve.
SPEAKER_01: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_01: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_01: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_01: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_01: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_01: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_01: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_01: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_01: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_01: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_01: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_01: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_01: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_01: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_01: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_01: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_01: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_01: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_01: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_01: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_01: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_01: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_01: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_01: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_01: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_01: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_01: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_01: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_01: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_01: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_01: Help us!
SPEAKER_01: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_01: Quick!
SPEAKER_01: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_01: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_01: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_01: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_01: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_01: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_01: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_01: and life will get better and better.