SPEAKER_02: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_02: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_02: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_02: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_02: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_02: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_02: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_02: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_02: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_02: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_02: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_02: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_02: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_02: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_02: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_02: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_02: The 1940s
SPEAKER_02: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_02: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_02: Well?
SPEAKER_02: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_02: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_02: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_02: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_02: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_02: Besides...
SPEAKER_02: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_02: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_02: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_02: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_02: As for me...
SPEAKER_02: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_02: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_02: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_02: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_02: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_02: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_02: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_02: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_02: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_02: come see the show.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_02: The Red Guards are in control!