SPEAKER_03: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_03: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_03: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_03: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_03: It's settled.
SPEAKER_03: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_03: The wounded.
SPEAKER_03: No one's left.
SPEAKER_03: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_03: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_03: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_03: So, no running?
SPEAKER_03: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_03: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_03: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_03: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui...
SPEAKER_03: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_03: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_03: It's money.
SPEAKER_03: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_03: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_03: I will remember.
SPEAKER_03: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_03: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_03: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_03: Never mind.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_03: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui!
SPEAKER_03: Who's there?
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_03: Who?
SPEAKER_03: What do you want?
SPEAKER_03: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_03: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui...
SPEAKER_03: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_03: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_03: You came for this?
SPEAKER_03: Take this...
SPEAKER_03: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_03: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_03: No.
SPEAKER_03: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_03: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_03: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_03: and better get back.
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng, remember...