SPEAKER_10: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_10: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_10: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_10: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_10: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_10: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_10: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_10: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_10: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_10: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_10: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_10: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_10: Back already?
SPEAKER_10: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_10: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_10: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_10: Uncle.
SPEAKER_10: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_10: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_10: Very soon.
SPEAKER_10: And then?
SPEAKER_10: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_10: After oxen...
SPEAKER_10: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_10: I want to ride on an ox's back!