SPEAKER_06: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_06: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_06: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_06: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_06: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_06: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_06: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_06: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_06: As for me...
SPEAKER_06: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_06: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_06: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_06: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_06: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_06: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_06: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_06: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_06: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_06: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_06: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_06: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_06: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_06: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_06: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_06: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_06: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_06: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_06: Wake up.
SPEAKER_06: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_06: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_06: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_06: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_06: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_06: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_06: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_06: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_06: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_06: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_06: Of course.
SPEAKER_06: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_06: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: They did.
SPEAKER_06: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_06: No doctors?
SPEAKER_06: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_06: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_06: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_06: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_06: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_06: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_06: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_06: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_06: Is it?
SPEAKER_06: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_06: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_06: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_06: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_06: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_06: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_06: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_06: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_06: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_06: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_06: Let's see.
SPEAKER_06: and the geese will turn into sheep...