SPEAKER_05: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_05: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_05: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_05: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_05: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_05: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_05: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_05: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_05: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_05: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_05: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_05: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_05: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_05: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_05: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_05: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_05: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_05: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_05: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_05: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_05: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_05: Please come again.
SPEAKER_05: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_05: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_05: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_05: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_05: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_05: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_05: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_05: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_05: Cheers!
SPEAKER_05: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_05: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_05: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_05: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_05: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_05: No.
SPEAKER_05: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_05: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_05: Let me think.
SPEAKER_05: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_05: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_05: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_05: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_05: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_05: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_05: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_05: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_05: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_05: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_05: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_05: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_05: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_05: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_05: Little Bun, behave yourself.