SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_14: Take care.
SPEAKER_14: - What'd he just say?
- Nothing. Eat.
SPEAKER_14: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_14: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_14: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_14: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_14: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_14: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_14: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_14: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_14: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_14: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_14: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_14: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_14: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_14: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_14: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_14: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_14: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_14: Okay?
SPEAKER_14: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_14: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_14: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_14: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_14: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_14: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_14: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_14: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_14: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_14: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_14: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_14: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_14: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_14: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_14: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_14: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_14: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_14: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_14: Take this.
SPEAKER_14: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_14: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_14: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_14: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_14: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_14: How could that be?
SPEAKER_14: How?
SPEAKER_14: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_14: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_14: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_14: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_14: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_14: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_14: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_14: How could you?
SPEAKER_14: What is this?
SPEAKER_14: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_14: This is too much.
SPEAKER_14: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_14: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_14: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_14: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_14: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_14: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_14: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_14: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_14: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_14: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_14: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_14: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_14: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_14: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_14: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_14: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_14: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_14: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_14: Let her go!
SPEAKER_14: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_14: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_14: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_14: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_14: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_14: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_14: We must be going.
SPEAKER_14: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_14: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_14: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_14: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_14: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_14: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_14: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_14: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_14: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_14: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_14: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_14: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_14: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_14: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_14: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_14: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_14: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_14: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_14: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_14: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_14: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_14: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_14: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_14: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_14: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_14: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_14: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_14: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_14: Good idea.
SPEAKER_14: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_14: Oxygen.