SPEAKER_11: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_11: Get out!
SPEAKER_11: I've just...
SPEAKER_11: Let's play!
SPEAKER_11: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_11: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_11: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_11: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_11: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_11: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_11: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_11: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_11: So, no running?
SPEAKER_11: How?
SPEAKER_11: How could you?
SPEAKER_11: This is too much.
SPEAKER_11: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_11: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_11: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_11: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_11: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_11: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_11: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_11: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_11: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_11: Answer me!
SPEAKER_11: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_11: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_11: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_11: No!
SPEAKER_11: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_11: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_11: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_11: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_11: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_11: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_11: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_11: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_11: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_11: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_11: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_11: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_11: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_11: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_11: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_11: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_11: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_11: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_11: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_11: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_11: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_11: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_11: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_11: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_11: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_11: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_11: He was starving.
SPEAKER_11: It's okay.
SPEAKER_11: We shouldn't have given him water.