SPEAKER_00: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_00: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_00: You're up.
SPEAKER_00: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_00: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_00: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_00: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_00: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_00: I'm home.
SPEAKER_00: Home.
SPEAKER_00: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_00: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_00: They shot him.
SPEAKER_00: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_00: He is dead.
SPEAKER_00: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_00: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_00: When you get there...
SPEAKER_00: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_00: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_00: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_00: That's good.
SPEAKER_00: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_00: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_00: Our family...
SPEAKER_00: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_00: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_00: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_00: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_00: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_00: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_00: From where?
SPEAKER_00: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_00: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_00: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_00: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_00: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_00: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_00: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_00: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_00: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_00: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_00: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_00: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_00: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_00: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_00: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_00: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_00: I wouldn't dare.
SPEAKER_00: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_00: Have some water.