SPEAKER_02: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_02: Go!
SPEAKER_02: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_02: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_02: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_02: Sir!
SPEAKER_02: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_02: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_02: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_02: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_02: wounded me
SPEAKER_02: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_02: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_02: Take that!
SPEAKER_02: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_02: Enough!
SPEAKER_02: How could you?
SPEAKER_02: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_02: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_02: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_02: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_02: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_02: Enough?
SPEAKER_02: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_02: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_02: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_02: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_02: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_02: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_02: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_02: The 1960s
SPEAKER_02: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_02: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_02: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_02: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_02: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_02: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_02: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_02: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_02: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_02: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_02: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_02: Come over here.
SPEAKER_02: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_02: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_02: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_02: He'll know.
SPEAKER_02: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_02: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_02: You'll pull through!
SPEAKER_02: Oxygen.