SPEAKER_24: Fugui...
SPEAKER_24: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_24: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_24: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_24: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_24: Granny!
SPEAKER_24: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_24: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_24: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_24: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_24: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_24: What's his name?
SPEAKER_24: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_24: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_24: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_24: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_24: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_24: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_24: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_24: from making you go.
SPEAKER_24: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_24: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_24: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_24: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_24: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_24: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_24: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_24: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_24: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_24: Go away!
SPEAKER_24: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_24: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_24: You killed him.
SPEAKER_24: You cold?
SPEAKER_24: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_24: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_24: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_24: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_24: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_24: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_24: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.