SPEAKER_10: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_10: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_10: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_10: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_10: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_10: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_10: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_10: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_10: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_10: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_10: Well?
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_10: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_10: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_10: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_10: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_10: What is it?
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_10: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_10: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_10: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_10: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_10: Okay?
SPEAKER_10: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_10: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_10: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_10: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_10: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_10: Fugui...
SPEAKER_10: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_10: Good.
SPEAKER_10: This is great.
SPEAKER_10: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_10: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_10: Rice costs more than wheat.