SPEAKER_14: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_14: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_14: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_14: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_14: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_14: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_14: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_14: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_14: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_14: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_14: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_14: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_14: Wake up.
SPEAKER_14: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_14: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_14: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_14: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_14: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_14: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_14: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_14: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_14: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_14: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_14: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_14: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_14: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_14: He's all right.
SPEAKER_14: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_14: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_14: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_14: Help us!
SPEAKER_14: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_14: Quick!
SPEAKER_14: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_14: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_14: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_14: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_14: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_14: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_14: How about in here?
SPEAKER_14: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_14: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_14: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_14: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_14: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_14: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_14: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_14: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_14: and life will get better and better.