SPEAKER_25: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_25: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_25: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_25: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_25: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_25: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_25: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_25: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_25: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_25: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_25: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_25: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_25: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_25: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_25: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_25: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_25: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_25: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_25: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_25: Look at this.
SPEAKER_25: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_25: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_25: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_25: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_25: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_25: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_25: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_25: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_25: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_25: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_25: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_25: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_25: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_25: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_25: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_25: It's all here?
SPEAKER_25: Keep these.
SPEAKER_25: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_25: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_25: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_25: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_25: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_25: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_25: I see your point.
SPEAKER_25: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_25: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_25: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_25: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_25: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_25: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_25: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_25: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_25: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_25: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_25: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_25: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_25: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_25: How so?
SPEAKER_25: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_25: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_25: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_25: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_25: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_25: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_25: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_25: Fugui...
SPEAKER_25: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_25: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_25: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_25: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_25: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_25: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_25: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_25: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_25: Sit here.
SPEAKER_25: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_25: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_25: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_25: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_25: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_25: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_25: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_25: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_25: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_25: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_25: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_25: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_25: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_25: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_25: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_25: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_25: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_25: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_25: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_25: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_25: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_25: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_25: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_25: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_25: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_25: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_25: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_25: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_25: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_25: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_25: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_25: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_25: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_25: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_25: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_25: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_25: No, really.
SPEAKER_25: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_25: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_25: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_25: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_25: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_25: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_25: Cheers!
SPEAKER_25: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_25: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_25: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_25: Why?
SPEAKER_25: I don't know.
SPEAKER_25: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_25: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_25: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_25: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_25: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_25: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_25: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_25: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_25: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_25: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_25: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_25: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_25: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_25: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_25: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_25: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_25: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_25: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_25: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_25: Some water should help.