SPEAKER_01: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_01: How much?
SPEAKER_01: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_01: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_01: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_01: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_01: It's settled.
SPEAKER_01: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_01: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_01: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_01: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_01: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_01: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_01: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_01: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_01: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_01: The day...
SPEAKER_01: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_01: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_01: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_01: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_01: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_01: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_01: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_01: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_01: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_01: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_01: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_01: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_01: Landlords?
SPEAKER_01: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_01: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_01: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_01: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_01: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_01: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_01: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_01: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_01: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_01: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_01: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_01: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_01: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_01: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_01: that we could...
SPEAKER_01: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_01: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_01: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_01: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_01: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_01: He can run?
SPEAKER_01: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_01: I approve.
SPEAKER_01: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_01: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_01: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_01: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_01: We approve.
SPEAKER_01: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_01: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_01: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_01: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_01: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_01: Of course.
SPEAKER_01: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_01: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_01: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_01: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_01: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_01: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_01: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_01: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_01: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_01: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_01: They did.
SPEAKER_01: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_01: No doctors?
SPEAKER_01: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_01: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_01: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_01: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_01: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_01: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_01: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_01: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_01: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_01: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_01: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_01: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_01: Is it?
SPEAKER_01: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_01: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_01: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_01: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_01: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_01: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_01: Let's see.