SPEAKER_21: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_21: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_21: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_21: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_21: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_21: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_21: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_21: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_21: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_21: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_21: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_21: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_21: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_21: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_21: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_21: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_21: The 1940s
SPEAKER_21: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_21: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_21: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_21: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_21: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_21: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_21: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_21: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_21: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_21: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_21: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_21: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_21: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_21: Of course.
SPEAKER_21: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_21: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_21: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_21: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_21: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_21: As for me...
SPEAKER_21: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_21: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_21: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_21: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_21: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_21: Written?
SPEAKER_21: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_21: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_21: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_21: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_21: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_21: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_21: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_21: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_21: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_21: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_21: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_21: On the mend.
SPEAKER_21: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_21: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_21: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_21: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_21: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_21: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_21: You just have to!
SPEAKER_21: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_21: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_21: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_21: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_21: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_21: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_21: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_21: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_21: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_21: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_21: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_21: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_21: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_21: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_21: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_21: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_21: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_21: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_21: It's much too much.