SPEAKER_09: And after the ox?
SPEAKER_09: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_09: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_09: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_09: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_09: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_09: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_09: Back already?
SPEAKER_09: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_09: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_09: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_09: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_09: Grandpa, where will the chicks live?
SPEAKER_09: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_09: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_09: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_09: Uncle.
SPEAKER_09: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_09: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_09: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_09: Very soon.
SPEAKER_09: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_09: After oxen...
SPEAKER_09: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_09: I want to ride on an ox's back!