SPEAKER_28: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_28: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_28: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_28: What's his name?
SPEAKER_28: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_28: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_28: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_28: from making you go.
SPEAKER_28: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_28: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_28: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_28: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_28: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_28: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_28: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_28: Go away!
SPEAKER_28: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_28: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_28: You killed him.
SPEAKER_28: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_28: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_28: It was the water that did it.