SPEAKER_06: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_06: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_06: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_06: I see your point.
SPEAKER_06: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_06: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_06: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_06: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_06: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_06: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_06: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_06: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_06: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_06: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_06: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_06: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_06: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_06: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_06: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_06: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_06: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: Let's go.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia's about to give birth?