SPEAKER_26: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_26: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_26: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_26: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_26: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_26: Just like me.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_26: wounded me
SPEAKER_26: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_26: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_26: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_26: Enough!
SPEAKER_26: How could you?
SPEAKER_26: What's happened?
SPEAKER_26: Answer me!
SPEAKER_26: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_26: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_26: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_26: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_26: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_26: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_26: Move aside! Stand still!