SPEAKER_25: Of course.
SPEAKER_25: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_25: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_25: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_25: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_25: This is too much.
SPEAKER_25: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_25: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_25: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_25: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_25: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_25: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_25: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_25: You just have to!
SPEAKER_25: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_25: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_25: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_25: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_25: Are they in there?