SPEAKER_15: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_15: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_15: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_15: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_15: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_15: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_15: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_15: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_15: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_15: Well?
SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_15: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_15: Well?
SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_15: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_15: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_15: What is it?
SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_15: Good.
SPEAKER_15: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_15: Okay.