SPEAKER_13: Get out!
SPEAKER_13: I've just...
SPEAKER_13: Let's play!
SPEAKER_13: Go!
SPEAKER_13: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_13: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_13: Sit down.
SPEAKER_13: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_13: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_13: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_13: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_13: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_13: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_13: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_13: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_13: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_13: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_13: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_13: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_13: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_13: Take this.
SPEAKER_13: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_13: How could you?
SPEAKER_13: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_13: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_13: What is this?
SPEAKER_13: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_13: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_13: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_13: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_13: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_13: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_13: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_13: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_13: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_13: Now!
SPEAKER_13: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_13: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_13: Daddy.
SPEAKER_13: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_13: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_13: How dare you!
SPEAKER_13: What's going on?
SPEAKER_13: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_13: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_13: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_13: No!
SPEAKER_13: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_13: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_13: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_13: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_13: Sit down.
SPEAKER_13: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_13: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_13: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_13: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_13: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_13: He was starving.
SPEAKER_13: But he was okay after the water.
SPEAKER_13: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_13: Oxygen.