SPEAKER_09: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_09: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_09: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_09: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_09: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_09: This is too much.
SPEAKER_09: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_09: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_09: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_09: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_09: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_09: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_09: Please come again.
SPEAKER_09: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_09: You just have to!
SPEAKER_09: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_09: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_09: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_09: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_09: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_09: Yes, just gobbled them up.