SPEAKER_29: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_29: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_29: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_29: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_29: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_29: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_29: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_29: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_29: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_29: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_29: from making you go.
SPEAKER_29: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_29: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_29: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him.
SPEAKER_29: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_29: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_29: Very!
SPEAKER_29: What a clever boy!