SPEAKER_24: Take care.
SPEAKER_24: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_24: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_24: Dad!
SPEAKER_24: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_24: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_24: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_24: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_24: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_24: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_24: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_24: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_24: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_24: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_24: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_24: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_24: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_24: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_24: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_24: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_24: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_24: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_24: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_24: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_24: - How is he?
- They're both fine!