SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_19: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_19: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_19: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_19: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_19: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_19: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_19: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_19: What?
SPEAKER_19: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_19: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_19: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_19: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_19: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_19: Fugui...
SPEAKER_19: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_19: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_19: It's money.
SPEAKER_19: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_19: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_19: I will remember.
SPEAKER_19: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_19: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_19: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_19: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_19: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_19: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_19: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_19: Never mind.
SPEAKER_19: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_19: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_19: Fugui!
SPEAKER_19: Who's there?
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: Who?
SPEAKER_19: What do you want?
SPEAKER_19: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_19: Well?
SPEAKER_19: Fugui...
SPEAKER_19: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_19: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_19: Take this...
SPEAKER_19: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_19: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_19: No.
SPEAKER_19: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_19: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_19: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_19: and better get back.
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng, remember...