SPEAKER_05: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_05: How much?
SPEAKER_05: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_05: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_05: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_05: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_05: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_05: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_05: Fugui...
SPEAKER_05: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_05: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_05: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_05: It's settled.
SPEAKER_05: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_05: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_05: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_05: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_05: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_05: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_05: Okay?
SPEAKER_05: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_05: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_05: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_05: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_05: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_05: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_05: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_05: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_05: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_05: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_05: As for me...
SPEAKER_05: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_05: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_05: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_05: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_05: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_05: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_05: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_05: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_05: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_05: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_05: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_05: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_05: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_05: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_05: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_05: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_05: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_05: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_05: They shot him.
SPEAKER_05: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_05: He is dead.
SPEAKER_05: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_05: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_05: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_05: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_05: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_05: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_05: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_05: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_05: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_05: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_05: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_05: come see the show.
SPEAKER_05: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_05: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_05: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_05: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_05: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_05: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_05: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_05: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_05: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_05: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_05: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_05: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_05: When you get there...
SPEAKER_05: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_05: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_05: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_05: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_05: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_05: That's good.
SPEAKER_05: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_05: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_05: Our family...
SPEAKER_05: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_05: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_05: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_05: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_05: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_05: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_05: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_05: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_05: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_05: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_05: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_05: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_05: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_05: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_05: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_05: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_05: From where?
SPEAKER_05: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_05: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_05: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_05: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_05: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_05: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_05: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_05: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_05: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_05: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_05: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_05: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_05: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_05: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_05: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_05: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_05: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_05: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_05: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_05: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_05: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_05: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_05: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_05: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_05: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_05: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_05: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_05: On the mend.
SPEAKER_05: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_05: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_05: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_05: Cheers!
SPEAKER_05: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_05: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_05: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_05: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_05: This is great.
SPEAKER_05: Of course.
SPEAKER_05: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_05: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_05: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_05: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_05: You came for this?
SPEAKER_05: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_05: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_05: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_05: Why?
SPEAKER_05: I don't know.
SPEAKER_05: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_05: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_05: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_05: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_05: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_05: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_05: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_05: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_05: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_05: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_05: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_05: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_05: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_05: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_05: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_05: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_05: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_05: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_05: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_05: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_05: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_05: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_05: He's all right.
SPEAKER_05: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_05: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_05: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_05: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_05: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_05: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_05: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_05: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_05: Help us!
SPEAKER_05: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_05: Quick!
SPEAKER_05: Is it?
SPEAKER_05: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_05: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_05: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_05: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_05: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_05: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_05: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_05: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_05: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_05: How about in here?
SPEAKER_05: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_05: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_05: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_05: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_05: And then...
SPEAKER_05: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_05: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_05: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_05: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...