SPEAKER_11: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_11: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_11: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_11: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_11: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_11: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_11: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_11: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_11: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_11: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_11: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_11: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_11: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_11: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_11: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_11: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_11: The 1940s
SPEAKER_11: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_11: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_11: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_11: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_11: Take that!
SPEAKER_11: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_11: Enough?
SPEAKER_11: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_11: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_11: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_11: Enough?
SPEAKER_11: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_11: Sit here.
SPEAKER_11: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_11: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_11: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_11: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_11: Come over here.
SPEAKER_11: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_11: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_11: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_11: Some years later...