SPEAKER_12: Are you having fun?
SPEAKER_12: More, more, more!
SPEAKER_12: - Are you all right?
- Yes!
SPEAKER_12: Come then, so you can
get some water on you.
SPEAKER_12: It’s August 9, 1996.
SPEAKER_12: Tomorrow is the parade of Silleteros.
Don Carlos Zapata is here with us
SPEAKER_12: who’s going to parade with a
monumental style silleta.
SPEAKER_12: Don Carlos, for how long have you been
participating in the parade?
SPEAKER_12: About ten years now, that I participate
in the parade of Silleteros.
SPEAKER_12: And how many times have you won?
SPEAKER_12: I've only lost twice in ten years.
SPEAKER_12: Because I stopped competing. I've been
the winner for eight years now.
SPEAKER_12: - You stopped competing?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_12: - We wish you good luck for tomorrow.
- Thank you.
SPEAKER_12: Federico.
SPEAKER_12: Federico...
SPEAKER_12: MUTE FIRE