SPEAKER_11: Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_11: No, no. I think it's better alone.
SPEAKER_11: This is the first recorded
game of the Atlético Nacional,
SPEAKER_11: in this filmic document
of the Pelbet company.
SPEAKER_11: We will present indistinctly,
according to journalistic consideration
SPEAKER_11: the main games, the ones
we consider essential
SPEAKER_11: for the conquer of the title of 1981.
SPEAKER_11: The first goal was scored by
Victor Luna and Guillermo La Rosa
SPEAKER_11: from the midfield, inside the area
SPEAKER_11: so that he can be, as
usually, close to the goal.
SPEAKER_11: But let’s have a look
from the reverse angle.
SPEAKER_11: The one from the cameras at the other side
of the goal, placed by Pelbet’s company.
SPEAKER_11: Look at that karate blow from Gonzalez
Aquino to the peruvian Cesar Cueto.
SPEAKER_11: About ten years now, that I participate
in the parade of Silleteros.