SPEAKER_21: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_21: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_21: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_21: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_21: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_21: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_21: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_21: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_21: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_21: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_21: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_21: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_21: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_21: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_21: The day...
SPEAKER_21: Written?
SPEAKER_21: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_21: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_21: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_21: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_21: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_21: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_21: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_21: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_21: Wake up.
SPEAKER_21: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_21: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_21: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_21: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_21: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_21: that we could...
SPEAKER_21: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_21: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_21: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_21: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_21: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_21: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_21: He can run?
SPEAKER_21: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_21: I approve.
SPEAKER_21: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_21: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_21: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_21: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_21: They did.
SPEAKER_21: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_21: No doctors?
SPEAKER_21: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_21: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_21: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_21: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_21: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_21: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_21: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_21: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_21: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_21: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_21: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_21: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_21: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_21: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_21: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_21: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_21: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_21: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_21: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_21: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_21: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_21: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_21: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_21: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_21: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_21: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_21: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_21: and life will get better and better.