SPEAKER_11: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_11: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_11: Look at this.
SPEAKER_11: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_11: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_11: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_11: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_11: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_11: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_11: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_11: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_11: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_11: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_11: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_11: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_11: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_11: It's all here?
SPEAKER_11: Keep these.
SPEAKER_11: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_11: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_11: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_11: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_11: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_11: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_11: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_11: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_11: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_11: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_11: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_11: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_11: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_11: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_11: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_11: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_11: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_11: Take that!
SPEAKER_11: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_11: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_11: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_11: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_11: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_11: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_11: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_11: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_11: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_11: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_11: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_11: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_11: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_11: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_11: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_11: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_11: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_11: Fugui...
SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_11: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_11: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_11: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_11: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_11: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_11: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_11: What's happened?
SPEAKER_11: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_11: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_11: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_11: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_11: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_11: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_11: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_11: I wouldn't dare.