SPEAKER_07: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_07: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_07: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_07: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_07: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_07: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_07: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_07: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_07: You're up.
SPEAKER_07: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_07: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_07: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_07: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_07: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_07: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_07: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_07: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_07: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_07: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_07: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_07: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_07: Landlords?
SPEAKER_07: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_07: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_07: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_07: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_07: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_07: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_07: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_07: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_07: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_07: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_07: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_07: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_07: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_07: How so?
SPEAKER_07: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_07: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_07: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_07: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_07: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_07: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_07: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_07: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_07: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_07: Daddy.
SPEAKER_07: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_07: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_07: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_07: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_07: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_07: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_07: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_07: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_07: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_07: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_07: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_07: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_07: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_07: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_07: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_07: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_07: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_07: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_07: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_07: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_07: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_07: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_07: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_07: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_07: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_07: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_07: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_07: Is it?
SPEAKER_07: Take the medicine to Granny.