SPEAKER_32: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_32: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_32: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_32: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_32: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_32: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_32: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_32: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_32: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_32: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_32: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_32: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_32: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_32: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_32: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_32: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_32: The 1940s
SPEAKER_32: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_32: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_32: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_32: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_32: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_32: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_32: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_32: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_32: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_32: Enough?
SPEAKER_32: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_32: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_32: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_32: Sit here.
SPEAKER_32: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_32: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_32: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_32: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_32: Come over here.
SPEAKER_32: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_32: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_32: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_32: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_32: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_32: Some years later...