SPEAKER_25: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_25: Take care.
SPEAKER_25: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_25: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_25: Dad!
SPEAKER_25: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_25: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_25: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_25: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_25: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_25: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_25: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_25: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_25: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_25: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_25: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_25: Please come again.
SPEAKER_25: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_25: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_25: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_25: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_25: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_25: Yes, 7.9 pounds!