SPEAKER_02: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_02: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_02: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_02: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_02: and after that...
SPEAKER_02: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_02: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_02: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_02: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_02: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_02: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_02: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_02: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_02: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_02: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_02: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_02: You cold?
SPEAKER_02: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_02: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_02: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_02: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_02: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_02: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_02: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_02: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_02: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_02: Yes.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_02: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_02: When is it due?
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_02: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_02: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_02: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_02: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_02: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_02: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_02: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_02: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_02: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_02: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_02: Uncle.
SPEAKER_02: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.