SPEAKER_15: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_15: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_15: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_15: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_15: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_15: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_15: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_15: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_15: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_15: How could that be?
SPEAKER_15: So, no running?
SPEAKER_15: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_15: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_15: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_15: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_15: Let her go!
SPEAKER_15: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_15: We must be going.
SPEAKER_15: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_15: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_15: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_15: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_15: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_15: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_15: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_15: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_15: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_15: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_15: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_15: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_15: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_15: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_15: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_15: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_15: Careful! Don't drop them!