SPEAKER_04: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_04: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_04: Look at this.
SPEAKER_04: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_04: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_04: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_04: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_04: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_04: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_04: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_04: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_04: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_04: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_04: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_04: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_04: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_04: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_04: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_04: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_04: It's all here?
SPEAKER_04: Keep these.
SPEAKER_04: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_04: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_04: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_04: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_04: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_04: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_04: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_04: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_04: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_04: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_04: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_04: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_04: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_04: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_04: I see your point.
SPEAKER_04: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_04: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_04: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_04: Take that!
SPEAKER_04: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_04: Enough?
SPEAKER_04: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_04: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_04: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_04: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_04: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_04: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_04: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_04: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_04: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_04: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_04: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_04: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_04: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_04: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_04: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_04: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_04: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui...
SPEAKER_04: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_04: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_04: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_04: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_04: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_04: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_04: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_04: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_04: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_04: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_04: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_04: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_04: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_04: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_04: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_04: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_04: Let's go.
SPEAKER_04: What do you think?
SPEAKER_04: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_04: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_04: What's happened?
SPEAKER_04: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_04: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_04: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_04: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_04: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_04: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.