SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_20: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_20: You're up.
SPEAKER_20: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_20: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_20: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_20: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_20: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_20: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_20: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_20: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_20: What?
SPEAKER_20: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_20: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_20: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_20: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_20: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_20: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_20: It's money.
SPEAKER_20: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_20: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_20: I will remember.
SPEAKER_20: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_20: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_20: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_20: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_20: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_20: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_20: Never mind.
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_20: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui!
SPEAKER_20: Who's there?
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_20: Who?
SPEAKER_20: What do you want?
SPEAKER_20: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_20: Well?
SPEAKER_20: Fugui...
SPEAKER_20: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_20: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_20: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_20: Take this...
SPEAKER_20: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_20: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_20: No.
SPEAKER_20: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_20: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_20: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_20: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_20: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_20: and better get back.
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng, remember...