SPEAKER_10: Are you having fun?
SPEAKER_10: More, more, more!
SPEAKER_10: - Are you all right?
- Yes!
SPEAKER_10: Come then, so you can
get some water on you.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ I can't deny it, I was
scared to confess to you
SPEAKER_10: ♪ how I would adore you.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ You looked at me, and I stared at you.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Until one day, we finally
understood each other.
SPEAKER_10: ♪ Who could imagine that then
our children would come
SPEAKER_10: ♪ To bring joy to this
place for all eternity.
SPEAKER_10: It’s August 9, 1996.
SPEAKER_10: Tomorrow is the parade of Silleteros.
Don Carlos Zapata is here with us
SPEAKER_10: who’s going to parade with a
monumental style silleta.
SPEAKER_10: Don Carlos, for how long have you been
participating in the parade?
SPEAKER_10: About ten years now, that I participate
in the parade of Silleteros.
SPEAKER_10: And how many times have you won?
SPEAKER_10: I've only lost twice in ten years.
SPEAKER_10: Because I stopped competing. I've been
the winner for eight years now.
SPEAKER_10: - You stopped competing?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_10: - We wish you good luck for tomorrow.
- Thank you.
SPEAKER_10: Federico.
SPEAKER_10: Federico...
SPEAKER_10: MUTE FIRE