SPEAKER_07: The strange thing was that I didn’t
notice her as worried as I was.
SPEAKER_07: If I wake up mute I would
probably go crazy.
SPEAKER_07: I noticed it was an attitude
that she was assuming.
SPEAKER_07: I could never knew if was just
in front of me or everyone
SPEAKER_07: or facing life.
SPEAKER_07: Maybe she was punishing us all.
SPEAKER_07: But then she stopped speaking.
SPEAKER_07: I don’t think she can’t speak,
I think that she has decided not to speak.
SPEAKER_07: And I think it’s a voluntary decision.
SPEAKER_07: I thought, however, that it
could be a medical issue.
SPEAKER_07: We took her to the doctor
SPEAKER_07: I talked to Héctor, to César
and to other people.
SPEAKER_07: To everyone I thought could know.
SPEAKER_07: They all came to the
same conclusion:
SPEAKER_07: Aracelly's problem
is inexplicable.
SPEAKER_07: It’s not physiological, and it
doesn’t seem psychological either.
SPEAKER_07: Always, always, always, I think
that she always understands us.
SPEAKER_07: She hasn't lost the
capacity of understanding
SPEAKER_07: nor has she lost any
other kind of routines.
SPEAKER_07: She reads, she walks, she thinks,
SPEAKER_07: she insinuates, she takes initiatives.
SPEAKER_07: I think that she is taking somehow revenge.
SPEAKER_07: And I think that, somehow, what she’s pretending
is to make life unbearable to everyone.
SPEAKER_07: If that’s the case, she
should have said it,
SPEAKER_07: and it would have been better
SPEAKER_07: that we would just
have ended everything.
SPEAKER_07: I think that families begin
SPEAKER_07: and families dissolve, families
should not self-destruct.
SPEAKER_07: I think we never talked enough about love.
SPEAKER_07: Because if we had talked
enough about love
SPEAKER_07: we would have understood
it from the beginning.
SPEAKER_07: Love is born, it grows and it
dies like everything in nature.
SPEAKER_07: I believe that the academic attitude is not
only repeating texts in the universities
SPEAKER_07: but to live academically,
and that we have lacked.