SPEAKER_11: ♪ With justice and truth
next to the people it is
SPEAKER_11: ♪ with the first fire of the dawn
SPEAKER_11: ♪ of struggle and future.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ With Bolivar, Galán already rode again.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ No more weeping and pain of the homeland.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ We are people who go after freedom
SPEAKER_11: ♪ building the path of peace.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
SPEAKER_11: ♪ for the fatherland,
the people and the bread.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
SPEAKER_11: ♪ to achieve freedom.
SPEAKER_11: ♪ Guerrilla of the FARC
with the people to triumph
SPEAKER_11: ♪ Guerilla of the FARC,
with the voice of unity
SPEAKER_11: ♪ to achieve freedom.