SPEAKER_02: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_02: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_02: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_02: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_02: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_02: Please.
SPEAKER_02: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_02: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_02: Tell me.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_02: Come home.
SPEAKER_02: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_02: I've realized...
SPEAKER_02: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_02: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_02: Granny!
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_02: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_02: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_02: Me.
SPEAKER_02: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_02: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_02: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_02: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_02: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_02: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_02: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_02: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_02: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_02: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_02: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_02: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_02: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_02: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_02: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_02: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_02: You should have written.
SPEAKER_02: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_02: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_02: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_02: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_02: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_02: They never get...
SPEAKER_02: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_02: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_02: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_02: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_02: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_02: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_02: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_02: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_02: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_02: They shot him.
SPEAKER_02: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_02: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_02: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_02: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_02: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_02: Of course.
SPEAKER_02: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_02: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_02: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_02: Good idea!
SPEAKER_02: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_02: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_02: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_02: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_02: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_02: How so?
SPEAKER_02: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_02: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_02: What do you know?
SPEAKER_02: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_02: Well?
SPEAKER_02: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_02: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_02: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_02: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_02: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_02: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_02: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_02: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_02: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_02: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_02: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_02: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_02: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_02: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_02: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_02: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_02: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_02: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_02: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_02: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_02: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_02: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_02: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_02: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_02: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_02: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_02: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_02: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_02: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_02: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_02: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_02: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_02: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_02: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_02: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_02: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_02: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_02: A good family.
SPEAKER_02: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_02: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_02: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_02: No, really.
SPEAKER_02: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_02: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_02: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_02: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_02: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_02: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_02: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_02: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_02: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_02: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_02: We approve.
SPEAKER_02: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_02: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_02: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_02: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_02: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_02: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_02: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_02: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_02: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_02: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_02: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_02: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_02: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_02: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_02: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_02: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_02: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_02: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_02: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_02: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_02: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_02: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_02: Come inside.
SPEAKER_02: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_02: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_02: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_02: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_02: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_02: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_02: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_02: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_02: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_02: Go ask.
SPEAKER_02: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_02: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_02: Want one?
SPEAKER_02: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_02: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_02: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_02: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_02: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_02: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_02: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_02: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_02: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_02: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_02: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_02: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_02: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_02: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_02: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_02: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_02: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_02: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_02: What's with him?
SPEAKER_02: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_02: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_02: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_02: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_02: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_02: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_02: to show her.
SPEAKER_02: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_02: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_02: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_02: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_02: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_02: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_02: You will ride on an ox's back.