SPEAKER_26: Of course.
SPEAKER_26: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_26: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_26: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_26: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_26: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_26: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_26: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_26: This is too much.
SPEAKER_26: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_26: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_26: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_26: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_26: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_26: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_26: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_26: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_26: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_26: Please come again.
SPEAKER_26: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_26: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_26: You just have to!
SPEAKER_26: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_26: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_26: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_26: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_26: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_26: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_26: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_26: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_26: Yes, just gobbled them up.