SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_16: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_16: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_16: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_16: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_16: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_16: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_16: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_16: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_16: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_16: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_16: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_16: So, no running?
SPEAKER_16: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_16: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_16: Let her go!
SPEAKER_16: We must be going.
SPEAKER_16: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_16: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_16: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_16: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_16: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_16: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_16: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_16: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_16: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_16: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_16: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_16: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_16: It's okay.
SPEAKER_16: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_16: anything made from wheat.