SPEAKER_25: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_25: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_25: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_25: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_25: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_25: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_25: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_25: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_25: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_25: Just like me.
SPEAKER_25: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_25: You won't go?
SPEAKER_25: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_25: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_25: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_25: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_25: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_25: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_25: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_25: Daddy.
SPEAKER_25: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_25: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_25: What's happened?
SPEAKER_25: Answer me!
SPEAKER_25: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_25: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_25: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_25: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_25: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_25: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_25: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_25: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_25: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_25: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_25: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_25: What do you mean?