SPEAKER_14: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_14: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_14: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_14: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_14: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_14: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_14: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_14: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_14: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_14: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_14: Well?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_14: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: Well?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_14: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_14: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_14: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_14: What is it?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_14: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_14: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_14: Good.
SPEAKER_14: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_14: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_14: This is great.
SPEAKER_14: Okay.