SPEAKER_13: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_13: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_13: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_13: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_13: You're up.
SPEAKER_13: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_13: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_13: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_13: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_13: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_13: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_13: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_13: Fugui...
SPEAKER_13: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_13: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_13: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_13: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_13: It's settled.
SPEAKER_13: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_13: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_13: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_13: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_13: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_13: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_13: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_13: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_13: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_13: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_13: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_13: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_13: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_13: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_13: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_13: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_13: As for me...
SPEAKER_13: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_13: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_13: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_13: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_13: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_13: Fugui...
SPEAKER_13: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_13: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_13: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_13: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_13: The day...
SPEAKER_13: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_13: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_13: Written?
SPEAKER_13: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_13: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_13: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_13: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_13: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_13: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_13: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_13: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_13: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_13: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_13: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_13: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_13: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_13: He is dead.
SPEAKER_13: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_13: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_13: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_13: Landlords?
SPEAKER_13: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_13: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_13: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_13: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_13: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_13: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_13: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_13: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_13: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_13: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_13: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_13: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_13: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_13: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_13: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_13: Wake up.
SPEAKER_13: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_13: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_13: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_13: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_13: When you get there...
SPEAKER_13: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_13: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_13: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_13: That's good.
SPEAKER_13: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_13: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_13: Our family...
SPEAKER_13: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_13: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_13: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_13: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_13: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_13: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_13: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_13: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_13: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_13: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_13: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_13: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_13: that we could...
SPEAKER_13: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_13: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_13: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_13: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_13: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_13: He can run?
SPEAKER_13: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_13: I approve.
SPEAKER_13: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_13: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_13: From where?
SPEAKER_13: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_13: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_13: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_13: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_13: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_13: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_13: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_13: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_13: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_13: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_13: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_13: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_13: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_13: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_13: On the mend.
SPEAKER_13: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_13: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_13: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_13: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_13: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_13: Of course.
SPEAKER_13: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_13: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_13: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_13: You came for this?
SPEAKER_13: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_13: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_13: Why?
SPEAKER_13: I don't know.
SPEAKER_13: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_13: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_13: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_13: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_13: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_13: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_13: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_13: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_13: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_13: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_13: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_13: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_13: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_13: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_13: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_13: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_13: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_13: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_13: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_13: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_13: They did.
SPEAKER_13: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_13: No.
SPEAKER_13: No doctors?
SPEAKER_13: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_13: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_13: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_13: He's all right.
SPEAKER_13: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_13: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_13: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_13: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_13: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_13: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_13: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_13: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_13: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_13: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_13: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_13: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_13: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_13: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_13: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_13: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_13: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_13: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_13: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_13: Help us!
SPEAKER_13: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_13: Quick!
SPEAKER_13: Is it?
SPEAKER_13: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_13: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_13: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_13: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_13: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_13: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_13: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_13: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_13: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_13: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_13: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_13: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_13: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_13: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_13: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_13: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_13: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_13: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_13: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_13: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_13: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_13: How about in here?
SPEAKER_13: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_13: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_13: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_13: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_13: And then...
SPEAKER_13: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_13: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_13: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_13: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_13: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_13: and life will get better and better.