SPEAKER_10: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_10: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_10: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_10: want more time
SPEAKER_10: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_10: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_10: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_10: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_10: Come out!
SPEAKER_10: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_10: wounded me
SPEAKER_10: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_10: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_10: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_10: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_10: Take that!
SPEAKER_10: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_10: Enough?
SPEAKER_10: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_10: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_10: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_10: What's up?
SPEAKER_10: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_10: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_10: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_10: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_10: Don't move.
SPEAKER_10: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_10: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_10: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_10: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_10: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_10: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_10: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_10: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_10: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_10: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_10: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_10: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?