SPEAKER_07: Besides...
SPEAKER_07: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_07: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_07: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_07: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_07: As for me...
SPEAKER_07: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_07: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_07: The wounded.
SPEAKER_07: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_07: No one's left.
SPEAKER_07: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_07: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_07: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_07: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_07: Who?
SPEAKER_07: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_07: Well?
SPEAKER_07: Fugui...
SPEAKER_07: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_07: Take this...
SPEAKER_07: and my heart will be at ease.