SPEAKER_23: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_23: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui...
SPEAKER_23: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_23: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_23: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_23: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_23: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_23: You're here.
SPEAKER_23: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_23: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_23: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_23: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_23: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_23: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_23: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_23: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_23: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_23: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_23: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_23: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_23: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_23: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_23: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_23: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_23: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_23: from making you go.
SPEAKER_23: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_23: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_23: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_23: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_23: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_23: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_23: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_23: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_23: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_23: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_23: Go away!
SPEAKER_23: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_23: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_23: You killed him.
SPEAKER_23: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_23: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_23: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_23: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_23: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_23: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_23: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_23: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_23: Very!
SPEAKER_23: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_23: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_23: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_23: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_23: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_23: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_23: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_23: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_23: What a food bill he must have.