SPEAKER_24: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_24: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_24: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_24: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_24: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_24: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_24: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_24: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_24: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_24: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_24: Well?
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_24: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_24: Well?
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_24: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_24: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_24: What is it?
SPEAKER_24: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_24: Okay?
SPEAKER_24: Written?
SPEAKER_24: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_24: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_24: Good.
SPEAKER_24: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_24: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_24: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_24: Come on in!
SPEAKER_24: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_24: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_24: Okay.
SPEAKER_24: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_24: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_24: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_24: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_24: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_24: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_24: Little Bun, behave yourself.