SPEAKER_22: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_22: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_22: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_22: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_22: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_22: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_22: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_22: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_22: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_22: Just like me.
SPEAKER_22: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_22: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_22: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_22: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_22: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_22: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_22: What's happened?
SPEAKER_22: Answer me!
SPEAKER_22: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_22: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_22: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_22: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_22: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_22: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_22: Where's Erxi?