SPEAKER_13: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_13: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_13: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_13: want more time
SPEAKER_13: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_13: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_13: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_13: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_13: Come out!
SPEAKER_13: It's ready.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_13: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_13: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_13: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_13: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_13: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_13: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_13: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_13: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_13: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_13: The only child I have left.