SPEAKER_03: Let's play!
SPEAKER_03: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_03: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_03: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_03: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_03: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_03: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_03: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_03: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_03: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_03: This is too much.
SPEAKER_03: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_03: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_03: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_03: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_03: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_03: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_03: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_03: From where?
SPEAKER_03: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_03: Cheers!
SPEAKER_03: You just have to!
SPEAKER_03: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_03: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_03: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_03: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_03: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_03: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_03: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_03: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_03: Take the medicine to Granny.