SPEAKER_10: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_10: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_10: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_10: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_10: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_10: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_10: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_10: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_10: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_10: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_10: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_10: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_10: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_10: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_10: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_10: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_10: The 1940s
SPEAKER_10: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_10: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_10: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_10: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_10: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_10: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_10: Enough?
SPEAKER_10: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_10: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_10: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_10: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_10: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_10: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_10: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_10: Sit here.
SPEAKER_10: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_10: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_10: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_10: No doctors?
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_10: Some years later...