SPEAKER_11: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_11: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_11: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_11: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_11: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_11: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_11: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_11: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_11: What's up?
SPEAKER_11: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_11: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_11: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_11: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_11: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_11: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_11: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_11: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_11: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_11: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_11: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_11: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_11: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_11: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_11: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_11: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_11: Don't move.
SPEAKER_11: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_11: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_11: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_11: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_11: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_11: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_11: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_11: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_11: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_11: He'll know.
SPEAKER_11: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_11: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_11: Back already?
SPEAKER_11: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_11: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_11: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_11: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_11: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_11: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_11: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_11: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_11: Very soon.
SPEAKER_11: And then?
SPEAKER_11: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_11: After oxen...
SPEAKER_11: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_11: I want to ride on an ox's back!