SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_16: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_16: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_16: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_16: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_16: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_16: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_16: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_16: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_16: What?
SPEAKER_16: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_16: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_16: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui...
SPEAKER_16: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_16: Tired?
SPEAKER_16: Fugui!
SPEAKER_16: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_16: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_16: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_16: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui...
SPEAKER_16: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_16: It's money.
SPEAKER_16: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_16: I will remember.
SPEAKER_16: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_16: Let's go.
SPEAKER_16: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_16: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_16: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_16: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_16: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_16: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_16: Never mind.
SPEAKER_16: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_16: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_16: Fugui!
SPEAKER_16: Who's there?
SPEAKER_16: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_16: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_16: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_16: No.
SPEAKER_16: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_16: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_16: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_16: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_16: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_16: and better get back.
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng, remember...
SPEAKER_16: Okay, we're going.