SPEAKER_14: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_14: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_14: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_14: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_14: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_14: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_14: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_14: How could that be?
SPEAKER_14: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_14: Home!
SPEAKER_14: Home?
SPEAKER_14: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_14: Run now...
SPEAKER_14: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_14: That's right.
SPEAKER_14: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_14: How?
SPEAKER_14: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_14: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_14: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_14: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_14: The coat's from my brother's unit.