SPEAKER_02: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_02: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_02: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_02: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_02: You're up.
SPEAKER_02: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_02: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_02: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_02: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_02: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_02: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_02: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_02: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui...
SPEAKER_02: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_02: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_02: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_02: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_02: Please.
SPEAKER_02: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_02: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_02: Tell me.
SPEAKER_02: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_02: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_02: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_02: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_02: It's settled.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_02: Come home.
SPEAKER_02: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_02: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_02: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_02: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_02: What's his name?
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_02: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_02: Me.
SPEAKER_02: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_02: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_02: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_02: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_02: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_02: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_02: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_02: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_02: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_02: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_02: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_02: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_02: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_02: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_02: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_02: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_02: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_02: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_02: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_02: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_02: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_02: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_02: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_02: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_02: As for me...
SPEAKER_02: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_02: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_02: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_02: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_02: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_02: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_02: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_02: The day...
SPEAKER_02: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_02: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_02: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_02: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_02: You should have written.
SPEAKER_02: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_02: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_02: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_02: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_02: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_02: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_02: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_02: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_02: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_02: They never get...
SPEAKER_02: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_02: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_02: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_02: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_02: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_02: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_02: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_02: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_02: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_02: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_02: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_02: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_02: Look at this.
SPEAKER_02: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_02: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_02: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_02: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_02: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_02: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_02: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_02: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_02: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_02: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_02: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_02: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_02: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_02: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_02: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_02: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_02: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_02: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_02: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_02: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_02: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_02: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_02: They shot him.
SPEAKER_02: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_02: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_02: He is dead.
SPEAKER_02: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_02: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_02: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_02: Landlords?
SPEAKER_02: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_02: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_02: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_02: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_02: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_02: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_02: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_02: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_02: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_02: Of course.
SPEAKER_02: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_02: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_02: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_02: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_02: Good idea!
SPEAKER_02: It's all here?
SPEAKER_02: Keep these.
SPEAKER_02: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_02: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_02: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_02: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_02: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_02: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_02: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_02: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_02: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_02: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_02: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_02: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_02: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_02: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_02: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_02: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_02: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_02: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_02: and after that...
SPEAKER_02: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_02: I see your point.
SPEAKER_02: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_02: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_02: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_02: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_02: Take that!
SPEAKER_02: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_02: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_02: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_02: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_02: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_02: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_02: How so?
SPEAKER_02: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_02: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_02: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_02: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_02: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_02: What do you know?
SPEAKER_02: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_02: Well?
SPEAKER_02: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_02: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_02: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_02: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_02: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_02: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_02: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_02: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_02: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_02: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_02: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_02: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_02: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_02: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_02: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_02: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_02: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_02: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_02: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_02: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_02: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_02: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_02: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_02: Wake up.
SPEAKER_02: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_02: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_02: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_02: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_02: When you get there...
SPEAKER_02: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_02: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_02: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_02: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_02: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_02: That's good.
SPEAKER_02: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_02: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_02: Our family...
SPEAKER_02: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_02: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_02: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_02: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_02: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_02: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_02: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_02: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_02: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_02: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_02: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_02: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_02: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_02: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_02: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_02: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_02: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_02: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_02: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_02: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_02: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_02: that we could...
SPEAKER_02: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_02: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_02: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_02: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_02: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_02: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_02: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_02: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_02: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_02: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_02: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_02: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui...
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_02: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_02: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_02: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_02: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_02: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_02: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_02: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_02: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_02: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_02: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_02: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_02: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_02: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_02: He can run?
SPEAKER_02: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_02: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_02: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_02: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_02: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_02: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_02: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_02: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_02: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_02: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_02: A good family.
SPEAKER_02: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_02: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_02: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_02: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_02: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_02: No, really.
SPEAKER_02: What do you think?
SPEAKER_02: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_02: I approve.
SPEAKER_02: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_02: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_02: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_02: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_02: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_02: A cripple?
SPEAKER_02: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_02: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_02: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_02: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_02: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_02: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_02: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_02: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_02: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_02: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_02: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_02: We approve.
SPEAKER_02: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_02: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_02: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_02: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_02: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_02: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_02: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_02: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_02: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_02: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_02: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_02: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_02: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_02: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_02: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_02: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_02: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_02: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_02: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_02: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_02: On the mend.
SPEAKER_02: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_02: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_02: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_02: Really?
SPEAKER_02: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_02: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_02: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_02: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_02: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_02: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_02: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_02: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_02: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_02: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_02: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_02: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_02: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_02: This is great.
SPEAKER_02: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_02: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_02: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_02: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_02: Of course.
SPEAKER_02: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_02: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_02: You came for this?
SPEAKER_02: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_02: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_02: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_02: Why?
SPEAKER_02: I don't know.
SPEAKER_02: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_02: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_02: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_02: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_02: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_02: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_02: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_02: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_02: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_02: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_02: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_02: Come inside.
SPEAKER_02: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_02: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_02: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_02: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_02: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_02: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_02: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_02: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_02: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_02: What's happened?
SPEAKER_02: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_02: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_02: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_02: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_02: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_02: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_02: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_02: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_02: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_02: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_02: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_02: When is it due?
SPEAKER_02: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_02: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_02: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: They did.
SPEAKER_02: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_02: No.
SPEAKER_02: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_02: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_02: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_02: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_02: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_02: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_02: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_02: I wouldn't dare.
SPEAKER_02: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_02: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_02: Go ask.
SPEAKER_02: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_02: He's all right.
SPEAKER_02: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_02: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_02: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_02: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_02: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_02: Want one?
SPEAKER_02: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_02: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_02: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_02: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_02: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_02: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_02: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_02: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_02: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_02: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_02: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_02: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_02: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_02: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_02: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_02: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_02: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_02: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_02: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_02: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_02: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_02: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_02: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_02: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_02: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_02: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_02: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_02: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_02: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_02: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_02: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_02: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_02: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_02: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_02: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_02: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_02: Help us!
SPEAKER_02: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_02: Quick!
SPEAKER_02: Is it?
SPEAKER_02: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_02: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_02: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_02: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_02: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_02: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_02: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_02: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_02: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_02: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_02: to show her.
SPEAKER_02: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_02: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_02: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_02: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_02: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_02: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_02: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_02: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_02: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_02: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_02: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_02: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_02: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_02: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_02: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_02: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_02: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_02: Let's see.
SPEAKER_02: How about in here?
SPEAKER_02: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_02: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_02: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_02: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_02: And then...
SPEAKER_02: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_02: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_02: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_02: You will ride on an ox's back.
SPEAKER_02: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_02: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_02: and life will get better and better.