SPEAKER_17: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_17: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_17: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_17: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_17: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_17: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_17: How could that be?
SPEAKER_17: So, no running?
SPEAKER_17: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_17: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_17: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_17: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_17: We must be going.
SPEAKER_17: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_17: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_17: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_17: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_17: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_17: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_17: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_17: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_17: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_17: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_17: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_17: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_17: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_17: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_17: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_17: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_17: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_17: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_17: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_17: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_17: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_17: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_17: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_17: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_17: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_17: Have some water.
SPEAKER_17: It's okay.
SPEAKER_17: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_17: anything made from wheat.