SPEAKER_22: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_22: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_22: As for me...
SPEAKER_22: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_22: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_22: The day...
SPEAKER_22: Written?
SPEAKER_22: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_22: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_22: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_22: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_22: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_22: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_22: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_22: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_22: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_22: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_22: that we could...
SPEAKER_22: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_22: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_22: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_22: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_22: He can run?
SPEAKER_22: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_22: I approve.
SPEAKER_22: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_22: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_22: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_22: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_22: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_22: They did.
SPEAKER_22: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_22: No doctors?
SPEAKER_22: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_22: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_22: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_22: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_22: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_22: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_22: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_22: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_22: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_22: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_22: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_22: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_22: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_22: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_22: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_22: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_22: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_22: Rice costs more than wheat.