SPEAKER_04: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_04: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_04: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_04: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_04: I see your point.
SPEAKER_04: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_04: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_04: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_04: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_04: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_04: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_04: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_04: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_04: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_04: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_04: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_04: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_04: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_04: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_04: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_04: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_04: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_04: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_04: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_04: No, really.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_04: Time does fly!