SPEAKER_06: Mr. Xie...
SPEAKER_06: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_06: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_06: Look at this.
SPEAKER_06: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_06: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_06: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_06: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_06: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_06: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_06: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_06: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_06: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_06: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_06: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_06: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_06: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_06: It's all here?
SPEAKER_06: Keep these.
SPEAKER_06: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_06: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_06: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_06: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_06: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_06: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_06: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_06: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_06: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_06: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_06: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_06: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_06: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_06: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_06: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_06: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_06: Take that!
SPEAKER_06: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_06: Enough?
SPEAKER_06: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_06: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_06: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_06: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_06: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_06: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_06: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_06: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_06: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_06: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_06: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_06: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_06: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_06: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_06: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_06: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_06: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_06: Fugui...
SPEAKER_06: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_06: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_06: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_06: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_06: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_06: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_06: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_06: What's happened?
SPEAKER_06: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_06: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_06: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_06: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_06: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_06: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_06: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_06: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_06: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_06: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_06: I wouldn't dare.