SPEAKER_09: Get out!
SPEAKER_09: I've just...
SPEAKER_09: Let's play!
SPEAKER_09: Go!
SPEAKER_09: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_09: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_09: Sit down.
SPEAKER_09: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_09: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_09: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_09: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_09: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_09: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_09: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_09: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_09: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_09: Take this.
SPEAKER_09: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_09: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_09: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_09: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_09: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_09: How could you?
SPEAKER_09: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_09: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_09: What is this?
SPEAKER_09: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_09: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_09: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_09: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_09: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_09: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_09: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_09: Now!
SPEAKER_09: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_09: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_09: Go away!
SPEAKER_09: All right.
SPEAKER_09: I'm going.
SPEAKER_09: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_09: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_09: How dare you!
SPEAKER_09: What's going on?
SPEAKER_09: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_09: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_09: Let her go!
SPEAKER_09: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_09: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_09: No!
SPEAKER_09: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_09: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_09: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_09: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_09: Sit down.
SPEAKER_09: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_09: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_09: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_09: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_09: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_09: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_09: He was starving.
SPEAKER_09: But he was okay after the water.
SPEAKER_09: Oxygen.