SPEAKER_02: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_02: How much?
SPEAKER_02: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_02: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_02: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_02: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_02: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_02: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_02: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_02: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_02: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui...
SPEAKER_02: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_02: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_02: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_02: It's settled.
SPEAKER_02: Of course.
SPEAKER_02: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_02: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_02: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_02: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_02: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_02: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_02: Okay?
SPEAKER_02: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_02: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_02: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_02: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_02: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_02: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_02: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_02: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_02: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_02: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_02: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_02: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_02: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_02: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_02: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_02: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_02: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_02: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_02: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_02: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_02: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_02: They shot him.
SPEAKER_02: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_02: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_02: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_02: come see the show.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_02: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_02: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_02: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_02: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_02: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_02: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_02: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_02: When you get there...
SPEAKER_02: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_02: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_02: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_02: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_02: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_02: That's good.
SPEAKER_02: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_02: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_02: Our family...
SPEAKER_02: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_02: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_02: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_02: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_02: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_02: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_02: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_02: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_02: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_02: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_02: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_02: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_02: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_02: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_02: From where?
SPEAKER_02: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_02: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_02: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_02: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_02: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_02: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_02: We approve.
SPEAKER_02: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_02: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_02: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_02: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_02: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_02: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_02: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_02: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_02: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_02: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_02: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_02: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_02: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_02: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_02: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_02: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_02: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_02: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_02: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_02: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_02: On the mend.
SPEAKER_02: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_02: Really?
SPEAKER_02: Cheers!
SPEAKER_02: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_02: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_02: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_02: This is great.
SPEAKER_02: Of course.
SPEAKER_02: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_02: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_02: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_02: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_02: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_02: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_02: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_02: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_02: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_02: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_02: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_02: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_02: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_02: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_02: He's all right.
SPEAKER_02: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_02: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_02: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_02: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_02: Good idea.
SPEAKER_02: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_02: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_02: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_02: Help us!
SPEAKER_02: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_02: Quick!
SPEAKER_02: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_02: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_02: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_02: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_02: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_02: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_02: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_02: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_02: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_02: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_02: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_02: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_02: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_02: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_02: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...