SPEAKER_11: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_11: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_11: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_11: want more time
SPEAKER_11: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_11: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_11: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_11: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_11: Come out!
SPEAKER_11: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_11: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_11: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_11: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_11: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_11: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_11: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_11: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_11: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_11: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_11: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_11: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_11: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_11: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_11: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_11: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_11: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_11: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_11: The only child I have left.