SPEAKER_03: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_03: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_03: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_03: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_03: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_03: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_03: Please.
SPEAKER_03: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_03: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_03: Tell me.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_03: Come home.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui...
SPEAKER_03: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_03: I've realized...
SPEAKER_03: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_03: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_03: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_03: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_03: Granny!
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_03: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_03: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_03: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_03: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_03: Me.
SPEAKER_03: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_03: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_03: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_03: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_03: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_03: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_03: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_03: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_03: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_03: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_03: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_03: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_03: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_03: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_03: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_03: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_03: You should have written.
SPEAKER_03: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_03: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_03: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_03: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_03: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_03: They never get...
SPEAKER_03: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_03: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_03: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_03: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_03: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_03: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_03: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_03: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_03: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_03: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_03: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_03: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_03: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_03: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_03: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_03: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_03: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_03: Of course.
SPEAKER_03: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_03: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_03: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_03: Good idea!
SPEAKER_03: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_03: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_03: and after that...
SPEAKER_03: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_03: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_03: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_03: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_03: What do you know?
SPEAKER_03: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_03: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_03: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_03: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_03: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_03: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_03: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_03: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_03: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_03: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_03: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_03: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_03: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_03: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_03: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_03: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_03: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_03: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_03: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_03: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_03: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_03: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_03: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_03: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_03: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_03: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_03: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_03: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_03: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_03: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_03: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_03: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_03: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_03: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_03: A good family.
SPEAKER_03: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_03: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_03: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: What do you think?
SPEAKER_03: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_03: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_03: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_03: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_03: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_03: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_03: A cripple?
SPEAKER_03: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_03: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_03: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_03: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_03: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_03: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_03: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_03: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_03: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_03: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_03: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_03: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_03: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_03: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_03: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_03: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_03: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_03: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_03: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_03: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_03: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_03: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_03: Come inside.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_03: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_03: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_03: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_03: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_03: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_03: When is it due?
SPEAKER_03: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_03: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_03: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_03: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_03: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_03: Go ask.
SPEAKER_03: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_03: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_03: Want one?
SPEAKER_03: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_03: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_03: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_03: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_03: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_03: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_03: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_03: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_03: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_03: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_03: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_03: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_03: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_03: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_03: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_03: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_03: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_03: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_03: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_03: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_03: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_03: What's with him?
SPEAKER_03: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_03: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_03: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_03: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_03: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_03: to show her.
SPEAKER_03: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_03: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_03: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_03: Uncle.
SPEAKER_03: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_03: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_03: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_03: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_03: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_03: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_03: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_03: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_03: You will ride on an ox's back.