SPEAKER_19: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_19: What's his name?
SPEAKER_19: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_19: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_19: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_19: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_19: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_19: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_19: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_19: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_19: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_19: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_19: Fugui...
SPEAKER_19: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_19: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_19: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_19: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_19: He is dead.
SPEAKER_19: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_19: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_19: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_19: Wake up.
SPEAKER_19: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_19: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_19: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_19: Come inside.
SPEAKER_19: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_19: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_19: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_19: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_19: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_19: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_19: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_19: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_19: Who?
SPEAKER_19: You came for this?
SPEAKER_19: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_19: Why?
SPEAKER_19: I don't know.
SPEAKER_19: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_19: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_19: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_19: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_19: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_19: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_19: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_19: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_19: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_19: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_19: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_19: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_19: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_19: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_19: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_19: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_19: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_19: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_19: How about in here?
SPEAKER_19: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_19: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_19: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_19: and life will get better and better.