SPEAKER_10: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_10: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_10: Look at this.
SPEAKER_10: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_10: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_10: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_10: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_10: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_10: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_10: It's all here?
SPEAKER_10: Keep these.
SPEAKER_10: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_10: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_10: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_10: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_10: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_10: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_10: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_10: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_10: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_10: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_10: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_10: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_10: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_10: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_10: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_10: Fugui...
SPEAKER_10: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_10: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_10: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_10: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_10: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_10: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.