SPEAKER_20: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_20: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_20: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_20: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_20: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_20: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_20: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_20: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_20: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_20: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_20: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_20: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_20: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_20: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_20: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_20: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_20: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_20: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_20: What do you want?
SPEAKER_20: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_20: I wouldn't dare.