SPEAKER_18: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_18: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_18: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_18: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_18: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_18: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_18: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_18: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_18: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_18: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_18: Well?
SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_18: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_18: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_18: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_18: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_18: What is it?
SPEAKER_18: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_18: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_18: Good.
SPEAKER_18: Okay.
SPEAKER_18: Fengxia, after the child is born...