SPEAKER_28: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_28: Take care.
SPEAKER_28: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_28: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_28: Dad!
SPEAKER_28: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_28: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_28: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_28: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_28: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_28: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_28: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_28: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_28: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_28: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_28: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_28: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_28: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_28: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_28: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_28: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_28: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_28: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_28: Let me think.
SPEAKER_28: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_28: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_28: Is it a boy?