SPEAKER_27: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_27: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_27: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_27: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_27: So, no running?
SPEAKER_27: Fugui...
SPEAKER_27: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_27: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_27: Go away!
SPEAKER_27: All right.
SPEAKER_27: I'm going.
SPEAKER_27: We must be going.
SPEAKER_27: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_27: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_27: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_27: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_27: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_27: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_27: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_27: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_27: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_27: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_27: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_27: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_27: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_27: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_27: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_27: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_27: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_27: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_27: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_27: Have some water.
SPEAKER_27: It's okay.
SPEAKER_27: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_27: anything made from wheat.