SPEAKER_04: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_04: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_04: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_04: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_04: from making you go.
SPEAKER_04: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_04: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_04: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_04: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_04: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_04: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_04: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_04: Go away!
SPEAKER_04: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_04: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_04: You killed him.
SPEAKER_04: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_04: After oxen...
SPEAKER_04: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.