SPEAKER_29: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_29: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_29: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_29: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_29: Just like me.
SPEAKER_29: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_29: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_29: wounded me
SPEAKER_29: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_29: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_29: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_29: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_29: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_29: You won't go?
SPEAKER_29: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_29: Enough!
SPEAKER_29: How could you?
SPEAKER_29: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_29: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_29: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_29: What's happened?
SPEAKER_29: Answer me!
SPEAKER_29: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_29: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_29: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_29: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_29: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_29: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_29: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_29: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_29: Time to wrap up.