SPEAKER_28: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_28: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_28: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_28: It's settled.
SPEAKER_28: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_28: What's his name?
SPEAKER_28: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_28: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_28: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_28: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_28: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_28: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_28: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_28: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_28: They shot him.
SPEAKER_28: He is dead.
SPEAKER_28: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_28: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_28: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_28: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_28: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_28: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_28: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_28: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_28: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_28: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_28: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_28: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_28: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_28: He can run?
SPEAKER_28: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_28: We approve.
SPEAKER_28: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_28: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_28: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_28: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_28: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_28: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_28: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_28: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_28: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_28: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_28: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_28: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_28: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_28: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_28: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_28: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_28: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_28: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_28: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_28: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_28: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_28: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_28: How about in here?
SPEAKER_28: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_28: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_28: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_28: And soon they'll grow up.