SPEAKER_29: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_29: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_29: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_29: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_29: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_29: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_29: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_29: It's ready.
SPEAKER_29: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_29: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_29: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_29: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_29: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_29: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_29: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_29: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_29: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_29: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_29: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_29: from making you go.
SPEAKER_29: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_29: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_29: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_29: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_29: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_29: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_29: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_29: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_29: Go away!
SPEAKER_29: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_29: You killed him.
SPEAKER_29: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_29: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_29: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_29: Very!
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia! You'll pull through.
Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_29: Please, Doctor, she's my only daughter.
SPEAKER_29: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_29: After oxen...
SPEAKER_29: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.