SPEAKER_08: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_08: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_08: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_08: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_08: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_08: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_08: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_08: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_08: This is too much.
SPEAKER_08: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_08: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_08: Sit here.
SPEAKER_08: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_08: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_08: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_08: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_08: You just have to!
SPEAKER_08: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_08: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_08: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_08: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_08: Yes, just gobbled them up.