SPEAKER_12: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_12: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_12: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_12: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_12: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_12: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_12: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_12: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_12: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_12: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_12: Really?
SPEAKER_12: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_12: Cheers!
SPEAKER_12: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_12: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_12: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_12: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_12: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_12: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_12: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_12: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_12: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_12: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_12: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_12: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_12: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_12: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_12: Let me think.
SPEAKER_12: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_12: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_12: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_12: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_12: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_12: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_12: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_12: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_12: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_12: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_12: Have some water.
SPEAKER_12: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_12: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_12: It's okay.
SPEAKER_12: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_12: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_12: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_12: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_12: Little Bun, behave yourself.