SPEAKER_14: Get out!
SPEAKER_14: I've just...
SPEAKER_14: Let's play!
SPEAKER_14: Go!
SPEAKER_14: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_14: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_14: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_14: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_14: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_14: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_14: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_14: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_14: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_14: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_14: Take this.
SPEAKER_14: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_14: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_14: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_14: How could you?
SPEAKER_14: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_14: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_14: What is this?
SPEAKER_14: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_14: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_14: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_14: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_14: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_14: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_14: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_14: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_14: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_14: Now!
SPEAKER_14: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_14: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_14: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_14: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_14: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_14: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_14: Go away!
SPEAKER_14: All right.
SPEAKER_14: I'm going.
SPEAKER_14: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_14: How dare you!
SPEAKER_14: What's going on?
SPEAKER_14: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_14: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_14: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_14: No!
SPEAKER_14: The 1960s
SPEAKER_14: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_14: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_14: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_14: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_14: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_14: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_14: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_14: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_14: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_14: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_14: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_14: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_14: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_14: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_14: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_14: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_14: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_14: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_14: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_14: Good idea.
SPEAKER_14: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_14: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_14: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_14: He was starving.
SPEAKER_14: But he was okay after the water.
SPEAKER_14: Oxygen.