SPEAKER_23: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_23: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_23: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_23: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_23: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_23: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_23: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_23: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_23: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_23: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_23: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_23: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_23: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_23: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_23: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_23: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_23: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_23: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_23: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_23: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_23: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_23: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_23: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_23: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.