SPEAKER_18: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_18: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_18: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_18: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_18: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_18: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_18: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_18: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_18: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_18: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_18: Fugui...
SPEAKER_18: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_18: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_18: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_18: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_18: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_18: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_18: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_18: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_18: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_18: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_18: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_18: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_18: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_18: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_18: As for me...
SPEAKER_18: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_18: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_18: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_18: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_18: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_18: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_18: Fugui...
SPEAKER_18: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_18: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_18: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_18: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_18: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_18: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_18: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_18: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_18: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_18: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_18: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_18: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_18: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_18: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_18: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_18: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_18: Landlords?
SPEAKER_18: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_18: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_18: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_18: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_18: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_18: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_18: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_18: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_18: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_18: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_18: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_18: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_18: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_18: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_18: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_18: Wake up.
SPEAKER_18: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_18: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_18: Our family...
SPEAKER_18: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_18: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_18: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_18: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_18: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_18: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_18: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_18: that we could...
SPEAKER_18: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_18: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_18: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_18: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_18: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_18: I approve.
SPEAKER_18: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_18: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_18: From where?
SPEAKER_18: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_18: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_18: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_18: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_18: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_18: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_18: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_18: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_18: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_18: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_18: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_18: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_18: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_18: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_18: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_18: On the mend.
SPEAKER_18: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_18: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_18: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_18: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_18: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_18: Of course.
SPEAKER_18: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_18: You came for this?
SPEAKER_18: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_18: Why?
SPEAKER_18: I don't know.
SPEAKER_18: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_18: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_18: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_18: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_18: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_18: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_18: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_18: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_18: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_18: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_18: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_18: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_18: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_18: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_18: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_18: They did.
SPEAKER_18: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_18: No doctors?
SPEAKER_18: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_18: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_18: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_18: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_18: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_18: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_18: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_18: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_18: Is it?
SPEAKER_18: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_18: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_18: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_18: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_18: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_18: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_18: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_18: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_18: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_18: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_18: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_18: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_18: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_18: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_18: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_18: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_18: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_18: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_18: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_18: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_18: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_18: And then...
SPEAKER_18: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_18: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_18: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_18: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_18: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_18: and life will get better and better.