SPEAKER_07: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_07: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_07: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_07: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_07: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_07: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_07: Okay?
SPEAKER_07: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_07: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_07: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_07: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_07: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_07: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_07: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_07: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_07: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_07: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_07: Are you happy?