SPEAKER_01: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_01: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_01: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_01: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_01: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_01: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_01: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_01: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_01: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_01: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_01: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_01: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_01: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_01: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_01: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_01: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_01: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_01: Come on in!