SPEAKER_27: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_27: The day...
SPEAKER_27: Written?
SPEAKER_27: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_27: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_27: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_27: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_27: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_27: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_27: come see the show.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_27: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_27: When you get there...
SPEAKER_27: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_27: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_27: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_27: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_27: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_27: That's good.
SPEAKER_27: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_27: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_27: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_27: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_27: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_27: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_27: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_27: Where's Erxi?