SPEAKER_26: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_26: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_26: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_26: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_26: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_26: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_26: Sit down.
SPEAKER_26: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_26: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_26: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_26: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_26: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_26: Just like me.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_26: You won't go?
SPEAKER_26: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_26: Enough!
SPEAKER_26: How could you?
SPEAKER_26: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_26: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_26: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_26: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_26: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_26: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_26: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_26: Daddy.
SPEAKER_26: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_26: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_26: What's happened?
SPEAKER_26: Answer me!
SPEAKER_26: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_26: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_26: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_26: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_26: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_26: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_26: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_26: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_26: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_26: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_26: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_26: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_26: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_26: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_26: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_26: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_26: He gobbled up seven buns.