SPEAKER_16: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_16: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_16: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_16: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_16: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_16: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_16: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_16: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_16: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_16: Well?
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_16: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_16: Well?
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_16: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_16: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_16: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_16: What is it?
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_16: How?
SPEAKER_16: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_16: Good.
SPEAKER_16: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_16: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_16: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_16: This is great.
SPEAKER_16: Okay.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia, after the child is born...