SPEAKER_05: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_05: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_05: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_05: want more time
SPEAKER_05: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_05: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_05: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_05: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_05: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_05: Come out!
SPEAKER_05: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_05: wounded me
SPEAKER_05: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_05: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_05: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_05: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_05: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_05: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_05: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_05: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_05: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_05: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_05: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_05: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_05: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_05: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_05: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_05: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.