SPEAKER_11: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_11: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_11: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_11: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_11: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_11: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_11: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_11: How could that be?
SPEAKER_11: So, no running?
SPEAKER_11: Go away!
SPEAKER_11: All right.
SPEAKER_11: I'm going.
SPEAKER_11: We must be going.
SPEAKER_11: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_11: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_11: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_11: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_11: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_11: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_11: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_11: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_11: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_11: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_11: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_11: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_11: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_11: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_11: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_11: What's with him?
SPEAKER_11: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_11: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_11: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_11: It's okay.
SPEAKER_11: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_11: anything made from wheat.