SPEAKER_01: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_01: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_01: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_01: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_01: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_01: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_01: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_01: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_01: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_01: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_01: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_01: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_01: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_01: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_01: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_01: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_01: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_01: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_01: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_01: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_01: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_01: Good idea.