SPEAKER_23: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_23: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_23: want more time
SPEAKER_23: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_23: It's ready.
SPEAKER_23: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_23: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_23: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_23: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_23: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_23: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_23: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_23: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_23: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_23: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_23: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_23: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_23: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_23: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_23: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_23: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_23: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_23: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_23: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_23: Let her go!
SPEAKER_23: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_23: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_23: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_23: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_23: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_23: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_23: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_23: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_23: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.