SPEAKER_04: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_04: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_04: Well?
SPEAKER_04: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_04: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_04: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_04: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_04: What's up?
SPEAKER_04: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_04: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_04: And after the ox?
SPEAKER_04: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_04: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_04: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_04: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_04: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_04: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_04: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_04: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_04: Don't move.
SPEAKER_04: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_04: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_04: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_04: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_04: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_04: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_04: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_04: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_04: He'll know.
SPEAKER_04: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_04: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_04: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_04: Back already?
SPEAKER_04: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_04: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_04: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_04: Grandpa, where will the chicks live?
SPEAKER_04: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_04: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_04: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_04: Let's see.
SPEAKER_04: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_04: Very soon.
SPEAKER_04: And then?
SPEAKER_04: And then...
SPEAKER_04: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_04: After oxen...
SPEAKER_04: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_04: I want to ride on an ox's back!