SPEAKER_16: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_16: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_16: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_16: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_16: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_16: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_16: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_16: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_16: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_16: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_16: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_16: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_16: Really?
SPEAKER_16: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_16: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_16: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_16: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_16: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_16: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_16: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_16: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_16: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_16: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_16: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_16: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_16: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_16: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_16: Let me think.
SPEAKER_16: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_16: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_16: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_16: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_16: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_16: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_16: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_16: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_16: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_16: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_16: Have some water.
SPEAKER_16: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_16: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_16: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_16: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_16: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_16: Little Bun, behave yourself.