SPEAKER_28: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_28: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_28: Look at this.
SPEAKER_28: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_28: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_28: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_28: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_28: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_28: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_28: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_28: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_28: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_28: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_28: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_28: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_28: It's all here?
SPEAKER_28: Keep these.
SPEAKER_28: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_28: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_28: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_28: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_28: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_28: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_28: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_28: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_28: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_28: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_28: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_28: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_28: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_28: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_28: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_28: Take that!
SPEAKER_28: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_28: Enough?
SPEAKER_28: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_28: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_28: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_28: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_28: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_28: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_28: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_28: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_28: Fugui...
SPEAKER_28: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_28: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_28: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_28: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_28: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_28: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_28: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_28: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_28: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_28: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_28: What's happened?
SPEAKER_28: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_28: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_28: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_28: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_28: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_28: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_28: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_28: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_28: I wouldn't dare.