SPEAKER_03: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_03: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_03: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_03: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_03: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_03: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_03: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_03: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_03: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_03: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_03: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_03: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_03: You cold?
SPEAKER_03: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_03: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_03: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_03: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_03: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_03: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_03: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_03: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_03: Yes.
SPEAKER_03: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_03: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_03: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_03: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_03: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_03: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_03: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_03: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_03: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_03: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_03: Quick!