SPEAKER_08: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_08: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_08: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_08: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_08: I see your point.
SPEAKER_08: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_08: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_08: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_08: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_08: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_08: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_08: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_08: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_08: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_08: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_08: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_08: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_08: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_08: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_08: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_08: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_08: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_08: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_08: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_08: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_08: Fengxia's about to give birth?