SPEAKER_19: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_19: How much?
SPEAKER_19: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_19: You're up.
SPEAKER_19: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_19: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_19: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_19: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_19: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_19: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_19: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_19: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_19: As for me...
SPEAKER_19: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_19: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_19: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_19: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_19: The day...
SPEAKER_19: Written?
SPEAKER_19: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_19: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_19: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_19: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_19: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_19: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_19: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_19: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_19: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_19: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_19: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_19: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_19: Wake up.
SPEAKER_19: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_19: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_19: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_19: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_19: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_19: that we could...
SPEAKER_19: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_19: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_19: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_19: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_19: He can run?
SPEAKER_19: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_19: I approve.
SPEAKER_19: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_19: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_19: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_19: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_19: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_19: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_19: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_19: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_19: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_19: They did.
SPEAKER_19: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_19: No doctors?
SPEAKER_19: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_19: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_19: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_19: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_19: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_19: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_19: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_19: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_19: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_19: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_19: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_19: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_19: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_19: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_19: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_19: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_19: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_19: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_19: Help us!
SPEAKER_19: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_19: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_19: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_19: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_19: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_19: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_19: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_19: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_19: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_19: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_19: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_19: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_19: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_19: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_19: and life will get better and better.