SPEAKER_27: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_27: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_27: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_27: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_27: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_27: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_27: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_27: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_27: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_27: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_27: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_27: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_27: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_27: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_27: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_27: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_27: The 1940s
SPEAKER_27: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_27: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_27: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_27: Is gambling all you know?
SPEAKER_27: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_27: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_27: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_27: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_27: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_27: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_27: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_27: Come out!
SPEAKER_27: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_27: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_27: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_27: The 1950s
SPEAKER_27: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_27: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_27: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_27: Take a break.
SPEAKER_27: Tired?
SPEAKER_27: Fugui!
SPEAKER_27: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_27: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_27: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_27: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_27: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_27: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_27: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_27: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_27: Enough?
SPEAKER_27: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_27: The 1960s
SPEAKER_27: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_27: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_27: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_27: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_27: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_27: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_27: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_27: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_27: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_27: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_27: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_27: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_27: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_27: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_27: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_27: Come over here.
SPEAKER_27: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_27: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_27: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_27: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_27: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_27: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_27: Some years later...