SPEAKER_07: Besides...
SPEAKER_07: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_07: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_07: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_07: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_07: As for me...
SPEAKER_07: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_07: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_07: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_07: The wounded.
SPEAKER_07: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_07: No one's left.
SPEAKER_07: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_07: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_07: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_07: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_07: It's all in this account. Take it.