SPEAKER_23: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_23: Take care.
SPEAKER_23: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_23: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_23: Dad!
SPEAKER_23: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_23: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_23: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_23: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_23: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_23: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_23: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_23: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_23: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_23: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_23: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_23: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_23: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_23: Cheers!
SPEAKER_23: Sit down.
SPEAKER_23: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_23: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_23: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_23: Yes, 7.9 pounds!