SPEAKER_09: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_09: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_09: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_09: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_09: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_09: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_09: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_09: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_09: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_09: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_09: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_09: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_09: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_09: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_09: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_09: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_09: The 1940s
SPEAKER_09: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_09: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_09: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_09: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_09: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_09: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_09: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_09: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_09: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_09: Take a break.
SPEAKER_09: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_09: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_09: Enough?
SPEAKER_09: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_09: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_09: Sit here.
SPEAKER_09: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_09: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_09: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_09: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_09: Come over here.
SPEAKER_09: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_09: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_09: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_09: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_09: Some years later...