SPEAKER_04: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_04: How much?
SPEAKER_04: You're here.
SPEAKER_04: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_04: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_04: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_04: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_04: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_04: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_04: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_04: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_04: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_04: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_04: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_04: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_04: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_04: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_04: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_04: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_04: He'll know.