SPEAKER_03: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_03: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_03: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_03: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_03: Tired?
SPEAKER_03: Fugui!
SPEAKER_03: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_03: It's ready.
SPEAKER_03: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_03: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_03: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_03: and after that...
SPEAKER_03: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_03: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_03: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_03: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_03: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_03: Come inside.
SPEAKER_03: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_03: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_03: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_03: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: What do you think?
SPEAKER_03: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_03: A cripple?
SPEAKER_03: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_03: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_03: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_03: You cold?
SPEAKER_03: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_03: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_03: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_03: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_03: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_03: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_03: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_03: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_03: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_03: Yes.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_03: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_03: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_03: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_03: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_03: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_03: When is it due?
SPEAKER_03: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_03: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_03: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_03: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_03: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_03: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_03: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_03: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_03: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_03: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_03: Uncle.
SPEAKER_03: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_03: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_03: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_03: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_03: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_03: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_03: After oxen...
SPEAKER_03: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.