SPEAKER_11: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_11: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_11: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_11: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_11: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_11: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_11: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_11: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_11: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_11: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_11: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_11: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_11: Wake up.
SPEAKER_11: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_11: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_11: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_11: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_11: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_11: They did.
SPEAKER_11: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_11: No.
SPEAKER_11: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_11: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_11: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_11: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_11: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_11: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_11: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_11: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_11: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_11: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_11: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_11: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_11: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_11: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_11: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_11: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_11: Help us!
SPEAKER_11: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_11: Quick!
SPEAKER_11: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_11: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_11: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_11: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_11: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_11: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_11: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_11: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_11: How about in here?
SPEAKER_11: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_11: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_11: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_11: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_11: And then...
SPEAKER_11: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_11: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_11: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_11: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_11: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_11: and life will get better and better.