SPEAKER_13: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_13: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_13: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_13: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_13: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_13: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_13: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_13: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_13: Good.
SPEAKER_13: A gambling debt's a debt,
and debts must be paid.
SPEAKER_13: I thought I'd live my final days here.
SPEAKER_13: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_13: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_13: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_13: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_13: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_13: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_13: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_13: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_13: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_13: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_13: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_13: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_13: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_13: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_13: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_13: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_13: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_13: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_13: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_13: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_13: Let me think.
SPEAKER_13: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.