SPEAKER_15: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_15: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_15: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_15: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_15: It's settled.
SPEAKER_15: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_15: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_15: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_15: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_15: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_15: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_15: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_15: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_15: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_15: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_15: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_15: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_15: They shot him.
SPEAKER_15: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_15: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_15: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_15: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_15: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_15: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_15: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_15: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_15: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_15: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_15: that we could...
SPEAKER_15: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_15: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_15: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_15: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_15: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_15: I approve.
SPEAKER_15: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_15: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_15: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_15: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_15: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_15: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_15: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_15: Why?
SPEAKER_15: I don't know.
SPEAKER_15: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_15: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_15: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_15: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_15: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_15: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_15: No doctors?
SPEAKER_15: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_15: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_15: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_15: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_15: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_15: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_15: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_15: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_15: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_15: Seven times seven is 49.