SPEAKER_20: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_20: Dad!
SPEAKER_20: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_20: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_20: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_20: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_20: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_20: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_20: Please.
SPEAKER_20: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_20: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_20: Tell me.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_20: Come home.
SPEAKER_20: Fugui...
SPEAKER_20: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_20: I've realized...
SPEAKER_20: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_20: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_20: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_20: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_20: Granny!
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_20: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_20: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_20: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_20: What's his name?
SPEAKER_20: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_20: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_20: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_20: Me.
SPEAKER_20: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_20: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_20: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_20: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_20: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_20: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_20: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_20: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_20: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_20: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_20: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_20: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_20: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_20: You should have written.
SPEAKER_20: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_20: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_20: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_20: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_20: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_20: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_20: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_20: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_20: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_20: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_20: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_20: You're here.
SPEAKER_20: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_20: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_20: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_20: Of course.
SPEAKER_20: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_20: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_20: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_20: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_20: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_20: and after that...
SPEAKER_20: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_20: What do you know?
SPEAKER_20: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_20: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_20: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_20: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_20: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_20: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_20: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_20: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_20: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_20: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_20: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_20: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_20: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_20: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_20: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_20: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_20: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_20: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_20: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_20: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_20: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_20: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_20: from making you go.
SPEAKER_20: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_20: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_20: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_20: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_20: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_20: You killed him.
SPEAKER_20: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_20: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_20: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_20: A good family.
SPEAKER_20: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_20: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_20: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_20: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_20: A cripple?
SPEAKER_20: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_20: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_20: We approve.
SPEAKER_20: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_20: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_20: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_20: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_20: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_20: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_20: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_20: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_20: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_20: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_20: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_20: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_20: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_20: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_20: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_20: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_20: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_20: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_20: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_20: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_20: Very!
SPEAKER_20: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_20: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_20: Come inside.
SPEAKER_20: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_20: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_20: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_20: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_20: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_20: When is it due?
SPEAKER_20: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_20: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_20: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_20: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_20: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_20: Don't move.
SPEAKER_20: Go ask.
SPEAKER_20: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_20: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_20: Want one?
SPEAKER_20: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_20: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_20: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_20: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_20: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_20: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_20: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_20: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_20: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_20: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_20: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_20: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_20: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_20: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_20: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_20: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_20: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_20: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_20: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_20: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_20: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_20: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_20: Have some water.
SPEAKER_20: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_20: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_20: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_20: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_20: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_20: to show her.
SPEAKER_20: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_20: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_20: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_20: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_20: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_20: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_20: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_20: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_20: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_20: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_20: You will ride on an ox's back.