SPEAKER_10: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_10: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_10: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_10: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_10: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_10: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_10: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_10: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_10: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_10: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_10: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_10: Okay?
SPEAKER_10: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_10: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_10: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_10: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_10: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_10: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_10: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_10: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_10: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_10: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_10: Enough?
SPEAKER_10: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_10: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_10: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_10: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_10: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_10: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_10: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_10: Come on in!
SPEAKER_10: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_10: Really?
SPEAKER_10: Who?
SPEAKER_10: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_10: What do you want?
SPEAKER_10: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_10: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_10: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_10: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_10: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_10: You just have to!
SPEAKER_10: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_10: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_10: I wouldn't dare.
SPEAKER_10: It's a boy.