SPEAKER_06: Go!
SPEAKER_06: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_06: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_06: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_06: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_06: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_06: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_06: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_06: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_06: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_06: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_06: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_06: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_06: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_06: It's ready.
SPEAKER_06: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_06: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_06: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_06: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_06: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_06: Enough?
SPEAKER_06: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_06: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_06: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_06: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_06: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_06: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_06: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_06: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_06: Come over here.
SPEAKER_06: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_06: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_06: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_06: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_06: Some years later...