SPEAKER_17: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_17: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_17: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_17: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui.
SPEAKER_17: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_17: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_17: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_17: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_17: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_17: As for me...
SPEAKER_17: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_17: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_17: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_17: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_17: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_17: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_17: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_17: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_17: It's money.
SPEAKER_17: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_17: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_17: I will remember.
SPEAKER_17: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_17: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_17: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_17: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_17: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_17: Of course.
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_17: Well?
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_17: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_17: You came for this?
SPEAKER_17: Take this...
SPEAKER_17: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_17: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_17: No.
SPEAKER_17: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_17: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_17: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_17: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_17: No, thank you, I've got to go.