SPEAKER_09: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_09: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_09: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_09: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_09: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_09: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_09: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_09: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_09: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_09: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_09: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_09: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_09: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_09: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_09: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_09: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_09: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_09: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_09: He's all right.
SPEAKER_09: Let's see.