SPEAKER_14: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_14: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_14: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_14: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_14: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_14: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_14: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_14: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_14: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_14: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_14: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_14: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_14: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_14: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_14: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_14: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_14: The 1940s
SPEAKER_14: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_14: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_14: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_14: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_14: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_14: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_14: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_14: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_14: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_14: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_14: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_14: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_14: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_14: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_14: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_14: What is it?
SPEAKER_14: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_14: Everyone's here today.
SPEAKER_14: So let's do what must be done.
SPEAKER_14: How?
SPEAKER_14: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_14: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_14: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_14: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_14: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_14: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_14: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_14: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_14: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_14: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_14: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_14: What's happened?
SPEAKER_14: I have to confess my crimes.