SPEAKER_02: Well?
SPEAKER_02: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_02: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_02: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_02: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_02: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_02: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_02: The wounded.
SPEAKER_02: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_02: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_02: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_02: Run now...
SPEAKER_02: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_02: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_02: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_02: That's right.
SPEAKER_02: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_02: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_02: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_02: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_02: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_02: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_02: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_02: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_02: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_02: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_02: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_02: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_02: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_02: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_02: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_02: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_02: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_02: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_02: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_02: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_02: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_02: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_02: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_02: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_02: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_02: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_02: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_02: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.