SPEAKER_23: As for me...
SPEAKER_23: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_23: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_23: No one's left.
SPEAKER_23: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_23: Home?
SPEAKER_23: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_23: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_23: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_23: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_23: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_23: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_23: It's all here?
SPEAKER_23: Keep these.
SPEAKER_23: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_23: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_23: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_23: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_23: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_23: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_23: This is too much.
SPEAKER_23: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_23: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_23: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_23: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_23: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_23: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui...
SPEAKER_23: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_23: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_23: Fugui!
SPEAKER_23: Who's there?
SPEAKER_23: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_23: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_23: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_23: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_23: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_23: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_23: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_23: The Red Guards are in control!