SPEAKER_16: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_16: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_16: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_16: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_16: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_16: What?
SPEAKER_16: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_16: Home!
SPEAKER_16: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_16: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_16: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_16: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_16: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_16: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_16: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_16: Look at this.
SPEAKER_16: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_16: to get you a better job. What do you think?