SPEAKER_08: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_08: How much?
SPEAKER_08: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: Fugui...
SPEAKER_08: Well?
SPEAKER_08: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_08: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_08: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_08: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_08: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_08: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_08: The day...
SPEAKER_08: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_08: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_08: Written?
SPEAKER_08: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_08: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_08: come see the show.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_08: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_08: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_08: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_08: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_08: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_08: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_08: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_08: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_08: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_08: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_08: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_08: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_08: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_08: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_08: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_08: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_08: Rice costs more than wheat.