SPEAKER_19: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_19: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_19: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_19: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_19: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_19: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_19: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_19: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_19: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_19: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_19: Of course.
SPEAKER_19: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_19: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_19: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_19: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_19: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_19: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_19: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_19: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_19: I see your point.
SPEAKER_19: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_19: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_19: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_19: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_19: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_19: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_19: How so?
SPEAKER_19: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_19: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_19: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_19: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_19: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_19: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_19: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_19: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_19: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_19: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_19: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_19: Daddy.
SPEAKER_19: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_19: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_19: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_19: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_19: No, really.
SPEAKER_19: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_19: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_19: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_19: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_19: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_19: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_19: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_19: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_19: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_19: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_19: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_19: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_19: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_19: My son was only 5.5 pounds.