SPEAKER_00: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_00: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_00: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_00: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_00: Turtle spawn! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_00: I'll cut him into pieces! I'll clobber him!
SPEAKER_00: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_00: I want him dead!
SPEAKER_00: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_00: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_00: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_00: Take that!
SPEAKER_00: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_00: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_00: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_00: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_00: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_00: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_00: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_00: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_00: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_00: After oxen...
SPEAKER_00: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_00: I want to ride on an ox's back!