SPEAKER_21: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_21: A dog's gotta eat shit! Little bastard!
SPEAKER_21: Of all you could have learned, bastard!
SPEAKER_21: Will you cut it out?
SPEAKER_21: - What'd he just say?
- Nothing. Eat.
SPEAKER_21: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_21: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_21: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_21: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_21: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_21: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_21: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_21: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_21: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_21: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_21: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_21: wounded me
SPEAKER_21: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_21: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_21: They never get...
SPEAKER_21: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_21: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_21: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_21: Landlords?
SPEAKER_21: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_21: Good idea!
SPEAKER_21: The 1950s
SPEAKER_21: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_21: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_21: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_21: Take a break.
SPEAKER_21: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_21: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_21: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_21: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_21: What is this?
SPEAKER_21: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_21: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_21: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_21: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_21: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_21: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_21: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_21: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_21: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_21: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_21: And after the ox?
SPEAKER_21: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_21: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_21: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_21: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_21: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_21: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_21: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_21: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_21: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_21: Go away!
SPEAKER_21: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_21: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_21: The 1960s
SPEAKER_21: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_21: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_21: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_21: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_21: He can run?
SPEAKER_21: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_21: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_21: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_21: What do you think?
SPEAKER_21: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_21: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_21: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_21: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_21: We must be going.
SPEAKER_21: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_21: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_21: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_21: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_21: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_21: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_21: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_21: Okay.
SPEAKER_21: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_21: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_21: Yes.
SPEAKER_21: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_21: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_21: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_21: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_21: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_21: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_21: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_21: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_21: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_21: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_21: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_21: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_21: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_21: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_21: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_21: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_21: You'll pull through!
SPEAKER_21: It's all right.
SPEAKER_21: Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_21: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_21: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_21: Oxygen.
SPEAKER_21: Please, Doctor, she's my only daughter.
SPEAKER_21: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.