SPEAKER_18: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_18: Get out!
SPEAKER_18: I've just...
SPEAKER_18: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_18: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_18: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_18: Sit down.
SPEAKER_18: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_18: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_18: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_18: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_18: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_18: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_18: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_18: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_18: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_18: Both sides must sign.
SPEAKER_18: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_18: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_18: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_18: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_18: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_18: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_18: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_18: Take this.
SPEAKER_18: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_18: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_18: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_18: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_18: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_18: How could you?
SPEAKER_18: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_18: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_18: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_18: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_18: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_18: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_18: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_18: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_18: Now!
SPEAKER_18: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_18: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_18: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_18: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_18: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_18: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_18: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_18: What's up?
SPEAKER_18: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_18: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_18: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_18: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_18: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_18: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_18: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_18: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_18: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_18: What's happened?
SPEAKER_18: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_18: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_18: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_18: How dare you!
SPEAKER_18: What's going on?
SPEAKER_18: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_18: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_18: Let her go!
SPEAKER_18: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_18: No!
SPEAKER_18: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_18: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_18: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_18: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_18: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_18: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_18: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_18: Please come again.
SPEAKER_18: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_18: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_18: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_18: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_18: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_18: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_18: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_18: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_18: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_18: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_18: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_18: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_18: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_18: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_18: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_18: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_18: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_18: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_18: Good idea.
SPEAKER_18: What's with him?
SPEAKER_18: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_18: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_18: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_18: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_18: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_18: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_18: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_18: He was starving.
SPEAKER_18: But he was okay after the water.