SPEAKER_07: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_07: want more time
SPEAKER_07: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_07: Is gambling all you know?
SPEAKER_07: Let's play!
SPEAKER_07: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_07: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_07: Sir!
SPEAKER_07: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_07: Come out!
SPEAKER_07: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_07: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_07: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_07: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_07: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_07: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_07: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_07: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_07: How could that be?
SPEAKER_07: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_07: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_07: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_07: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_07: Just like me.
SPEAKER_07: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_07: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_07: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_07: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_07: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_07: You won't go?
SPEAKER_07: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_07: Enough!
SPEAKER_07: How could you?
SPEAKER_07: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_07: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_07: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_07: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_07: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_07: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_07: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_07: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_07: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_07: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_07: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_07: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_07: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_07: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_07: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_07: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_07: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_07: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_07: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_07: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_07: Answer me!
SPEAKER_07: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_07: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_07: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_07: Go away!
SPEAKER_07: All right.
SPEAKER_07: I'm going.
SPEAKER_07: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_07: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_07: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_07: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_07: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_07: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_07: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_07: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_07: They say she's great. No problems.