SPEAKER_05: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_05: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_05: You're up.
SPEAKER_05: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_05: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_05: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_05: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_05: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_05: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_05: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_05: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_05: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_05: I'm home.
SPEAKER_05: Home.
SPEAKER_05: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_05: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_05: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_05: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_05: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_05: He is dead.
SPEAKER_05: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_05: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_05: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_05: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_05: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_05: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_05: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_05: When you get there...
SPEAKER_05: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_05: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_05: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_05: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_05: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_05: That's good.
SPEAKER_05: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_05: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_05: Our family...
SPEAKER_05: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_05: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_05: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_05: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_05: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_05: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_05: From where?
SPEAKER_05: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_05: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_05: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_05: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_05: On the mend.
SPEAKER_05: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_05: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_05: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_05: This is great.
SPEAKER_05: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_05: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_05: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_05: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_05: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_05: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_05: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_05: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_05: Is it?
SPEAKER_05: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_05: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_05: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_05: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_05: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_05: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_05: I'll find a home for them when we get back.