SPEAKER_03: Take care.
SPEAKER_03: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_03: Good.
SPEAKER_03: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_03: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_03: Never mind.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_03: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_03: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_03: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_03: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_03: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_03: Cheers!
SPEAKER_03: Sit down.
SPEAKER_03: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_03: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_03: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_03: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_03: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_03: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_03: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_03: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_03: Little Bun, behave yourself.