SPEAKER_12: If you don't stop...
SPEAKER_12: we'll lose the little we have.
SPEAKER_12: Aren't you capable of anything else?
SPEAKER_12: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_12: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_12: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_12: Tired?
SPEAKER_12: Fugui!
SPEAKER_12: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_12: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_12: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_12: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_12: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_12: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_12: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_12: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_12: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_12: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_12: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_12: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_12: You cold?
SPEAKER_12: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_12: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_12: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_12: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_12: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_12: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_12: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_12: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_12: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_12: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_12: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_12: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_12: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_12: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_12: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_12: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_12: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_12: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_12: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_12: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_12: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_12: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_12: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_12: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_12: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_12: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_12: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_12: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_12: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_12: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_12: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_12: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_12: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_12: He'll know.
SPEAKER_12: Fengxia! You'll pull through.
Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_12: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_12: Back already?
SPEAKER_12: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_12: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_12: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_12: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_12: Grandpa, where will the chicks live?
SPEAKER_12: Uncle.
SPEAKER_12: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_12: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_12: Very soon.
SPEAKER_12: And then?