SPEAKER_04: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_04: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_04: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_04: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_04: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_04: Come inside.
SPEAKER_04: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_04: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_04: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_04: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_04: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_04: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_04: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_04: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_04: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_04: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_04: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_04: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_04: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_04: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_04: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_04: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_04: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_04: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_04: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_04: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_04: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_04: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_04: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_04: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_04: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_04: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_04: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_04: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_04: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_04: It's okay.
SPEAKER_04: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_04: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_04: anything made from wheat.