SPEAKER_13: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_13: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_13: Sit down.
SPEAKER_13: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_13: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_13: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_13: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_13: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_13: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_13: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_13: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_13: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_13: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_13: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_13: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_13: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_13: Take this.
SPEAKER_13: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_13: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_13: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_13: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_13: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_13: Now!
SPEAKER_13: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_13: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_13: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_13: come see the show.
SPEAKER_13: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_13: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_13: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_13: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_13: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_13: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_13: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_13: Good idea.