SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_11: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_11: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_11: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_11: Look at this.
SPEAKER_11: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_11: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_11: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_11: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_11: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_11: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_11: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_11: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_11: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_11: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_11: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_11: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_11: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_11: It's all here?
SPEAKER_11: Keep these.
SPEAKER_11: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_11: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_11: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_11: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_11: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_11: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_11: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_11: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_11: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_11: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_11: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_11: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_11: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_11: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_11: I see your point.
SPEAKER_11: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_11: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_11: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_11: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_11: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_11: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_11: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_11: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_11: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_11: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_11: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_11: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_11: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_11: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_11: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_11: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_11: Sit here.
SPEAKER_11: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_11: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_11: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_11: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_11: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_11: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_11: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_11: Fugui...
SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_11: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_11: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_11: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_11: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_11: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_11: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_11: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: Let's go.
SPEAKER_11: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_11: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_11: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_11: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_11: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_11: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_11: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_11: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_11: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_11: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_11: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_11: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_11: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_11: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_11: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_11: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_11: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_11: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_11: Go now, I'll be okay.