SPEAKER_08: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_08: It's money.
SPEAKER_08: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_08: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_08: Never mind.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_08: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_08: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_08: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_08: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_08: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_08: Really?
SPEAKER_08: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_08: Cheers!
SPEAKER_08: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_08: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_08: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_08: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_08: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_08: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_08: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_08: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_08: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_08: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_08: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_08: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_08: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_08: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_08: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_08: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_08: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_08: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_08: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_08: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_08: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_08: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_08: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_08: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_08: What's with him?
SPEAKER_08: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_08: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_08: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_08: It's okay.
SPEAKER_08: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_08: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_08: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_08: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_08: Little Bun, behave yourself.