SPEAKER_01: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_01: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_01: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_01: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_01: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_01: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_01: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_01: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_01: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_01: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_01: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_01: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_01: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_01: Enough!
SPEAKER_01: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_01: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_01: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_01: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_01: What's going on?
SPEAKER_01: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_01: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_01: No!
SPEAKER_01: The 1960s
SPEAKER_01: Come on in!
SPEAKER_01: Oxygen.