SPEAKER_31: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_31: Take care.
SPEAKER_31: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_31: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_31: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_31: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_31: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_31: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_31: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_31: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_31: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_31: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_31: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_31: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_31: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_31: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_31: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_31: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_31: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_31: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_31: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_31: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_31: We must be going.
SPEAKER_31: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_31: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_31: Please come again.
SPEAKER_31: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_31: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_31: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_31: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_31: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_31: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_31: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_31: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_31: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_31: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_31: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_31: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_31: Don't panic. Think of something.