SPEAKER_28: Go!
SPEAKER_28: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_28: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_28: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_28: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_28: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_28: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_28: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_28: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_28: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_28: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_28: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_28: So, no running?
SPEAKER_28: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_28: How could you?
SPEAKER_28: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_28: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_28: What is this?
SPEAKER_28: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_28: This is too much.
SPEAKER_28: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_28: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_28: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_28: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_28: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_28: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_28: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_28: Let her go!
SPEAKER_28: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_28: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_28: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_28: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_28: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_28: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_28: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_28: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_28: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_28: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_28: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_28: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_28: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_28: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_28: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?