SPEAKER_32: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_32: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_32: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_32: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_32: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_32: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_32: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_32: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_32: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_32: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_32: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_32: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_32: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_32: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_32: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_32: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_32: The 1940s
SPEAKER_32: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_32: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_32: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_32: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_32: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_32: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_32: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_32: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_32: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_32: Dad!
SPEAKER_32: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_32: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_32: Well?
SPEAKER_32: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_32: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_32: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_32: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_32: Well?
SPEAKER_32: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_32: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_32: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_32: What is it?
SPEAKER_32: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_32: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_32: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_32: Good.
SPEAKER_32: Okay.
SPEAKER_32: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_32: Take this...