SPEAKER_28: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_28: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_28: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_28: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_28: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_28: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_28: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_28: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_28: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_28: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_28: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_28: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_28: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_28: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_28: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_28: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_28: The 1940s
SPEAKER_28: You've lost again.
SPEAKER_28: Not one lucky toss all night.
SPEAKER_03: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_03: How much?
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: I've run up a pile of debts lately.
SPEAKER_03: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_03: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_03: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_03: They're too tired. Been at it all night.
SPEAKER_01: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_03: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_23: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_14: Old Man Heaven
SPEAKER_14: Don't make it so late
SPEAKER_14: Me and my lover
SPEAKER_14: want more time
SPEAKER_14: To frolic in our great big bed
SPEAKER_28: Long'er, you're nearly there.
SPEAKER_28: One more night like this...
SPEAKER_28: you'll have him right where you want him.
SPEAKER_28: Sure there's no mistake?
SPEAKER_28: Look at the records.
SPEAKER_16: Master Fugui is going home. You take him.
SPEAKER_12: Take care.
SPEAKER_12: Take care, Master.
SPEAKER_12: Welcome home, sir.
SPEAKER_12: Dad!
SPEAKER_12: Degenerate! Another night gambling!
SPEAKER_17: A dog's gotta eat shit! Little bastard!
SPEAKER_17: If you don't stop...
SPEAKER_17: we'll lose the little we have.
SPEAKER_17: Aren't you capable of anything else?
SPEAKER_24: Is gambling all you know?
SPEAKER_17: Of all you could have learned, bastard!
SPEAKER_26: Little bastards from big bastards grow.
SPEAKER_26: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_26: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_26: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_17: Will you cut it out?
SPEAKER_17: - What'd he just say?
- Nothing. Eat.
SPEAKER_26: Mother, when you finish,
send him to his room.
SPEAKER_10: Grandpa's cursing you again.
SPEAKER_18: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_18: You're up.
SPEAKER_18: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_03: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_03: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_06: You said you wouldn't gamble
if I got pregnant.
SPEAKER_06: Who was gambling? I went to watch.
SPEAKER_18: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_18: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_03: Let me wipe your tears.
SPEAKER_04: I'm not your father. I can't be fooled.
SPEAKER_03: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui...
SPEAKER_04: I've said all there is to say.
SPEAKER_04: Can't you listen just this once?
Quit gambling.
SPEAKER_04: It's like kicking an opium habit, you know.
SPEAKER_03: Too fast, and boing, you snap!
Could kill you.
SPEAKER_03: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_04: Please.
SPEAKER_04: I'm not asking much.
SPEAKER_04: Only to live a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, you choose. Gambling or family?
SPEAKER_04: Tell me.
SPEAKER_28: Your win, Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_03: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_03: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, your wife's here.
SPEAKER_28: What are you doing here?
SPEAKER_28: Well?
SPEAKER_19: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_03: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_03: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_03: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_03: It's settled.
SPEAKER_22: Mr. Xie...
SPEAKER_03: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_03: Of course.
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, you lost.
SPEAKER_28: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_00: Come, give Mrs. Xu a seat.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui, for the last time.
SPEAKER_04: Come home.
SPEAKER_01: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_01: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_01: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_01: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_08: Get out!
SPEAKER_08: I've just...
SPEAKER_08: Let's play!
SPEAKER_25: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_25: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_08: Go!
SPEAKER_08: Let's roll!
SPEAKER_28: Well?
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui, you're out of the game.
SPEAKER_28: You've lost everything.
SPEAKER_03: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_28: You bet your property.
It's equal to what you owe Long'er.
SPEAKER_28: You don't have a roof tile to your name.
SPEAKER_28: What is it?
SPEAKER_28: Master Fugui must settle his account.
SPEAKER_01: It's all in order, I'll be going.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui, don't think badly of me...
SPEAKER_01: for leaving you homeless.
SPEAKER_01: But I sure like that mansion of yours.
SPEAKER_01: See you there in a few days.
SPEAKER_03: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_03: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui, I'm sorry...
SPEAKER_01: but you've nothing left.
What would you wager?
SPEAKER_01: If you're unhappy, talk to Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_01: This can't be happening!
SPEAKER_13: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_13: It's not over yet!
SPEAKER_08: Sit down.
SPEAKER_13: - Sit down!
- You planned all this, didn't you?
SPEAKER_08: - Sit.
- Just one more round!
SPEAKER_16: I am very sorry, but you've got nothing left.
SPEAKER_16: What could you stake the bet on?
We don't accept empty bets.
SPEAKER_08: I'll stake my life.
SPEAKER_08: Don't talk like that.
SPEAKER_08: Anyway, your life's worth little now.
SPEAKER_12: Not that we'd accept it as ante.
SPEAKER_03: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_03: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_25: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_25: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_03: Okay?
SPEAKER_16: Your wife's been waiting for ages.
SPEAKER_04: Fugui...
SPEAKER_04: I just wanted to tell you...
SPEAKER_04: I've realized...
SPEAKER_04: you'll never change. I can't live like this.
SPEAKER_04: I'm taking Fengxia with me.
SPEAKER_04: If the baby is a boy...
SPEAKER_04: I won't let him be like you.
SPEAKER_03: Master Fugui, I'll take you.
SPEAKER_14: - What are you doing?
- Master Fugui.
SPEAKER_11: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_11: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_16: Mr. Xu, any mistakes?
SPEAKER_30: No, Fugui's signature is on each one.
SPEAKER_30: Long'er, is our Xu family home...
SPEAKER_30: enough to settle Fugui's debt?
SPEAKER_30: Good.
SPEAKER_30: A gambling debt's a debt,
and debts must be paid.
SPEAKER_30: Everyone's here today.
SPEAKER_30: So let's do what must be done.
SPEAKER_21: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_21: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_21: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_21: Both sides must sign.
SPEAKER_21: I thought I'd live my final days here.
SPEAKER_21: Fugui.
SPEAKER_21: Turtle spawn! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_21: I'll cut him into pieces! I'll clobber him!
SPEAKER_21: I'll never forgive you!
SPEAKER_21: I want him dead!
SPEAKER_21: Sir!
SPEAKER_01: It's valuable. Don't scratch it. Take it slowly.
SPEAKER_01: Careful, slowly. Don't move too fast!
SPEAKER_01: Don't break anything!
SPEAKER_01: Your mother's not well.
Go now, for her sake.
SPEAKER_01: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_01: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_01: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_11: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_04: Granny!
SPEAKER_04: Jiazhen's come home.
SPEAKER_04: Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_04: Come look at your son.
SPEAKER_06: He looks like you.
SPEAKER_03: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_03: What's his name?
SPEAKER_04: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_04: He'll never gamble.
SPEAKER_04: Who chose that name?
SPEAKER_04: Me.
SPEAKER_04: Very good, very good.
SPEAKER_04: I don't gamble now. Not even in my next life.
SPEAKER_04: I know. Or I wouldn't have come back.
SPEAKER_04: Is his name really "Don't Gamble"?
SPEAKER_04: I was just teasing Fugui. It's Youqing.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_04: Jiazhen, it's great to have you back.
SPEAKER_18: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_18: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_04: Let's put the past behind us...
SPEAKER_04: and live peacefully.
SPEAKER_18: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_18: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_04: I'll tidy up tomorrow. We'll be fine.
SPEAKER_03: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_18: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_04: Dad didn't give me much money...
SPEAKER_04: but she needs a doctor.
SPEAKER_04: We'll work something out.
SPEAKER_04: I'll borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_30: Life won't be easy.
SPEAKER_04: Don't say that.
SPEAKER_04: All I ask is a quiet life together.
SPEAKER_01: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_01: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_03: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_01: This old home of yours is great.
SPEAKER_01: Warm in winter, cool in summer.
SPEAKER_01: Great at any price.
SPEAKER_01: I've given up the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_01: Have a seat.
SPEAKER_01: I don't gamble anymore.
Don't want to end up like you.
SPEAKER_03: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_03: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_03: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_03: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_03: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_01: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_01: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_23: I never had to beg
when I ran the puppet troupe.
SPEAKER_01: Earn your money yourself.
SPEAKER_01: Put together a troupe.
SPEAKER_01: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_01: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_01: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_01: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_14: Me and my lover want more time
SPEAKER_14: To frolic on our great big bed
SPEAKER_14: Come out!
SPEAKER_00: Come on! Get a move on!
SPEAKER_00: 1949: Chiang Kai-shek's Nationalist Army
is losing the civil war.
SPEAKER_00: The Communists under Mao Zedong
are poised to take over China.
SPEAKER_00: So we're fighting the Communists.
SPEAKER_19: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_19: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_19: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_19: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_20: Besides...
SPEAKER_20: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_20: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_20: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_20: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_20: As for me...
SPEAKER_20: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_20: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_19: I'd die happy if I could drive.
SPEAKER_18: As for me...
SPEAKER_18: I want to live. There's nothing like family.
SPEAKER_11: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_08: This case is in the way!
SPEAKER_08: Whose is it? Get rid of it!
SPEAKER_08: Sir, it's mine.
I've got my things in it. Let me keep it.
SPEAKER_08: Get it out of my sight then.
SPEAKER_03: It's just a bunch of puppets.
Get rid of them! This is war!
SPEAKER_03: They're not mine. It's how I make my living.
SPEAKER_20: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_18: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_20: The wounded.
SPEAKER_20: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_20: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_20: No one's left.
SPEAKER_20: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_08: Way to go, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_08: Take this.
SPEAKER_03: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_18: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_16: The wounded who froze to death.
SPEAKER_20: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_19: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_25: It really is booze!
SPEAKER_20: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_18: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_18: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_20: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_20: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_20: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_20: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_25: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_16: They've all run off.
SPEAKER_16: How could that be?
SPEAKER_20: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_19: What?
SPEAKER_19: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_25: Home!
SPEAKER_21: Home?
SPEAKER_21: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_20: Run now...
SPEAKER_20: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_21: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_20: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_16: So, no running?
SPEAKER_20: That's right.
SPEAKER_20: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_03: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_03: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_20: How?
SPEAKER_19: This will do the trick?
SPEAKER_20: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_20: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_20: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_20: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_19: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_11: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_18: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_18: Fugui...
SPEAKER_18: we've got to make it back alive.
SPEAKER_03: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan! They're shooting!
SPEAKER_21: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_03: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_20: The coat's from my brother's unit.
SPEAKER_08: - What are you doing?
- They're shooting!
SPEAKER_26: What's your brother look like?
SPEAKER_26: Just like me.
SPEAKER_26: Lao Quan!
SPEAKER_13: The enemy's secret weapon
SPEAKER_13: wounded me
SPEAKER_13: I gather my troops
SPEAKER_13: and we run for our lives
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_23: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_23: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_23: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_23: I'm home.
SPEAKER_23: Home.
SPEAKER_18: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_18: The day...
SPEAKER_03: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_03: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_04: She never shut her eyes...
SPEAKER_04: kept them fixed on the door,
so sure you'd be back.
SPEAKER_04: You should have written.
SPEAKER_18: Written?
SPEAKER_18: I never thought I'd make it back alive.
SPEAKER_03: I thought of you...
SPEAKER_18: all the time and worried...
SPEAKER_18: how you were getting by.
SPEAKER_18: The new government
paid for mother's burial...
SPEAKER_04: and gave me this job, delivering water.
SPEAKER_04: I'm up before dawn.
SPEAKER_04: Everyone wants water.
SPEAKER_04: The more I deliver, the more I earn.
SPEAKER_04: It's been hard on the kids.
SPEAKER_04: They never get...
SPEAKER_04: a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_03: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_18: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_18: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_04: In fact, she was lucky.
SPEAKER_04: For a week, she ran a high fever.
SPEAKER_04: No one thought she'd pull through.
SPEAKER_04: When the fever came down...
SPEAKER_04: she'd lost her voice.
SPEAKER_04: You're here.
SPEAKER_03: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_03: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_06: So you're our leading cadre.
SPEAKER_09: - I heard you got back this morning.
- I'm back.
SPEAKER_09: I have come to see if you need anything.
SPEAKER_09: Look at this.
SPEAKER_09: He has served in the Liberation Army?
SPEAKER_09: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_03: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_09: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_09: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_18: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_18: We won't see him for a while.
SPEAKER_09: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_09: to attend Long'er's public trial.
SPEAKER_09: Come along and get an education.
SPEAKER_09: What did Long'er do?
SPEAKER_04: Because of the family home,
he's been sentenced a landlord.
SPEAKER_09: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_09: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_09: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_09: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_09: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_18: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_07: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_07: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_07: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_04: Counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_09: Of course. You're you, he's him.
SPEAKER_00: Execute the revolutionary despot, Long'er!
SPEAKER_00: To the execution ground!
SPEAKER_00: We will crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_00: Crush the counterrevolution!
SPEAKER_00: Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_00: Long live the Communist Party!
SPEAKER_00: Long live the People's Government!
SPEAKER_00: Long live Chairman Mao!
Down with the counterrevolutionaries!
SPEAKER_00: Build a new China!
SPEAKER_04: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_04: Why are your pants wet?
SPEAKER_03: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_03: They shot him.
SPEAKER_29: They shot Long'er?
SPEAKER_03: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_03: He is dead.
SPEAKER_03: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_03: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_18: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_03: Landlords?
SPEAKER_03: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_04: Not landlords.
SPEAKER_04: Ordinary townspeople.
SPEAKER_03: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_03: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_04: - In the wash?
- No, here it is.
SPEAKER_03: Better dry it out fast.
SPEAKER_04: Have to keep it safe.
SPEAKER_04: Are you sure we're just townsfolk?
SPEAKER_04: Of course.
SPEAKER_04: Poor townspeople.
SPEAKER_04: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_04: Get a frame for it tomorrow.
SPEAKER_04: I'll hang it on the wall.
SPEAKER_04: Good idea!
SPEAKER_27: The 1950s
SPEAKER_27: 1958: Mao Zedong launches
the "Great Leap Forward."
SPEAKER_27: Steel production is now targeted
at 10.7 million tonnes per year.
SPEAKER_27: Every household donates its iron utensils.
SPEAKER_27: Take a break.
SPEAKER_29: Tired?
SPEAKER_29: Fugui!
SPEAKER_29: Our family's turn to donate iron.
SPEAKER_29: It's ready.
SPEAKER_09: It's all here?
SPEAKER_09: Keep these.
SPEAKER_09: To deliver water to the steelworks.
SPEAKER_09: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_09: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_06: If you take all our pots away,
how will we cook?
SPEAKER_09: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_09: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_09: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_09: just come to the canteen.
SPEAKER_09: There'll be meat, fish.
SPEAKER_09: Nothing else to contribute?
SPEAKER_09: Yes, there is!
SPEAKER_09: But that's wood.
SPEAKER_10: There's metal on it.
SPEAKER_02: And here are pins.
SPEAKER_18: It can't be worth much.
SPEAKER_09: We are less politically aware than your son.
SPEAKER_09: It's enough for two bullets.
SPEAKER_09: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_09: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_04: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_04: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_04: and after that...
SPEAKER_18: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_07: I see your point.
SPEAKER_09: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_09: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_03: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_03: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_03: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_02: We are not going to liberate Taiwan?
SPEAKER_09: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_11: Take that!
SPEAKER_11: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_11: Enough?
SPEAKER_11: Still not enough? Okay, I'll fill it right up.
SPEAKER_23: Big ambition for a little kid.
SPEAKER_23: It's more than enough.
SPEAKER_23: So gobble away. Help yourself to sauces.
SPEAKER_23: Youqing, I'll help you stir that up.
SPEAKER_23: What a big appetite!
SPEAKER_23: And so much chili sauce!
SPEAKER_29: That's a big bowl, Youqing.
SPEAKER_29: Give it to us if you can't finish.
SPEAKER_29: What the hell are you doing?
SPEAKER_08: How could you?
SPEAKER_08: Can't you control this child?
SPEAKER_08: What did you think you were doing?
SPEAKER_08: What is this?
SPEAKER_11: Look at all the chili sauce.
Let me see your eyes.
SPEAKER_25: This is too much.
SPEAKER_08: - Trying to kill him, or what?
- They're just kids.
SPEAKER_08: Kids? Where did he learn that from?
SPEAKER_18: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_08: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_08: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_08: It's sabotage.
Sabotage to the communal kitchen.
SPEAKER_08: And sabotage of the Great Leap Forward!
SPEAKER_08: That kid could not dream that up.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing! Look what you've done!
SPEAKER_08: Apologize. Say you were wrong.
SPEAKER_08: Now!
SPEAKER_08: I'm talking to you.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going?
- No.
SPEAKER_13: - Are you going or not?
- No!
SPEAKER_13: - I'm telling you to go!
SPEAKER_13: You won't go?
SPEAKER_11: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_13: Leave him alone! I'll kill him!
SPEAKER_13: Enough!
SPEAKER_13: How could you?
SPEAKER_03: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_04: That guy's word is law? The government?
SPEAKER_04: I tried to stop you.
SPEAKER_03: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_03: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_03: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_03: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_03: How so?
SPEAKER_03: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_03: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_03: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_25: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_25: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_04: Isn't he your own flesh and blood?
SPEAKER_04: You, looking after us! After all these years.
SPEAKER_04: What do you know?
SPEAKER_04: Kids had been bullying Fengxia.
He was defending her.
SPEAKER_04: Do you think I'd let this family go to ruin?
SPEAKER_04: I've stuck with you through good and bad.
SPEAKER_04: Have I ever complained?
SPEAKER_04: Poor Fengxia.
Can't even talk back to bullies.
SPEAKER_04: Youqing adores her. And you'd hit him.
SPEAKER_03: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_03: come see the show.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_03: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_03: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_03: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_03: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_14: He wouldn't come.
SPEAKER_26: Ask him again.
SPEAKER_26: Say I want him to.
SPEAKER_29: Youqing, daddy wants you to see the show.
SPEAKER_04: Well?
SPEAKER_04: I'm not going!
SPEAKER_04: Do you like hearing daddy sing?
SPEAKER_04: Mommy doesn't either. He's so smug.
SPEAKER_04: Let's play a practical joke on him.
SPEAKER_04: Take him tea full of vinegar.
SPEAKER_04: That will teach him.
SPEAKER_11: Enough?
SPEAKER_04: Okay, we'll really get him.
SPEAKER_02: Should we add chili?
SPEAKER_02: Good, it'll be hot and sour soup.
SPEAKER_29: Your boy's on his way with a bowl of tea.
SPEAKER_26: Youqing, is that tea for me?
SPEAKER_26: Good boy, bring it over here.
SPEAKER_18: Daddy.
SPEAKER_18: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_18: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_00: He's put in chili!
SPEAKER_09: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_09: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_09: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_09: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_09: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_09: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_09: with a whole pig stuffed in each one!
SPEAKER_03: Eat your fill, and then we'll continue.
SPEAKER_13: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_09: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_13: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_09: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_09: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_09: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_03: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_13: and we'll liberate Taiwan!
SPEAKER_26: Xia, Youqing, have some dumplings.
SPEAKER_04: Let them sleep. They'll eat later.
SPEAKER_02: Xu Youqing!
SPEAKER_02: What's up?
SPEAKER_02: The teacher wants us at school
smelting steel.
SPEAKER_29: The District Head's making an inspection.
SPEAKER_29: All right. You go on ahead.
SPEAKER_03: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_04: He's not going anywhere.
He hasn't slept in days.
SPEAKER_04: Leave him alone.
SPEAKER_04: - The District Chief is coming.
- So?
SPEAKER_04: A kid still has to sleep.
SPEAKER_18: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_18: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_18: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_18: Wake up.
SPEAKER_18: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_00: Come on, get up.
SPEAKER_00: Your classmates are already on their way.
SPEAKER_18: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_18: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_18: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_03: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_03: When you get there...
SPEAKER_03: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_03: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_03: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_03: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_03: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_03: That's good.
SPEAKER_03: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_03: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_03: Our family...
SPEAKER_03: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_03: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_03: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_03: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_02: And after the ox?
SPEAKER_03: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_03: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_12: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_12: District Chief arrived after dark.
SPEAKER_12: He backed up,
and his jeep knocked the wall down.
SPEAKER_12: Youqing was sleeping on the other side.
SPEAKER_12: When the wall collapsed...
SPEAKER_12: he didn't have a chance.
SPEAKER_12: The District Chief was hurt, too.
SPEAKER_12: He hadn't slept for three days.
SPEAKER_12: Fugui, listen to me.
SPEAKER_12: We have to try and bear it,
even in the worst of times.
SPEAKER_26: What's happened?
SPEAKER_26: Answer me!
SPEAKER_26: Daddy's here! Say something!
SPEAKER_13: Take the body away!
SPEAKER_26: We mustn't let his mother see.
SPEAKER_26: Mommy's here! Youqing!
SPEAKER_26: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_11: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_04: You never had the chance to eat
the dumplings I packed for you.
SPEAKER_04: Mommy's made you more...
SPEAKER_04: twenty this time.
SPEAKER_04: That should be enough.
SPEAKER_04: Once you've eaten...
SPEAKER_04: you can sleep...
SPEAKER_06: a nice, deep sleep.
SPEAKER_06: In life, you never had a good night's sleep.
SPEAKER_06: So sleep well now.
SPEAKER_06: Mommy will come see you every day.
SPEAKER_06: Youqing, can you ever forgive me?
SPEAKER_06: I shouldn't have let you go to school.
SPEAKER_06: I should've kept your dad...
SPEAKER_06: from making you go.
SPEAKER_05: It's all my fault.
SPEAKER_06: If only I'd stopped him.
SPEAKER_05: I shouldn't have let you go, Youqing!
SPEAKER_05: Oh, my poor darling.
SPEAKER_09: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_04: The one who ran over my son?
SPEAKER_04: What's he doing here?
SPEAKER_29: Tell him to leave. He killed my son.
SPEAKER_29: - He's already here.
- Tell him to go.
SPEAKER_30: It's me, Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_19: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_19: Fugui...
SPEAKER_19: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_03: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_03: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_03: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_03: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_03: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_13: You, behind the goddamn wheel!
SPEAKER_09: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_09: The District Chief is upset, too.
SPEAKER_09: How can I ever make it up?
SPEAKER_19: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_19: It's money.
SPEAKER_19: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_06: No one wants your money.
SPEAKER_06: I want my son. Give me back my son.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him! Give him back to me!
SPEAKER_05: Go away!
SPEAKER_06: Remember, you owe us a life.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him. Remember that.
SPEAKER_06: You killed him.
SPEAKER_06: Go away! Now!
SPEAKER_05: District Chief, let's go.
SPEAKER_07: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_08: Go away!
SPEAKER_08: All right.
SPEAKER_08: I'm going.
SPEAKER_19: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_19: I will remember.
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing, you little wretch?
I'll teach you a lesson!
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_08: How dare you!
SPEAKER_08: What's going on?
SPEAKER_08: She smashed the windows of the jeep.
SPEAKER_08: Who the heck is she?
SPEAKER_08: Let her go!
SPEAKER_08: Are you mad?
SPEAKER_08: Do you want your jeep?
SPEAKER_08: No!
SPEAKER_10: The 1960s
SPEAKER_11: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_10: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_10: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_03: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_03: Sit here.
SPEAKER_03: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_07: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_18: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_18: that we could...
SPEAKER_18: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_18: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_07: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_07: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_07: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_09: Latest editorial:
SPEAKER_09: "The older, the more reactionary."
SPEAKER_09: Do as Chairman Mao says.
SPEAKER_03: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_07: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_07: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_07: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_08: You can't keep them. Burn them!
SPEAKER_09: Fugui...
SPEAKER_09: Chunsheng has asked me many times...
SPEAKER_09: to get you a better job. What do you think?
SPEAKER_18: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_18: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_18: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_09: I may have found a prospect for Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: I'll tell you about him.
SPEAKER_04: Let's not let her in on it for now.
SPEAKER_07: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_07: His name is Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_07: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_07: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_03: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_03: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_03: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_04: a lame leg.
SPEAKER_04: How lame? Can he walk?
SPEAKER_07: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_18: He can run?
SPEAKER_04: Was he born a cripple?
SPEAKER_07: No, it was an accident at work.
SPEAKER_07: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_07: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_07: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_04: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_09: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_09: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_09: Fengxia's mom and dad.
SPEAKER_04: Come inside.
SPEAKER_04: Have something to drink.
SPEAKER_04: Quotations from Chairman Mao
SPEAKER_09: Comrade Wan works
at the East Wind Factory.
SPEAKER_09: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_09: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's father took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_04: A good family.
SPEAKER_04: The Liberation Army
gave me that certificate.
SPEAKER_28: Good.
SPEAKER_07: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_16: Comrade Wan Erxi.
SPEAKER_07: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_19: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_04: Have something to eat first. Lunch is ready.
SPEAKER_04: No, thanks.
SPEAKER_03: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_03: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_03: No, really.
SPEAKER_07: Let's go.
SPEAKER_04: What do you think?
SPEAKER_18: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_18: I approve.
SPEAKER_04: Who's to say he'll like our Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: He only glanced at her, and wouldn't stay.
SPEAKER_18: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_18: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_04: I think she likes him.
SPEAKER_04: It's different from before. Look.
SPEAKER_04: Go ask Mr. Niu...
SPEAKER_04: what the boy thinks.
SPEAKER_04: How's this for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Comrade, could I look at that one?
SPEAKER_25: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_25: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_25: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_03: From where?
SPEAKER_25: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_04: You'd better hurry back.
SPEAKER_04: A cripple?
SPEAKER_04: Must be Wan Erxi!
SPEAKER_04: He doesn't like Fengxia,
so he tears the place down.
SPEAKER_18: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_18: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_04: We'd better hurry.
SPEAKER_04: Don't forget your package!
SPEAKER_19: Aren't you busy!
SPEAKER_15: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_15: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_15: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_15: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_15: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_15: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_15: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_15: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_16: We must be going.
SPEAKER_26: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_13: Erxi painted this.
SPEAKER_03: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_08: Erxi is good with his hands.
SPEAKER_03: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_29: I'll get some water so you can wash up.
SPEAKER_16: Thanks, we'll go to the factory bathhouse.
SPEAKER_25: You've gone to so much trouble.
SPEAKER_13: Please come again.
SPEAKER_13: What do you think about Fengxia and me?
SPEAKER_03: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_04: We approve.
SPEAKER_04: Shall we set a date?
SPEAKER_03: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's had a hard life.
SPEAKER_04: If you don't mind...
SPEAKER_04: let's make the wedding a real occasion.
SPEAKER_04: To make her happy.
SPEAKER_09: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_03: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_03: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_03: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_03: Nothing compares
to the Party's benevolence
SPEAKER_03: Chairman Mao is dearer
than father and mother
SPEAKER_03: There's nothing as good as socialism
SPEAKER_03: No ocean as deep as class feeling
SPEAKER_03: Maoist Thought
is revolution's treasure trove
SPEAKER_03: Whoever opposes it, we take as our enemy
SPEAKER_03: Come on, you can't cry today.
SPEAKER_04: They're all singing for Fengxia...
SPEAKER_04: and she can't even join in!
SPEAKER_18: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_26: Time for a photo!
SPEAKER_26: Move aside! Stand still!
SPEAKER_08: Hold your little Red Books.
SPEAKER_11: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_11: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_11: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_13: Time to wrap up.
SPEAKER_13: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_16: Chairman Mao...
SPEAKER_16: Comrade Fengxia's mine now.
SPEAKER_13: Come over here.
SPEAKER_13: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_19: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_15: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_15: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_11: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_11: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_28: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_19: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_19: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_03: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_03: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_03: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_04: Water's not boiled.
SPEAKER_03: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_03: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_03: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_03: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_03: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_03: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_04: If only Youqing had been here today.
SPEAKER_19: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_18: Don't go. The tea's ready.
SPEAKER_19: Never mind.
SPEAKER_19: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_19: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_04: Give it back to him.
SPEAKER_04: I don't want his gifts.
SPEAKER_03: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_08: Dad! Mom!
SPEAKER_08: Come on in!
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, you're back!
SPEAKER_29: You cold?
SPEAKER_29: I'm fine, really.
SPEAKER_29: How are you feeling, Mom?
SPEAKER_03: On the mend.
SPEAKER_03: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_06: Have you eaten?
SPEAKER_15: I'll make something.
SPEAKER_15: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_03: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_06: You brought a bottle.
SPEAKER_15: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_03: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_03: Really?
SPEAKER_15: I just came from the hospital.
The doctor says it's due in autumn.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, you're going to be a mother.
SPEAKER_12: Cheers!
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, when you went to the hospital today...
SPEAKER_04: what did they say about Fengxia's health?
SPEAKER_15: That she's in terrific shape.
SPEAKER_04: Still, you can't be too careful.
SPEAKER_04: Your folks aren't around.
SPEAKER_04: After the birth,
you'll stay with us for a while.
SPEAKER_04: Spend as much time as you can with her.
SPEAKER_04: When I was pregnant with Fengxia...
SPEAKER_04: her dad was never around.
SPEAKER_15: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_06: Very!
SPEAKER_03: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_03: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_18: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_18: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_18: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_29: Help yourself.
SPEAKER_15: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_04: We haven't taken a photo in years.
SPEAKER_03: This is great.
SPEAKER_04: After the child is born...
SPEAKER_04: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_04: We've no photos of Fengxia as a child.
SPEAKER_28: Okay.
SPEAKER_29: Fengxia, after the child is born...
SPEAKER_29: have a photo taken every year.
SPEAKER_29: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_15: He's been arrested as a capitalist.
SPEAKER_15: They held a public trial against him.
SPEAKER_15: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_03: Of course.
SPEAKER_03: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_03: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_19: Fugui!
SPEAKER_19: Who's there?
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_19: Who?
SPEAKER_30: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_30: What do you want?
SPEAKER_30: Come out for a second.
SPEAKER_18: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_03: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_19: Well?
SPEAKER_19: Fugui...
SPEAKER_19: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_19: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_03: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_03: You came for this?
SPEAKER_19: Take this...
SPEAKER_19: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_03: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_03: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_19: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_03: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_03: Why?
SPEAKER_03: I don't know.
SPEAKER_03: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_19: No.
SPEAKER_19: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_03: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_03: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_03: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_03: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_03: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_25: You just have to!
SPEAKER_25: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_25: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_25: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_03: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_03: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_03: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_03: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_03: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_19: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_04: Chunsheng, it's cold.
SPEAKER_04: Come inside.
SPEAKER_03: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_03: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_19: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_19: and better get back.
SPEAKER_19: Chunsheng, remember...
SPEAKER_29: you still owe us a life!
SPEAKER_29: You've got to value yours!
SPEAKER_29: Mr. Niu, is your wife at home?
SPEAKER_29: Yes.
SPEAKER_09: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's about to have a baby.
It's to thank the matchmaker!
SPEAKER_07: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_03: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_03: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_03: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_03: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_03: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_04: We'll bring the baby to see you.
SPEAKER_04: - But you won't stay?
- No, thanks.
SPEAKER_04: Never mind. Let's go. Don't worry.
SPEAKER_04: Why's she crying?
SPEAKER_09: What's happened?
SPEAKER_09: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_09: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_09: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_04: You! Crimes?
SPEAKER_03: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_03: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_09: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_09: I've always followed Chairman Mao's path.
SPEAKER_04: When will they let you return?
SPEAKER_09: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_09: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_09: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_03: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_29: We'll visit you after
she's out of the hospital.
SPEAKER_09: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.
SPEAKER_15: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_15: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_04: When is it due?
SPEAKER_15: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_15: Fengxia, don't be nervous.
SPEAKER_29: Won't hurt a bit.
SPEAKER_29: Remember to breathe and push.
SPEAKER_29: When you're pushing, bite on a towel.
SPEAKER_29: Where's the towel?
SPEAKER_29: Here, bite on this. It'll save your teeth.
SPEAKER_29: Do whatever the doctor tells you.
SPEAKER_29: It'll be quick if you push.
SPEAKER_16: Do as Mommy says and push.
SPEAKER_16: Everything will be fine.
SPEAKER_02: What's this about pushing?
Too early for pushing!
SPEAKER_02: And what's this shouting? Out!
SPEAKER_02: Go wait in the corridor.
SPEAKER_03: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_03: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_08: Sit down.
SPEAKER_04: They're all so young.
SPEAKER_04: Are they nurses?
SPEAKER_18: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_18: They did.
SPEAKER_18: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_30: No.
SPEAKER_04: Go ask where the doctors are.
SPEAKER_04: We must find a good doctor.
SPEAKER_12: They've been locked away.
SPEAKER_12: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_18: No doctors?
SPEAKER_15: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_15: Yes, us!
SPEAKER_15: I mean, older ones.
SPEAKER_02: They're all reactionaries.
We've overthrown them.
SPEAKER_02: Relax. Your wife's fine. We can handle this.
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, I'm worried.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's a mute.
SPEAKER_04: Can these young people cope?
SPEAKER_18: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_18: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_15: Have to get one out.
SPEAKER_15: Let me think.
SPEAKER_02: What is he doing here?
No reactionaries allowed!
SPEAKER_02: Wang Bin! Stand up!
SPEAKER_15: This is the same Wang Bin
who once insulted...
SPEAKER_15: me and my wife,
saying she wasn't fit to reproduce.
SPEAKER_08: How vile can you get?
SPEAKER_16: We dragged him here today...
SPEAKER_16: to educate him, to criticize him...
SPEAKER_16: and to let him witness her giving birth.
SPEAKER_16: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_02: The working class is really something!
SPEAKER_02: Wang Bin, don't make any trouble.
SPEAKER_02: Don't move.
SPEAKER_09: I wouldn't dare.
SPEAKER_16: That's professor Wang...
SPEAKER_16: head of obstetrics.
SPEAKER_16: Dr. Wang, don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_15: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_15: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_15: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_15: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_03: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_03: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_04: Go ask.
SPEAKER_03: I'm just going to see him.
SPEAKER_03: He's all right.
SPEAKER_18: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_18: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_18: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_18: Where's Erxi?
SPEAKER_04: They've gone to eat.
SPEAKER_03: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: They say she's fine.
SPEAKER_04: Want one?
SPEAKER_04: Give them to Dr. Wang.
SPEAKER_04: Dr. Wang, have some buns.
SPEAKER_03: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_04: Fengxia's child won't be mute, will he?
SPEAKER_18: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_04: Will the baby be crippled?
SPEAKER_18: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_18: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_18: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_18: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_04: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_04: "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_18: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_18: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_04: "Little Bun."
SPEAKER_18: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_18: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_04: But it's a tradition.
SPEAKER_04: Cat, Dog or Little Bun...
SPEAKER_04: are not recorded in the Register of Names.
SPEAKER_04: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_04: He doesn't know those kids exist...
SPEAKER_04: so they don't die.
SPEAKER_04: That's what the old folks say.
SPEAKER_04: Okay, then Little Bun it is.
SPEAKER_04: For now, anyway.
SPEAKER_04: Later, his dad can give him a proper name.
SPEAKER_02: Where's the family of Xu Fengxia?
SPEAKER_02: It's a boy, 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_03: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_02: We said it would be fine!
SPEAKER_02: Comrade, how's my daughter?
SPEAKER_04: Fine. Mother and son are fine.
SPEAKER_04: Is he normal?
SPEAKER_04: Absolutely.
SPEAKER_03: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_02: No, there's danger of infection.
SPEAKER_04: Let us have a quick peek, please?
SPEAKER_03: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_08: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_06: It's a boy.
SPEAKER_06: They are fine. He's 7.9 pounds.
SPEAKER_13: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_13: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_16: - Have a look.
- Not yet!
SPEAKER_12: Please, I'm the father!
SPEAKER_02: It doesn't matter. We're not done yet.
SPEAKER_02: Wait outside. When we're finished,
you can see her as much as you want.
SPEAKER_02: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_12: Is it a boy?
SPEAKER_12: Yes, 7.9 pounds!
SPEAKER_13: - How is he?
- They're both fine!
SPEAKER_16: Erxi, you're a lucky man!
SPEAKER_08: My son was only 5.5 pounds.
SPEAKER_08: 7.9 pounds is excellent.
SPEAKER_15: If you get a car from the factory...
SPEAKER_15: we can drive Fengxia home.
SPEAKER_01: Good idea.
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, seeing as they are both fine...
SPEAKER_04: why don't you see Dr. Wang back.
SPEAKER_16: What's with him?
SPEAKER_16: He ate too quickly.
SPEAKER_25: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_25: Yes, just gobbled them up.
SPEAKER_24: Quick, get some water.
SPEAKER_15: You two get the car, we'll be fine.
SPEAKER_15: Have some water.
SPEAKER_03: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_04: Some water should help.
SPEAKER_03: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_03: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_03: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_03: Help us!
SPEAKER_03: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_03: Quick!
SPEAKER_13: Don't panic. Think of something.
SPEAKER_22: We're just students.
We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_03: Wouldn't Dr. Wang know?
SPEAKER_29: Yes, he's a professor.
SPEAKER_02: He'd know for sure.
SPEAKER_02: He'll know.
SPEAKER_13: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_13: What's wrong with him? What happened?
SPEAKER_03: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_13: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_08: He gobbled up seven buns.
SPEAKER_08: He was starving.
SPEAKER_08: But he was okay after the water.
SPEAKER_05: It was the water that did it.
SPEAKER_16: Never mind. Drag him over!
SPEAKER_16: She's bleeding! Quick!
SPEAKER_22: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_22: You'll pull through!
SPEAKER_22: It's all right.
SPEAKER_22: Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_14: Dr. Wang!
SPEAKER_13: - Feeling better?
- Not at all.
SPEAKER_13: Oxygen.
SPEAKER_22: Fengxia! You'll pull through.
Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_22: Please, Doctor, she's my only daughter.
SPEAKER_00: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_11: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_11: Some years later...
SPEAKER_02: Grandpa! It's crooked again.
SPEAKER_03: Is it?
SPEAKER_03: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_03: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_02: Granny, your medicine.
SPEAKER_02: Back already?
SPEAKER_02: Has Little Bun been a good boy?
SPEAKER_02: I delivered 10 thermoses of water.
SPEAKER_04: Such a good little boy.
SPEAKER_04: Ten whole thermoses.
SPEAKER_03: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_03: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_18: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_18: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_02: I light the fire?
SPEAKER_03: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_04: I want to visit Fengxia's grave again...
SPEAKER_04: and take Little Bun's photos...
SPEAKER_04: to show her.
SPEAKER_04: He's another year older.
SPEAKER_04: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_15: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_15: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_15: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_15: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_03: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_02: Grandpa, where will the chicks live?
SPEAKER_03: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_03: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_02: Youqing eats dumplings.
SPEAKER_02: Fengxia looks at photos.
SPEAKER_02: Little Bun, do you know who Youqing is?
SPEAKER_04: Uncle.
SPEAKER_04: - And Fengxia?
- Mommy.
SPEAKER_06: What a clever boy!
SPEAKER_02: Granny, why all the photos for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_04: Before you were born...
SPEAKER_04: Granny said to mommy that...
SPEAKER_04: she should take a photo every year.
SPEAKER_03: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_03: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_18: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_18: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_04: He always carries on like this.
SPEAKER_16: It's okay.
SPEAKER_18: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_18: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_18: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_18: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_18: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_18: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_04: Erxi, is it true that Dr. Wang...
SPEAKER_04: won't eat buns, only rice now?
SPEAKER_16: Not just buns...
SPEAKER_16: anything made from wheat.
SPEAKER_18: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_04: What a food bill he must have.
SPEAKER_15: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_15: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_15: Little Bun, behave yourself.
SPEAKER_02: Grandpa, where'll we put the chicks?
SPEAKER_02: Let's see.
SPEAKER_03: How about in here?
SPEAKER_03: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_03: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_03: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_03: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_02: When will they grow up?
SPEAKER_02: Very soon.
SPEAKER_02: And then?
SPEAKER_03: And then...
SPEAKER_03: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_03: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_03: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_02: And after the oxen?
SPEAKER_06: After oxen...
SPEAKER_06: After oxen, Little Bun will grow up.
SPEAKER_02: I want to ride on an ox's back!
SPEAKER_04: You will ride on an ox's back.
SPEAKER_03: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...
SPEAKER_18: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_18: and life will get better and better.