SPEAKER_02: Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_02: No, no. I think it's better alone.
SPEAKER_02: Or I introduce him.
Gustavo Rojas.
SPEAKER_02: Gustavo Rojas, he is chief
of the Kawiyarí tribe...
SPEAKER_02: Well, there's many different ones.
Like Tucanos, and some others...
SPEAKER_02: Let's stop for a minute. One question.
She will ask so you can answer that...
SPEAKER_02: This is the first recorded
game of the Atlético Nacional,
SPEAKER_02: in this filmic document
of the Pelbet company.
SPEAKER_02: We will present indistinctly,
according to journalistic consideration
SPEAKER_02: the main games, the ones
we consider essential
SPEAKER_02: for the conquer of the title of 1981.
SPEAKER_02: The first goal was scored by
Victor Luna and Guillermo La Rosa
SPEAKER_02: from the midfield, inside the area
SPEAKER_02: so that he can be, as
usually, close to the goal.
SPEAKER_02: Apparently, the foul can't
be seen clear enough.
SPEAKER_02: But let’s have a look
from the reverse angle.
SPEAKER_02: The one from the cameras at the other side
of the goal, placed by Pelbet’s company.
SPEAKER_02: Look at that karate blow from Gonzalez
Aquino to the peruvian Cesar Cueto.