SPEAKER_16: Come often. You're always welcome.
SPEAKER_16: Don't worry about her.
SPEAKER_16: Get out of my sight!
SPEAKER_16: What happened? No one's left?
SPEAKER_16: - Shouldn't we run, too?
- Where to?
SPEAKER_16: This is too much.
SPEAKER_16: I'll hit him again if I have to.
SPEAKER_16: Sit then. Right in front of me!
SPEAKER_16: You little bastard! I'll break your legs!
SPEAKER_16: There's trouble at your home.
SPEAKER_16: Red Guards are swarming over the place.
SPEAKER_16: I just caught them on a ladder,
pulling off roof tiles.
SPEAKER_16: No idea! The leader is a cripple.
SPEAKER_16: You just have to!
SPEAKER_16: We've been through the valley of death.
SPEAKER_16: Coming out alive wasn't easy.
SPEAKER_16: Can't you see?
SPEAKER_16: Do you hear him?
SPEAKER_16: Are they in there?
SPEAKER_16: We'll see them soon.
SPEAKER_16: Did he eat all seven buns?
SPEAKER_16: Yes, just gobbled them up.