SPEAKER_17: Mr. Long'er says
if you're busy he'll take a rain check.
SPEAKER_17: Might never go home again.
SPEAKER_17: What are you looking at?
SPEAKER_17: Thinking of escaping?
SPEAKER_17: The Nationalists will shoot you.
SPEAKER_17: Besides...
SPEAKER_17: troops for both sides are everywhere.
SPEAKER_17: If you don't fight the Reds,
you fight the KMT.
SPEAKER_17: But who will look after my wife,
my kids, my old mother?
SPEAKER_17: Forget it. Try to save your own skin.
SPEAKER_17: As for me...
SPEAKER_17: if I weren't looking for my brother,
I wouldn't be wearing this uniform.
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng, you really are mad.
SPEAKER_17: The wounded.
SPEAKER_17: No one's left.
SPEAKER_17: Must be tens of thousands
of us trapped here.
SPEAKER_17: Put it on. We must survive.
SPEAKER_17: Lao Quan, have a drink.
SPEAKER_17: We must help each other.
SPEAKER_17: Besides, we're from the same town.
SPEAKER_17: Lao Quan, the place is deserted.
SPEAKER_17: I meant to call...
SPEAKER_17: after I settled in.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: Take this for now.
SPEAKER_17: Tell me what else I can do.
SPEAKER_17: I owe you a life.
SPEAKER_17: I will remember.
SPEAKER_17: But there were so many people,
I didn't come in.
SPEAKER_17: Fugui!
SPEAKER_17: Who's there?
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_17: Who?
SPEAKER_17: It'll just take a minute.
SPEAKER_17: Well?
SPEAKER_17: Fugui...
SPEAKER_17: I've always felt terrible about Youqing.
SPEAKER_17: I've often tried to give you money.
You'd never accept it.
SPEAKER_17: It's all in this account. Take it.
SPEAKER_17: Take this...
SPEAKER_17: and my heart will be at ease.
SPEAKER_17: Yesterday, my wife killed herself.
SPEAKER_17: I don't think I can.
SPEAKER_17: I snuck out just now...
SPEAKER_17: and better get back.
SPEAKER_17: Chunsheng, remember...