SPEAKER_13: No, like Jiazhen.
SPEAKER_13: What's his name?
SPEAKER_13: I'd heard you'd had a boy,
and were living at home.
SPEAKER_13: But I was too ashamed to see you.
SPEAKER_13: What's that sound?
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng and I are lucky
to meet someone as nice as you.
SPEAKER_13: You've looked after us.
SPEAKER_13: And live a good life.
SPEAKER_13: Must not be politically backward.
You can sleep later.
SPEAKER_13: Are 15 dumplings enough?
SPEAKER_13: Have 20. You should eat more.
SPEAKER_13: how could it be your son?
SPEAKER_13: Chunsheng.
SPEAKER_13: How about in here?
SPEAKER_13: This box is bigger, isn't it?
SPEAKER_13: They'll have more room to run around.
SPEAKER_13: Then they'll eat more.
SPEAKER_13: And soon they'll grow up.
SPEAKER_13: And then...