SPEAKER_22: I'm home.
SPEAKER_22: Home.
SPEAKER_22: I brought some colleagues.
SPEAKER_22: We're fixing the place up.
SPEAKER_22: We replaced the roof tiles...
SPEAKER_22: so it wouldn't leak anymore.
SPEAKER_22: And we've painted Chairman Mao's portrait.
SPEAKER_22: Fengxia helped us.
SPEAKER_22: Dad, Mom...
SPEAKER_22: I'm taking Fengxia.
SPEAKER_22: I'll look after her.
SPEAKER_22: I'll be going.
SPEAKER_22: Never mind.
SPEAKER_22: Jiazhen, I know you don't want to see me.
SPEAKER_22: I'll leave my gift here and be gone.
SPEAKER_22: Lunch is all taken care of.
SPEAKER_22: Dad, Mom, we're having a baby.
SPEAKER_22: I had the photo framed.
SPEAKER_22: No.
SPEAKER_22: I just got an official notice.
SPEAKER_22: Comrade, are there any doctors?
SPEAKER_22: I was putting on a show.
SPEAKER_22: We're not accusing you.
SPEAKER_22: My wife's having a baby.
SPEAKER_22: I wanted you here for her sake.
SPEAKER_22: The only child I have left.
SPEAKER_22: We should've bought them
on the way home.
SPEAKER_22: Now we've got to carry them!
SPEAKER_22: Careful! Don't drop them!
SPEAKER_22: - I'll make dinner.
- I'll help.
SPEAKER_22: No, you're tired. You two have a rest.
I'll do it.
SPEAKER_22: Little Bun, behave yourself.