SPEAKER_08: Chalk it up.
SPEAKER_08: How much?
SPEAKER_08: But my calligraphy's improving.
SPEAKER_08: Long'er, you neglect your troupe.
SPEAKER_08: But not my money.
They sound like a pack of mules.
SPEAKER_08: I learned all I know from you.
SPEAKER_08: How do you think we lost
most of what we had in the first place?
SPEAKER_08: You're the one they call big bastard, Xu,
not me!
SPEAKER_08: Don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: It's not good for the baby.
SPEAKER_08: All right, do it yourself. But please don't cry.
SPEAKER_08: Fugui...
SPEAKER_08: Can't rush these things.
SPEAKER_08: Fengxia's growing up. Another's on the way.
SPEAKER_08: My luck's changed.
SPEAKER_08: Write that down. Another round.
SPEAKER_08: Well?
SPEAKER_08: No, have him wait. I'll be right there.
SPEAKER_08: This is the last time, okay? I promise.
SPEAKER_08: Go home, go.
SPEAKER_08: It's settled.
SPEAKER_08: get a rickshaw to take my wife home. I'm...
SPEAKER_08: Of course.
SPEAKER_08: You can't just win and walk away.
SPEAKER_08: The game's not over yet!
SPEAKER_08: We'll formalize the transfer in a few days...
SPEAKER_08: and explain to your old man.
SPEAKER_08: Just settle everything, okay?
SPEAKER_08: We'll settle everything then.
SPEAKER_08: Okay?
SPEAKER_08: Mother's feeling better.
SPEAKER_08: Normally she doesn't even get out of bed.
SPEAKER_08: Just call me Fugui.
SPEAKER_08: "Don't Gamble" is my son's name.
SPEAKER_08: You mocking me?
SPEAKER_08: No, his real name's Youqing.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen came back with him.
SPEAKER_08: We almost called him "Don't Gamble."
SPEAKER_08: I'd like to borrow money to set up a shop.
SPEAKER_08: - Where'd you get them?
- Off the corpses.
SPEAKER_08: They won't shoot us?
SPEAKER_08: Not as long as you've got your hands up.
SPEAKER_08: - The attack hasn't started.
- Let's put them down.
SPEAKER_08: - On one of the wounded.
- It's a killing field.
SPEAKER_08: Fengxia!
SPEAKER_08: It's your daddy.
SPEAKER_08: What are you doing?
SPEAKER_08: Where's mommy?
SPEAKER_08: we sang for the Liberation Army.
SPEAKER_08: Suppose I was singing for her, too.
SPEAKER_08: How come Fengxia can't talk?
SPEAKER_08: Fugui's back.
SPEAKER_08: This is our town leader, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_08: You participated in the revolution.
SPEAKER_08: I just dragged a cannon and sang opera.
SPEAKER_08: That's taking part.
SPEAKER_08: That wasn't ours.
It was counterrevolutionary timber.
SPEAKER_08: Five bullets. Five.
SPEAKER_08: They shot him.
SPEAKER_08: Pumped five bullets into him.
SPEAKER_08: He is dead.
SPEAKER_08: If I hadn't lost my home to him...
SPEAKER_08: that'd have been me.
SPEAKER_08: What class do we belong to?
SPEAKER_08: Landlords?
SPEAKER_08: Surely not. We lost that status to Long'er.
So, what are we?
SPEAKER_08: Sounds okay to me.
And I took part in the revolution.
SPEAKER_08: - What are you looking for?
- That certificate.
SPEAKER_08: It's good to be poor. Nothing like it.
SPEAKER_08: You can leave those.
SPEAKER_08: We won't touch them.
SPEAKER_08: We're off to the next house.
SPEAKER_08: Said he was a saboteur. I had to.
SPEAKER_08: Why wouldn't he just apologize?
SPEAKER_08: I hit him for not obeying.
SPEAKER_08: That's no excuse.
SPEAKER_08: You spoil him.
SPEAKER_08: How so?
SPEAKER_08: Can't you see I'm doing this for our family?
SPEAKER_08: Don't you understand?
SPEAKER_08: If you indulge him, we'll all go to ruin.
SPEAKER_08: Daddy will make it better.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, after dinner...
SPEAKER_08: come see the show.
SPEAKER_08: Youqing's not going to any stupid show.
SPEAKER_08: He uses the secret mirror
SPEAKER_08: and blinds all who look within
SPEAKER_08: I yell there's no time to waste
SPEAKER_08: Far away, we flee with haste
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen, where's Youqing?
SPEAKER_08: We've smelted our steel...
SPEAKER_08: and reached our production target.
SPEAKER_08: We're off to report the good news.
SPEAKER_08: There'll be dumplings
at the canteen tonight...
SPEAKER_08: Fifteen years, we'll surpass America.
SPEAKER_08: He won't be able to sleep or eat
or ever take a dump...
SPEAKER_08: Youqing, wake up. We're nearly there.
SPEAKER_08: When you get there...
SPEAKER_08: put your dumplings in hot water.
SPEAKER_08: Make sure you make them hot enough.
SPEAKER_08: Cold dumplings are bad for the tummy.
SPEAKER_08: - Do you like dumplings?
- Yes.
SPEAKER_08: - Do you like meat?
SPEAKER_08: That's good.
SPEAKER_08: If Youqing does as daddy says...
SPEAKER_08: our lives will get better and better.
SPEAKER_08: Our family...
SPEAKER_08: is like a little chicken.
SPEAKER_08: When it grows up, it becomes a goose.
SPEAKER_08: And that'll turn into a sheep.
SPEAKER_08: The sheep will turn into an ox.
SPEAKER_08: After the ox is Communism.
SPEAKER_08: And there'll be dumplings and meat
every day.
SPEAKER_08: It's Fugui's son?
SPEAKER_08: You're the District Chief?
SPEAKER_08: It was you who killed my son?
SPEAKER_08: I had only one son, Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_08: I had only one son!
SPEAKER_08: And you killed him!
SPEAKER_08: I think you should go, Chief.
SPEAKER_08: Sit here.
SPEAKER_08: You have to get rid of those puppets.
SPEAKER_08: Don't you see what they are?
SPEAKER_08: Let's not bring up the past.
SPEAKER_08: Burn them, okay?
I've got other people to see.
SPEAKER_08: I've found just the man for her.
SPEAKER_08: He is the leader of the factory's Red Guards.
SPEAKER_08: He'd like to meet her.
SPEAKER_08: Sounds too good. Will he go for Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: He's also got a handicap...
SPEAKER_08: Yes, and run if he has to.
SPEAKER_08: You won't stay?
SPEAKER_08: Have some lunch first.
SPEAKER_08: No, really.
SPEAKER_08: From where?
SPEAKER_08: You're just in time. We've just finished.
SPEAKER_08: - Don't rush off!
- I'll make you something to eat.
SPEAKER_08: Do stay! Come on inside.
SPEAKER_08: "The working class leads us all."
SPEAKER_08: He painted all the Chairman Maos
in our factory!
SPEAKER_08: We're happy if you are.
SPEAKER_08: Anytime. You decide.
SPEAKER_08: At least it's loud enough for her to hear.
SPEAKER_08: Congratulations on Fengxia's wedding.
SPEAKER_08: - When did you get here?
- A while ago.
SPEAKER_08: Come on inside.
SPEAKER_08: Jiazhen, make some tea.
SPEAKER_08: Isn't the tea ready yet?
SPEAKER_08: Chunsheng's been here for ages.
SPEAKER_08: Sit with us for a bit.
SPEAKER_08: Don't be like that.
SPEAKER_08: Come as soon as the water's ready.
SPEAKER_08: But here's boiled water.
SPEAKER_08: Chunsheng came to wish Fengxia well.
SPEAKER_08: You can't go on avoiding him.
SPEAKER_08: Can't we put this behind us?
SPEAKER_08: But it's Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_08: Better when you come over.
SPEAKER_08: Help me with the table.
SPEAKER_08: No wonder there's a bottle!
SPEAKER_08: Really?
SPEAKER_08: Cheers!
SPEAKER_08: Don't bring up the past.
SPEAKER_08: I was a real no-hoper.
SPEAKER_08: But things are better now.
SPEAKER_08: And will be better for your child.
SPEAKER_08: This is great.
SPEAKER_08: Of course.
SPEAKER_08: There's always been a line.
SPEAKER_08: Haven't had much to do with him for years.
SPEAKER_08: You came for this?
SPEAKER_08: All my debts will have been paid.
SPEAKER_08: What do you mean?
SPEAKER_08: Killed herself?
SPEAKER_08: Why?
SPEAKER_08: I don't know.
SPEAKER_08: Have you seen her body?
SPEAKER_08: You mustn't lose hope.
SPEAKER_08: Don't go getting any stupid ideas.
SPEAKER_08: You must bear it, no matter what!
SPEAKER_08: You can't take that road yourself.
SPEAKER_08: I don't want to live anymore!
SPEAKER_08: Let's say we accept this money.
SPEAKER_08: Keep it for us. There's plenty of time.
SPEAKER_08: I know how difficult it must be...
SPEAKER_08: but you've got to pull through...
SPEAKER_08: you've got to bear it!
SPEAKER_08: Yes, come in.
SPEAKER_08: No, thank you, I've got to go.
SPEAKER_08: Fengxia's about to give birth?
SPEAKER_08: Time does fly!
SPEAKER_08: Erxi sent word from the hospital.
SPEAKER_08: She's in labor. We're on our way there.
SPEAKER_08: You, a capitalist?
SPEAKER_08: Everyone knows you.
SPEAKER_08: Niu, don't let it get to you. Take care!
SPEAKER_08: Everything's fine and normal.
SPEAKER_08: Okay, we're going.
SPEAKER_08: - Sorry for the trouble.
- It's our job.
SPEAKER_08: The Red Guards are in control!
SPEAKER_08: To show him the heirs
of this new, Red world.
SPEAKER_08: No, it's better if I wear it.
SPEAKER_08: Let me wear it!
SPEAKER_08: How's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_08: Take your time. There's plenty.
SPEAKER_08: to think of a name for the kid?
SPEAKER_08: What name do you like?
SPEAKER_08: - Already?
- We didn't hear a sound.
SPEAKER_08: Can we see them?
SPEAKER_08: Please, comrade, just one peek?
SPEAKER_08: Dad! Mom! Has she given birth?
SPEAKER_08: Good idea.
SPEAKER_08: Careful, it's hot.
SPEAKER_08: Why'd he do that?
SPEAKER_08: He's been locked up without food.
He scoffed those buns.
SPEAKER_08: Drink it slowly.
SPEAKER_08: Help us!
SPEAKER_08: She's bleeding! We don't know what to do.
SPEAKER_08: Quick!
SPEAKER_08: He's eaten too much.
SPEAKER_08: Is it?
SPEAKER_08: I'll fix it.
SPEAKER_08: Take the medicine to Granny.
SPEAKER_08: Have you had your medicine?
SPEAKER_08: I'll make lunch.
SPEAKER_08: Yes, and I'll make some noodles.
SPEAKER_08: Are you happy?
SPEAKER_08: Where will they live?
SPEAKER_08: I'll find a home for them when we get back.
SPEAKER_08: If I hadn't given Dr. Wang those buns...
SPEAKER_08: everything would've been fine.
SPEAKER_08: the chickens will turn into geese...
SPEAKER_08: and the geese will turn into sheep...
SPEAKER_08: and the sheep will turn into oxen.
SPEAKER_08: Little Bun won't ride on an ox...