SPEAKER_00: He's just singing to himself.
SPEAKER_00: You're up.
SPEAKER_00: What's wrong?
SPEAKER_00: What are you crying for?
SPEAKER_00: If nothing else, can't you think of the baby?
SPEAKER_00: Youqing, excellent.
SPEAKER_00: I've paid the rent with mother's jewelry.
SPEAKER_00: It's crowded with all of us here.
SPEAKER_00: Which corpses?
SPEAKER_00: Dying like this,
their families won't even know.
SPEAKER_00: Mother died without knowing where I was.
SPEAKER_00: She was fine when I left.
SPEAKER_00: She can't even say "Daddy."
SPEAKER_00: He joined the army as a driver.
He went south with them.
SPEAKER_00: He burnt it?
SPEAKER_00: they captured two mountains a day.
SPEAKER_00: This hasn't anything to do with us adults.
SPEAKER_00: We don't know what's going on.
SPEAKER_00: Do you expect me to believe that?
SPEAKER_00: How do you like my singing?
SPEAKER_00: Pack a lunchbox. I'll wake him.
SPEAKER_00: Smelting steel is a duty.
We can't be politically backward.
SPEAKER_00: Mr. Niu praised us in front of everyone.
SPEAKER_00: Youqing has to go.
SPEAKER_00: Wake up.
SPEAKER_00: You have to go smelt steel.
SPEAKER_00: I was telling Jiazhen...
SPEAKER_00: that we could...
SPEAKER_00: do propaganda shows.
SPEAKER_00: Put these old things to new use.
SPEAKER_00: They always remind Jiazhen of Youqing.
SPEAKER_00: Delivering water is fine.
SPEAKER_00: Jiazhen's health is poor.
If we're together, I can look after her.
SPEAKER_00: We'll discuss it later.
SPEAKER_00: He can run?
SPEAKER_00: His leg's not so bad, and he seems nice.
SPEAKER_00: I approve.
SPEAKER_00: If it doesn't work out, we'll keep looking.
SPEAKER_00: Anyway, it's up to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_00: Anything is possible.
SPEAKER_00: Mr. Niu said he was a Red Guard.
SPEAKER_00: Erxi, drink up.
SPEAKER_00: Just say what you want.
SPEAKER_00: Who examined Fengxia?
SPEAKER_00: They did.
SPEAKER_00: You haven't seen any doctors?
SPEAKER_00: No doctors?
SPEAKER_00: We need an experienced doctor.
SPEAKER_00: Even if he only stands by, we would relax.
SPEAKER_00: Just hungry.
SPEAKER_00: Hasn't been fed for three days!
SPEAKER_00: I'll go buy some buns.
SPEAKER_00: Of course not. She wasn't born that way.
SPEAKER_00: Erxi's is a work-related injury.
It's not hereditary.
SPEAKER_00: Anyway, it's bad luck to talk like that.
SPEAKER_00: Why not use this time...
SPEAKER_00: - Don't be stupid.
- It was a joke.
SPEAKER_00: You just say anything!
SPEAKER_00: That's not a name!
SPEAKER_00: Little Bun...
SPEAKER_00: give me a hand.
SPEAKER_00: Fine, I'll let Erxi know.
SPEAKER_00: Little Bun! Hold onto those chicks.
SPEAKER_00: He could have saved our Fengxia.
SPEAKER_00: He's a professor, after all.
SPEAKER_00: We shouldn't have given him water.
SPEAKER_00: People say, once you drink water...
SPEAKER_00: one bun in the stomach turns to seven.
SPEAKER_00: Dr. Wang ate seven buns.
SPEAKER_00: Seven times seven is 49.
SPEAKER_00: It's much too much.
SPEAKER_00: Rice costs more than wheat.
SPEAKER_00: he'll ride trains and planes...
SPEAKER_00: and life will get better and better.