SPEAKER_12: Why don't you have a go?
Show them what it takes.
SPEAKER_12: Business is good, Mr. Xie.
SPEAKER_12: Why don't you go home?
There'll be other times.
SPEAKER_12: Your wife is right here.
SPEAKER_12: What's with you?
Can't take "no" for an answer?
SPEAKER_12: You want to make me lose face? Go away!
SPEAKER_12: I'll look after her for a few days?
SPEAKER_12: Until you're set up elsewhere.
SPEAKER_12: Want me to help you?
SPEAKER_12: A rare visitor indeed.
SPEAKER_12: Master Fugui! It's been a year at least.
SPEAKER_12: I'm not one to lend money.
SPEAKER_12: I'll lend you something else. More practical.
SPEAKER_12: They are fabulous.
SPEAKER_12: My heart is full of sorrow
SPEAKER_12: It's that hateful bandit, Jiang
SPEAKER_12: I'm lucky to be alive
SPEAKER_12: He gets compensation.
SPEAKER_12: Shall we invite him over?
Fengxia can check him out.
SPEAKER_12: He was very busy?
SPEAKER_12: Dad, I saw Chunsheng yesterday.
SPEAKER_12: We have to draw a line between us and him.
SPEAKER_12: They say she's great. No problems.
SPEAKER_12: From the contractions, not right now.
SPEAKER_12: Fengxia, don't be nervous.