SPEAKER_03: ERA International (HK) Ltd. Presents
SPEAKER_03: In Association with Shanghai Film Studios
SPEAKER_03: Producer: Chiu Fusheng
SPEAKER_03: Executive Producers:
Kow Fuhong and Christopher Tseng
SPEAKER_03: Associate Producer: Barbara Robinson
SPEAKER_03: Adaptation from Yu Hua's novel
SPEAKER_03: TO LIVE
SPEAKER_03: Script: Yu Hua and Lu Wei
SPEAKER_03: Screenplay: Lu Wei
SPEAKER_03: Director of Photography: Lu Yue
SPEAKER_03: Art Direction: Cao Jiuping
SPEAKER_03: Sound: Tao Jiping
SPEAKER_03: Music: Zhao Jiping
SPEAKER_03: Editor: Du Yuan
SPEAKER_03: Starring:
Ge You - Gong Li
SPEAKER_03: Directed by Zhang Yimou
SPEAKER_03: The 1940s
SPEAKER_03: I have nothing left.
SPEAKER_03: 63, 73, 83...
SPEAKER_03: Needles and threads for sale!
SPEAKER_03: One, two, three. One, two, three.
SPEAKER_03: Chunsheng!
SPEAKER_03: Take that!
SPEAKER_03: - Enough?
- No!
SPEAKER_03: Don't hit him!
SPEAKER_03: Youqing! What's going on?
SPEAKER_03: Let me see him!
SPEAKER_03: The 1960s
SPEAKER_03: June 1966: Start of the
"Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution."
SPEAKER_03: It lasted 10 years...
SPEAKER_03: and left no family unaffected.
SPEAKER_03: - You're eating?
- Come on in, Mr. Niu.
SPEAKER_03: - Don't let me interrupt.
- We're finished.
SPEAKER_03: Clear a path! Ship sailing through!
SPEAKER_03: Let's get the whole family.
SPEAKER_03: The ship of revolution! Advance
through the storm with Chairman Mao!
SPEAKER_03: Come over here.
SPEAKER_03: Now, bow!
SPEAKER_03: Go on, don't be sad.
SPEAKER_03: You'll be back!
SPEAKER_03: Get Dr. Wang over here.
SPEAKER_03: Please, Doctor, please!
SPEAKER_03: Oxygen.
SPEAKER_03: Fengxia! Mommy's here. Don't be afraid.
SPEAKER_03: Some years later...