SPEAKER_24: The Xu family home...
SPEAKER_24: goes to Long'er.
SPEAKER_24: And the debt is hereby settled.
SPEAKER_24: What a bloodbath.
SPEAKER_24: They're freezing.
SPEAKER_24: No one's looking after them?
SPEAKER_24: Was it from some dead officer?
SPEAKER_24: I'm still dizzy from drinking!
SPEAKER_24: How could that be?
SPEAKER_24: The Reds must be on the attack.
SPEAKER_24: Home!
SPEAKER_24: Home?
SPEAKER_24: Wait right here.
SPEAKER_24: Run now...
SPEAKER_24: and you'll be shot.
SPEAKER_24: Better to wait and become a POW.
SPEAKER_24: The Reds send POWs home.
SPEAKER_24: That's right.
SPEAKER_24: You want to go home, don't run.
SPEAKER_24: How?
SPEAKER_24: Don't reach for your waist!
SPEAKER_24: Do that and you're dead.
SPEAKER_24: The Reds treat POWs well.
I've been one before.
SPEAKER_24: Just put those hands up.
SPEAKER_24: Where did you find this coat?
SPEAKER_24: The coat's from my brother's unit.