SPEAKER_21: You were with Chunsheng.
Why isn't he back?
SPEAKER_21: Fugui, you're back just in time...
SPEAKER_21: But it's not just that.
SPEAKER_21: The government wanted part of the house.
SPEAKER_21: He refused, beat up a cadre...
SPEAKER_21: and then set fire to the place.
SPEAKER_21: Classic counterrevolutionary sabotage.
SPEAKER_21: It burnt for days.
SPEAKER_21: Your timber was first class!
SPEAKER_21: Everyone will be thirsty.
SPEAKER_21: We'll take these.
SPEAKER_21: We're racing towards Communism,
and you worry about food?
SPEAKER_21: We are setting up communal kitchens.
SPEAKER_21: When you're hungry...
SPEAKER_21: We are just two bullets short
of liberating Taiwan.
SPEAKER_21: So let's get that metal.
SPEAKER_21: The workers deserve entertaining,
don't they?
SPEAKER_21: You know, I sang for the Liberation Army...
SPEAKER_21: and after that...
SPEAKER_21: I see your point.
SPEAKER_21: All I've seen at the worksites
are student marching bands.
SPEAKER_21: We'll spur them on with puppet shows.
SPEAKER_21: Sure we are. We'll definitely liberate Taiwan.
SPEAKER_21: Everyone's earned merit.
SPEAKER_21: Fugui, Jiazhen,
you've made a real contribution.
SPEAKER_21: We've made enough steel
for three cannon balls.
SPEAKER_21: They'll all go to Taiwan!
SPEAKER_21: One to land on Chiang Kai-shek's bed...
SPEAKER_21: another on his dinner table...
SPEAKER_21: and the last in the toilet!
SPEAKER_21: The District Chief has come.
SPEAKER_21: Everyone knows about them.
SPEAKER_21: Emperors, scholars and beauties.
SPEAKER_21: Classic feudal types.
SPEAKER_21: Fetch a brazier.
SPEAKER_21: He works in a factory in the county seat.
SPEAKER_21: Does she mind us playing matchmaker?
SPEAKER_21: She's not opposed,
she does fret about leaving us.
SPEAKER_21: Comrade Wan Erxi's here.
SPEAKER_21: His father and grandfather
were workers, too.
SPEAKER_21: Solid working class stock.
SPEAKER_21: Where's Fengxia?
SPEAKER_21: Comrade Fengxia.
SPEAKER_21: Let's go.
SPEAKER_21: Today comrades, Wan Erxi and Xu Fengxia...
SPEAKER_21: begin their wedded life.
SPEAKER_21: In good times, we think of Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_21: Let's sing a song!
SPEAKER_21: First, pay respects to Chairman Mao.
SPEAKER_21: What are these eggs for?
SPEAKER_21: Another working class member on the way!
SPEAKER_21: So we've got to get going.
SPEAKER_21: What's happened?
SPEAKER_21: I'm no longer head of the township.
SPEAKER_21: They say I'm a capitalist.
SPEAKER_21: I have to confess my crimes.
SPEAKER_21: I have faith in the Party.
SPEAKER_21: Let's not talk about it.
SPEAKER_21: You go to Fengxia.
SPEAKER_21: Go now, I'll be okay.
SPEAKER_21: Send her my very best. She's producing
a little revolutionary successor.